http://www.businessinsider.com/bitcoin-back-to-1000-2014-1/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Sat, 12 Jul 2014 00:30:52 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: web3 (via varnish2)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 8955
X-Varnish: 1670498786
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 54.198.14.178
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>Bitcoin Is On A Huge Tear Again</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/bitcoin-back-to-1000-2014-1/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 20:30:52 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Joe Weisenthal</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cb022e6da811e5489ac557</guid>
				<title>AlephBlog</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 14:21:18 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cb022e6da811e5489ac557</link>
				<description>Bitcoin, like a promoted penny stock, is easily manipulated, because there is little intrinsic value</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52ca5acb6bb3f781314f26e2</guid>
				<title>You're dumb</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 02:27:07 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52ca5acb6bb3f781314f26e2</link>
				<description>'nough said.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9e7daeab8ea12474f26d7</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 18:16:42 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9e7daeab8ea12474f26d7</link>
				<description>For the first time in my life I can honestly say I WANT people to lose their money. Usually I feel bad for people who get scammed, but if you're buying Bitcoin you really do deserve to lose your money. If you can't see the writing on the wall, then it is time to thin out the herd.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9c49069beddc1424f26d4</guid>
				<title>anjansons</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 15:46:08 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9c49069beddc1424f26d4</link>
				<description>Why do I think that Bitcoin will thrive? Because even if the core Bitcoin protocol is not as good for certain types of transactions, services can be built upon it. Enter Mastercoin, that tried to build a new layer on Bitcoin that would allow for decentralized exchanges, smart money and contracts and securities etc. What they did was they basically created their own coin on Bitcoin Blockchain and similarly to Kickstarter, wrote about their idea and encouraged people to buy Mastercoins as sort of shares of their enterprise. They received some 600 000 USD in Bitcoin and now, due to Bitcoin and Mastercoin price increase, they have about 8-10 million USD to develop their service.

Now I ask you- which internet payment startup can get 8-10 million in 3 months?? Kickstarter? I believe the biggest ever project there was at 8 million? Plus the price of Bitcoin will still rise. Of course you can always go VC way, but will they just back some ''yet another project&quot;

Sure all this money cannot be withdrawn on the spot but it also does not need to be withdrawn on the spot. They can attract top programming talent with that and build their service, and if more people flock to buy Mastercoin, it's price rises, Bitcoin price rises too and they could soon look at 100 million dollars to develop their protocol. 

It's just a whole different ballgame. All those early adopters too, they see their coin value grow up by day. They cannot withdraw all of that at a time, but the market won't suffer if they withdraw say 2 million USD per day, exchanges can handle that. They can throw a lot of resources at a problem which regular start-ups with kids in garages just can't....</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9c1c8ecad040a0d4f26d1</guid>
				<title>anjansons</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 15:34:16 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9c1c8ecad040a0d4f26d1</link>
				<description>You don't need exchanges to buy and sell coins. If you are in America, you can use venture capital funded Coinbase to buy and sell Bitcoin. And then, if you want the big trading market of Mt.Gox, then just upload coins there and trade as you want, withdraw Bitcoins from Mt. Gox when you have grown (or lost) some and sell them on Coinbase or any other exchange that allows cash withdrawals (pretty much any other exchange except Mt. Gox).

In fact the only reason why Mt.Gox still thrives is that it doesn't need to even see your USD to be profitable. People love it because of the big volumes and I highly doubt that somebody buys coins there (due to their high price) and even more that somebody withdraws USD from there (due to the issues), but it's not needed because you can just trade Bitcoins for virtual USD ad nauseum there and cash out in Bitcoin. They just collect the trading fee in BTC. 

Major gambling sites like Satoshi Dice and Just-Dice just deal in Bitcoin. Upload Bitcoin and place bets in Bitcoin and collect winnings in Bitcoin. Just-Dice has more than 30 million USD worth of Bitcoins in their cold storage. Major exchanges have about 200 million USD or more in their accounts. 

Cryptsy is also an interesting exchange as they also do not deal with regular fiat currencies at all. They just take your Bitcoins, Litecoins etc. coins (trade between 60 crypto-currencies now) and let you trade between them and collect the fees in Bitcoin, Litecoin or whatever. 

Furthermore, miners buy new mining rigs for their earned Bitcoins. 

It's a healthy alive economy.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9b96d69bedd142b4f26d1</guid>
				<title>BitBillions</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 14:58:37 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9b96d69bedd142b4f26d1</link>
				<description>For those people who want to get into Bitcoin without spending massive amounts of money on mining hardware. Here is a way to get some every month. 

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitbillions.com/?refid=1LXxS1ht74BrnuwtiaBVgC9xrS25sVykzT&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.bitbillions.com/?refid=1LXxS1ht74BrnuwtiaBVgC9xrS25sVykzT&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9aee4eab8ea7c4f4f26d5</guid>
				<title>Jason Brand St</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 14:13:40 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9aee4eab8ea7c4f4f26d5</link>
				<description>So, how is it with withdrawals from BTC Exchanges?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9a6abeab8ea1c434f26d1</guid>
				<title>BTC_is_a_joke</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 13:38:35 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9a6abeab8ea1c434f26d1</link>
				<description>Doesn't mean dick when Mt.Gox doesn't allow withdrawals. Bitcoin is a fucking joke. Anymoe unregulated securities to sell me? The Internet has turned into a boiler room.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9a2b7ecad04b84f4f26db</guid>
				<title>huluplus</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 13:21:43 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c9a2b7ecad04b84f4f26db</link>
				<description>Look like'em be behr huntin' season.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c99cf4eab8ea612d4f26d5</guid>
				<title>Dogecoin</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 12:57:08 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c99cf4eab8ea612d4f26d5</link>
				<description>Dogecoin is a great new currency on the rise. 

get a wallet and post your addy and i will give you some. Get on the train!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c994b6ecad0452354f26d5</guid>
				<title>Bitcoin Exchange</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 12:21:58 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c994b6ecad0452354f26d5</link>
				<description>Great article. Bitcoin should be approached prudently with an eye towards risk management. We comment on this and similar issues on our blog. 

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitmorecoin.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.bitmorecoin.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

