http://www.businessinsider.com/bitcoin-inequality-2014-1/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Wed, 23 Jul 2014 14:23:13 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: web2 (via varnish3)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 21395
X-Varnish: 884717260
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 54.83.238.48
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>How Bitcoin Is Like North Korea</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/bitcoin-inequality-2014-1/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 10:23:13 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Joe Weisenthal</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52ebed396bb3f7ff6d2368f8</guid>
				<title>Pavel</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 13:36:41 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52ebed396bb3f7ff6d2368f8</link>
				<description>Exactly, plus there is currently 24,412,755 addresses with 0-0.001 BTC in it BUT you can create infinite those address by yourself - I personally created around 100 already. There is never going to be equal distribution as majority of people will be selling with 50 % profit and buying legal drugs for that. Those big ones are not there only by luck.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d592dd69beddb254d4ec43</guid>
				<title>Rassah</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 14:41:17 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d592dd69beddb254d4ec43</link>
				<description>I think I've spent over $10k worth of bitcoin in just the last two months. I guess I'm not &quot;everyone.&quot; Or I guess everyone doesn't do as you say.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d5828469bedd362ed4ec37</guid>
				<title>Rassah</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 13:31:32 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d5828469bedd362ed4ec37</link>
				<description>Glad you caught and pointed that out in the last paragraph. Talking about unequal distribution of bitcoin is rather pointless at this extremely early stage, since 5 years ago, 1 person owned 100% of the wealth, and a month later, 1 person held 90% and two others held %5 each. Like stocks and other things that start from a single point, the initial distribution is always concentrated by default, and spreads out over time.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d57be0eab8ea152ed4ec37</guid>
				<title>Tearman</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 13:03:12 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d57be0eab8ea152ed4ec37</link>
				<description>God your stupidity hurts my eyes</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d5540d6bb3f71b4ad4ec39</guid>
				<title>BitcoinMillionare</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 10:13:17 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d5540d6bb3f71b4ad4ec39</link>
				<description>Get some free Bitcoin bits here at this faucet that pays hourly. Lets break free!!!
&lt;a href=&quot;http://freebitco.in/?r=4260&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://freebitco.in/?r=4260&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d42538eab8ea5720bd2f21</guid>
				<title>Sergio Garcia</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 12:41:12 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d42538eab8ea5720bd2f21</link>
				<description>We don't need to be an expert on media manipulation to remark that mixing an advice with a photo of the most hated dicatator of the occidental world is a clear try to manipulate the opinion.

Regarding the &quot;ponzi scheme&quot; theory, it was told that when China would make oposition to the Bitcoin the market will collapse, but we see that it went down to get up again and there are many big businness that start to accept bitcoins (overstock.com is one of the lastest on that category).

&lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoincharts.com/charts/mtgoxUSD&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://bitcoincharts.com/charts/mtgoxUSD&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3fe3869bedd286fbd2f21</guid>
				<title>Kim Jong Un</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 09:54:48 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3fe3869bedd286fbd2f21</link>
				<description>Mr. Joe Weisenthal is a bigoted pseudo analyst who would have never thought of writing an article about the unequal distribution of wealth of the US dollar. 
Comparing bitcoin to North Korea is a pathetic attempt to undermine the real value of this new fascinating technology.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3f891ecad04476fbd2f1d</guid>
				<title>mark dunam</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 09:30:41 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3f891ecad04476fbd2f1d</link>
				<description>Yeah cool and all but I forget, Is the u.s. dollar equally distributed or does the top 1% have over 35% of the u.s. Dollar, and does the bottom 80% only have about 11 %?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3c7286bb3f734069d8927</guid>
				<title>Angry Taxpayer</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 05:59:52 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3c7286bb3f734069d8927</link>
				<description>This is true. BitCoin is on a trend to become more equally distributed while fiat currencies are engineered to do the reverse.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3bc1b6bb3f7dd6c9d8917</guid>
				<title>3nrg</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 05:12:43 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3bc1b6bb3f7dd6c9d8917</link>
				<description>Great point. Yes, some large wallet holders are probably exchanges. However, it is possible to view the activity of all wallets. And as this article has correctly stated, the majority of the big wallets have been in place since early on with little or no activity. It has been shown through blockchain research that exchanges do not count for much with regards to the distribution statistics stated. In more general terms about 50 people own 1/3 of all bitcoins and 1000 people own 1/2. More informed users in the bitcoin community have known about this situation for years and the potential adverse implications of such a top-heavy distribution has been written upon quite extensively. Far beyond the scope of this article. 

For those wanting more edification on the matter bitcointalk.org covers much on this topic. Plus it's a great place to meet more intelligent and open-minded users of the bitcoin community rather then those who simply cry over every article which touches upon the problems bitcoin faces for further mainstream adoption.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3abbf6da8113723c79b4a</guid>
				<title>baMacdonald</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 04:02:55 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d3abbf6da8113723c79b4a</link>
				<description>Alright I am going to keep this short. This article is, in the least, a misinformed embarrassment to the quality of articles normally produced by Business Insider. Bitcoin's distribution of wealth is nothing like that of N. Korea. It is completely decentralized, voluntary, and legitimately valuable. Yes, very few hold the vast majority. Guess what? That is because they were the first believes, the first risk takers, and the the Genesis Generation of Crypto-Currency. This is not problematic for the currency. It isn't problematic for any currency-- It's a natural development of the first stages of any product distribution. It goes from the few and out to the many. BTC is hardly halfway through its currently slated life cycle. There are a lot more legitimate complaints to be made about the insecurity of the system in the long run that has nothing to do with archaic monetary theory. There are major systemic issues that will be a burden decades from now. Other complaints are just red herrings.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d358af69beddd246b54554</guid>
				<title>Time to get your hands dirty Joe</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 22:08:31 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d358af69beddd246b54554</link>
				<description>People who speak in simile can shampoo my crotch.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d336ee6da81178451b7e82</guid>
				<title>André Kenji De Sousa</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 19:44:30 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d336ee6da81178451b7e82</link>
				<description>North Korea is a murderous tyranny, not a Ponzi Scheme.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d31c5deab8eab144b54559</guid>
				<title>Zurich</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 17:51:09 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d31c5deab8eab144b54559</link>
				<description>Basically owning a lot of bitcoins is the prize they get from betting large sums of money on such a risky thing that bitcoin were at the time they invested.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d310b9eab8eaf229b54576</guid>
				<title>Mark Matthews</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 17:01:29 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d310b9eab8eaf229b54576</link>
				<description>Correct. Wealth disparity is inevitable, its only bad when its done parasitically. North Korea is as far away from a free market is one could possibly get. Bitcoin, on the other hand, is the only true free market in the world. Indeed, it makes every stock on Wall Street look like North Korea, or as you correctly point out.

Wealth disparity in the debt/fiat world is because large capital pools (privately owned banks) have stolen that wealth without work or risk through government regulation and by the slow siphoning destructive forces of inflating currency. They are powerful without productive contribution. Conversely, the wealth disparity in Bitcoin is due to early investors providing liquidity when no one believed in its value. Its through cryptographers and developers who worked their butts off and explained, increased, or utilized the value potential they understood.

It's the decentralization of power that is important. The 0.01% use the coercive power of government to grant competitive advantage over others through regulation, subsidies/government contracts, and tax loopholes. Bitcoin distributes this power whereby individuals are on a more level playing field. How easy is it now for your average person to transfer money around the globe without the need of gatekeepers? Decentralization is key. This will inevitably need to a significant reduction in the false authority of quasi-government institutions like banks which only leech of society. In the coming decade this will mean a significant reduction of the income gap between the real &quot;North Korea&quot; and the rest of us.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2fb0eeab8eadc7cb54556</guid>
				<title>Rich Beer</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 15:29:02 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2fb0eeab8eadc7cb54556</link>
				<description>Comparing bitcoin to North Korea. Consider the source. Too funny! If one is going to smear a currency not controlled by the Fed at least try to hide the fact that you work for the benefit of the World Bank and Federal Reserve. You have no credibility with honest people.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2fa3269bedd6473b54554</guid>
				<title>lolek</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 15:25:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2fa3269bedd6473b54554</link>
				<description>Like reading trollbox....</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2e9f6ecad048d451b7e85</guid>
				<title>coreychambers</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 14:16:06 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2e9f6ecad048d451b7e85</link>
				<description>Wiesenthal and Business Insider are creeping to new lows with this salacious and fictitious financial pornography in disguise of a news article. Neither a journalist, nor a financial expert, Joe tries to pervertedly equate free markets with totalitarianism. If anyone dared to use Bitcoin in North Korea, they would certainly be executed. The dictator of North Korean did not obtain his power by investing in innovation, he inherited the power from his dictator father.

Just the opposite is true regarding the the brave, ingenious free-market visionaries who invested time and money into the the new experiment called Bitcoin. In a free market, the innovators who invest far more money, time, energy, education, resources and risk are the ones who receive the capital that is created when the risk pays off. The innovators typically do not squander it all, but re-invest most of it in new and improved innovations. That is one of the ingredients in building the greatest free market in the world, The United States of America.

Like other detractors of Bitcoin, Joe is clearly jealous because he did not have the vision to be a pioneer in something like Bitcoin, and he will thus not benefit as greatly. The good news for Joe is that he and the rest of the 99% will also benefit financially from cheaper and easier payment and monetary system.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2e8cbeab8eabf53b54560</guid>
				<title>Ivan Raszl</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 14:11:07 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2e8cbeab8eabf53b54560</link>
				<description>Look at the first day of overstock.com sales when they started accepting Bitcoin. The same thing happens with every single merchant who accepts bitcoins. Clearly people using it to purchase goods and services. Most people I know who own bitcoins spend them regularly.

Most people I know who have dollars keep most of their money in the bank. Would you characterize them as sitting on their dollars?

There is no fundamental difference between the two. You sit on most of your money and spend some as you need to.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2e6856bb3f74d483ac605</guid>
				<title>Ivan Raszl</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 14:01:25 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2e6856bb3f74d483ac605</link>
				<description>Did citigroup currency analyst Steven Englander consider that those giant wallets are owned by exchanges? These giant wallets can hold the investment of thousands of people. If he did he should do the same on the other side with $ too to be fair.

Also, bitcoin is just one of many crypto currencies. The majority holders of various cryptos are different people.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2dc4f6bb3f723303ac60d</guid>
				<title>Rsd</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 13:17:51 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2dc4f6bb3f723303ac60d</link>
				<description>Take a look on other countries like Argentina ( two digit inflation), poor countries. The same happens with gold, people sit on it since years because their value will be bigger. You can always make some money question is how to prevent loosing it value.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2d47869beddf01cb54556</guid>
				<title>Rsd</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 12:44:24 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2d47869beddf01cb54556</link>
				<description>bitcoin is not about equality in wealth sens. It is about equality rely on not loosing value in time, no inflation. If you are rich you can invest in goods, maket shares,gold to save your money if you are poor you dont have such possibility.
Early adopters took a risk simmilar to other people, entrepreneurs who succeed.
Luck Is What Happens When Preparation Meets Opportunity</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c4fb6bb3f72a033ac60c</guid>
				<title>Song</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 11:38:19 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c4fb6bb3f72a033ac60c</link>
				<description>Actually every stock in stockmarket, is like North Korea.
institute owners, company CEOs, chariman etc always have the most shares.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c4b36bb3f7c87f3ac607</guid>
				<title>Need more Jobs</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 11:37:07 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c4b36bb3f7c87f3ac607</link>
				<description>That's called free market capitalism. 

Some would say that is more equal than having banker socialism! Where the Banks get $75 Billion dollars for free every month!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c4686bb3f7ed7f3ac607</guid>
				<title>PragueBob</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 11:35:52 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c4686bb3f7ed7f3ac607</link>
				<description>The discussion about Gini coefficient is really nonsense. When bitcoin started and the genesis block was mined all of them were in ONE WALLET, so what do you think the Gini coefficient was at that point? Early miners jumped into the fray and mined at low difficulty so many of these gained a large number of bitcoins in a few wallets. It has simply taken this long for the distribution to be out into several million wallets which are now growing fatter, since bitcoin is now trading briskly on the exchanges and people are actually starting to use bitcoin to pay for goods and services, the Gini coefficient will continue to drop like a rock. But in any case it is just complete nonsense to discuss Gini coefficient in connection with bitcoin, each day more and more people are downloading wallets and beginning to use them. This is not like established populations in countries where fiat currencies have been in use since the beginning. Apples and oranges comparison!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c39c69bedd9371b54554</guid>
				<title>BitBillions</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 11:32:28 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c39c69bedd9371b54554</link>
				<description>Get some now before its too late! very little investment here. 

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitbillions.com/?refid=1LXxS1ht74BrnuwtiaBVgC9xrS25sVykzT&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.bitbillions.com/?refid=1LXxS1ht74BrnuwtiaBVgC9xrS25sVykzT&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c1cb6da811e2771b7e81</guid>
				<title>PoliticalPaul</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 11:24:43 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c1cb6da811e2771b7e81</link>
				<description>Because bitcoin tortures political prisoners, starves bitcoin citizenry, executes or imprisons anyone who dissents agains bitcoin and bitcoin keeps dodgecoin in poverty. From space, bitcoin is dark at night surrounded by all the other bright currencies. Oh, and bitcoin also loves the psychotic Dennis Rodman...

Like all neo socialist nut jobs, Joe thinks as a child, reasons as a child and has not put aside childish ways...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c0556da811f2741b7e89</guid>
				<title>bitcoininfo</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 11:18:29 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2c0556da811f2741b7e89</link>
				<description>It's true that only a few people technically own a lot of Bitcoins, but I'm pretty sure that many of the largest owners are Bitcoin exchanges and other payment services.</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

