http://www.businessinsider.com/overstockcom-is-now-officially-accepting-bitcoin-2014-1/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Fri, 11 Jul 2014 13:11:29 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: web3 (via varnish2)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 20989
X-Varnish: 1639142942
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 54.226.159.128
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>Someone Already Bought A $2,700 13-Piece Patio Set On Overstock.com Using Bitcoin</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/overstockcom-is-now-officially-accepting-bitcoin-2014-1/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 09:11:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Rob Wile</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2b7776bb3f7d7693ac60f</guid>
				<title>BetChain</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 10:40:39 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2b7776bb3f7d7693ac60f</link>
				<description>This shows that Bitcoins can actually be used to buy realistic things. 
Kudos to Overstock for taking the leap.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d0d9e96bb3f73648b13927</guid>
				<title>Bitcoin Exchange</title>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:43:05 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d0d9e96bb3f73648b13927</link>
				<description>Great article. At the moment, retailers tend to accept Bitcoin for the marketing benefit, but if successful, others will learn from the experience and begin to see Bitcoin as a legitimate medium of exchange. It will be very interesting to see what the future holds. We comment on this and similar issues on our blog. 

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitmorecoin.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.bitmorecoin.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d01d4669beddfa416aed55</guid>
				<title>Rev</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 11:18:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d01d4669beddfa416aed55</link>
				<description>Lol are you serious? If so: &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoinwisdom.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://bitcoinwisdom.com/&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d01c4269beddf0416aed51</guid>
				<title>Rev</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 11:13:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d01c4269beddf0416aed51</link>
				<description>A consistant drip of bitcoins being sold contributes to increased stability by reducing the price from overshooting. You're talking from a greedy perspective, wanting the boom and busts to go crazy. In reality what helps bitcoin in the longterm is the consistant decrease in volatility. The boom and busts help with this too in the long run, but seeing the boom and busts in themselves as what is supporting bitcoin is wrong.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cff0336da8111a600b6443</guid>
				<title>Chinthamani</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 08:05:55 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cff0336da8111a600b6443</link>
				<description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://freebitco.in/?r=191757&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://freebitco.in/?r=191757&lt;/a&gt; 

Let me guess, that r=191757 on the end is your referrer id, and if I follow they link and fill out a form, you'll get paid?

Nice try, spammer.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cfe00969beddc7396aed53</guid>
				<title>Frederik</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 06:56:57 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cfe00969beddc7396aed53</link>
				<description>Yes that's exactly how it is. One moment price is $4000, next thing you know it's $500.. So volatile man</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cfd4c1eab8eadc4bf52b56</guid>
				<title>Jostein</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 06:08:49 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cfd4c1eab8eadc4bf52b56</link>
				<description>The ones who own bitcoin now will obviously just buy back the coins they used on an exchange. We understand that it's important to both support the price and start using them so more adaption takes place. Thats also the beauty of a deflationary currency.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cfafb96da81102235f73c3</guid>
				<title>reverendcaptain</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 03:30:49 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cfafb96da81102235f73c3</link>
				<description>&quot;Obliviously&quot; Hahahahahahahahahaha!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf84366bb3f77631f3c8d2</guid>
				<title>bitcorati</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 00:25:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf84366bb3f77631f3c8d2</link>
				<description>Great news! As we anticipated 2014 will be the year many medium and large size business begin accepting bitcoin. Overstock.com has officially been added to the Bitcorati.com Bitcoin Directory as of today!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf62dbecad04e96bf3c8d7</guid>
				<title>Rassah</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 22:02:51 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf62dbecad04e96bf3c8d7</link>
				<description>Zoom out of the bitcoin price cart, and you;ll see that bitcoin has gone through at least 4 of these hype cycles already. Sure, we may be in another &quot;Trough of Disillusionment&quot; phase, but once it stabilizes for a few months, it'll be another HUGE runup as more people get in on adoption (I'm guessing $10,000 by end of 2014, and I have been wrong, guessing WAY lower than actual, every time so far)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf5b4eeab8eaa54db51fc0</guid>
				<title>nikolay</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 21:30:38 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf5b4eeab8eaa54db51fc0</link>
				<description>You're supporting Overstock and Coinbase, not Bitcoin. Everything you buy there results in the sale of bitcoins dragging the price down. You're not doing yourself a favor unless you spent you last bitcoins.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf5af06da81117395f73c2</guid>
				<title>nikolay</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 21:29:04 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf5af06da81117395f73c2</link>
				<description>Not really. If you believe in it, why part with your bitcoins?! Spend using your credit cards - it's cheaper if you believe in the growth! Don't even bother to pay your credit card balance - APR is nothing compared to the growth you're expecting!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf40ce6da811b4705f73a5</guid>
				<title>Jesse</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 19:37:34 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf40ce6da811b4705f73a5</link>
				<description>This is the time to get into 
bitcoins!!

 The price will be even higher soon and you will kick 
yourself for not getting started! (last year price was around 13$)

1)First you need to create a digital wallet @ &lt;a href=&quot;https://blockchain.info/wallet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://blockchain.info/wallet&lt;/a&gt;...

This is where your coins are &quot;stored&quot;. This will also generate a 
random &quot;address&quot; for you to receive your coins from other 
parties/merchants. 

2) second, we need to fill you to fill up your wallet with bitcoins!!

 How do you get bitcoins? You can buy them at exchanges like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mtgox.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://www.mtgox.com/&lt;/a&gt; or you can try win them for free!

This site, &lt;a href=&quot;http://freebitco.in/?r=191757&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://freebitco.in/?r=191757&lt;/a&gt; will give you free coins every hour, up to .2 BTC (which is about 200$!!!)

Don't wait to start earning free money!! :D</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf3238ecad04f310f3c8ce</guid>
				<title>ErikVoorhees</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 18:35:20 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf3238ecad04f310f3c8ce</link>
				<description>But Krugman said that nobody will buy stuff cause deflation!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf301c6da811883d5f73b3</guid>
				<title>SilentP</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 18:26:20 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf301c6da811883d5f73b3</link>
				<description>Actually it does. There was a lot of interest in MP3 before the iPod, but it didn't take off until the iPod even though there were early MP3 players available. The point is that when technology is limited only by the imagination and looks to be taking over the world is the Peak of Inflated Expectations (radio is dead!). Then real world limitations start to kick in and expectations are reset while innovators continue to work on it, leading (hopefully ) to a productive place for the tech to operate meaningfully in the real world.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf23ff6da8113c1c5f73a5</guid>
				<title>FreeJack2k2</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 17:34:39 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf23ff6da8113c1c5f73a5</link>
				<description>Sort of like how there wasn't that much interest in MP3 before the iPod was released...but I guess that doesn't really support your argument, does it?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf23ef6da8115e1b5f73b9</guid>
				<title>Tony Jah</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 17:34:23 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf23ef6da8115e1b5f73b9</link>
				<description>This is so awesome! Now I'm going to purchase as much as I can on overstock using bitcoin!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf2359eab8ea995ab51fc2</guid>
				<title>FreeJack2k2</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 17:31:53 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf2359eab8ea995ab51fc2</link>
				<description>Actually, considering that I paid an average of $300 or so each for my Bitcoin, almost anything I buy today I'm technically getting for free, until I am down to my initial investment.

That's the beauty of a deflationary currency.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf22f66da811611b5f73a5</guid>
				<title>FreeJack2k2</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 17:30:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf22f66da811611b5f73a5</link>
				<description>So much for the naysayers' insistence that nobody wants to use Bitcoin/Litecoin to buy anything.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf21ca69beddfd0af3c8ce</guid>
				<title>PdV</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 17:25:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf21ca69beddfd0af3c8ce</link>
				<description>You can get some more free Bitcoins over here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://freebitco.in/?r=103979&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://freebitco.in/?r=103979&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf1b5069bedd9479f3c8d0</guid>
				<title>anjansons</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:57:36 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf1b5069bedd9479f3c8d0</link>
				<description>Bitcoin is not as volatile, for a price to change so in a matter of seconds. Come on!! You can do better that spout out this ignorant shit!

As I said, if merchants team up with Coinbase or Bitpay it's very cheap and great for them to accept Bitcoin due to lower fees, no credit cards scam and chargebacks. Chargebacks can be implemented in another way, not as harmful to merchants as just some kind of African scammer making his bank cancel the payment after the item has been already received. 

It all of course rests on consumer adoption, I mean widespread adoption- but this could come with better user interfaces, less volatility and other interesting features provided on top of the Bitcoin protocol</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf19ee69bedddd76f3c8ce</guid>
				<title>anjansons</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:51:42 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf19ee69bedddd76f3c8ce</link>
				<description>Could happen but I tell you that- for merchants it's super easy and super cheap to accept Bitcoin - that's why they are doing it (for publicity). They don't need to hold the coins, they only use it as a payments platform and accept money in fiat from Bitpay, Coinbase etc.

Now... the question is whether customers will pay with Bitcoin and, well, there are a lot of miners out there for whom paying with bitcoin would be an obvious choice (as they pay for their mining gear), early adopters that would like to unload their cash etc. It is still not as easy for regular guys to buy Bitcoin, due to bad exchange rates and bank transfer fees, but this will improve with more developers and people interested in delivering a better service.

Of course if price is always going up there might not be so much buyers, but it has been observed that people are more likely to buy something with their coins during the big peaks (because they have risen in value and well, you want the new iPhone and you can afford to spend some, cause in USD you still are a big winner), but also now that price does not fluctuate super dramatically perhaps some people might decide it will not go up for a while and buy stuff with Bitcoin and purchase additional Bitcoins later, when price starts to go up, to again hoard a bit.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf1913eab8ea8744b51fc6</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:48:03 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf1913eab8ea8744b51fc6</link>
				<description>Looking to replace my beat up car. Can I buy a used car on Overstock with BTC?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf18e1ecad04d95df3c8dd</guid>
				<title>nahandro</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:47:13 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf18e1ecad04d95df3c8dd</link>
				<description>Very wise of you to use random comments by unknown parties in your investment decisions. Sounds like a brilliant strategy. Please do chime back here in a year or so and let us know how badly you got wiped out.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf18d1eab8eaaf46b51fc2</guid>
				<title>SilentP</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:46:57 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf18d1eab8eaaf46b51fc2</link>
				<description>Ah, not so fast. I have been a proponent of the technology since 2011 and think it is here to stay. I have also been working in tech since the 90's and have been though many of these Hype Cycles and there is no reason to think that Bitcoin is immune. The Peak of Inflated Expectations occurs when there is nothing but blue sky ahead, when reality of adoption sets in expectations must be reset. Mine is not an indictment of the technology or placing any limitation on what its real long term potential holds, but noting that it is likely to follow a pattern repeatedly observed when promising new tech is introduced.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf1896ecad044460f3c8d0</guid>
				<title>nahandro</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:45:58 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf1896ecad044460f3c8d0</link>
				<description>You mean, they spent between $3,500 and $2,000 depending on the millisecond they placed the ordered and the value of BTC at this particular moment. Could be that they only spent $1,000 tomorrow or may have spent as much as $5,000 for that same $2,700 set.... That's the beauty of it. Its like rolling the dice or playing the lotto every time you make a purchase...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf182d69bedded73f3c8ce</guid>
				<title>I'm buying</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:44:13 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf182d69bedded73f3c8ce</link>
				<description>Bitcoiners support overstock. 

I am looking for stuff to buy.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf0f8769bedd6a61f3c8d1</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:07:19 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf0f8769bedd6a61f3c8d1</link>
				<description>Nice to hear that there still a lot of nay-sayers. Looks like we are a very long way off from the peak!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf08ec6da811804e5f73ad</guid>
				<title>SilentP</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 15:39:08 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf08ec6da811804e5f73ad</link>
				<description>And this, along with Zynga's experiments, will mark the beginning of Bitcoin's entrance into the &quot;Trough of Disillusionment&quot; phase of the Technology Hype Cycle - &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hype_cycle&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hype_cycle&lt;/a&gt; . These experiments will reveal that there is actually little interest from the general public to adopt BTC as an online currency and that the current expectations for BTC's adoption are wildly inflated.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf05e2ecad04d337f3c8dc</guid>
				<title>JackMeOff</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 15:26:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf05e2ecad04d337f3c8dc</link>
				<description>Marketing gimmick to boost their website traffic. Its obliviously working!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf02646bb3f72e3bc1ec9d</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 15:11:16 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cf02646bb3f72e3bc1ec9d</link>
				<description>Dude... aren't you going to credit me of informing you of this event????!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cefe90eab8ea300dd0243c</guid>
				<title>BitBillions</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 14:54:56 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52cefe90eab8ea300dd0243c</link>
				<description>This is great news. I think i'm going to go there and pick something up. What? i don't know! 

I will support them though!

Want Bitcoins? Can get some for free here. 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitbillions.com/?refid=1LXxS1ht74BrnuwtiaBVgC9xrS25sVykzT&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.bitbillions.com/?refid=1LXxS1ht74BrnuwtiaBVgC9xrS25sVykzT&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

