http://www.businessinsider.com/category/tax-return.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Tue, 22 Jul 2014 19:45:52 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: web1 (via varnish2)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 115207
X-Varnish: 1874427218
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 50.17.88.74
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

    <channel>
        <title>Tax Return</title>
        <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/category/tax-return</link>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 15:45:52 -0400</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 15:45:52 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <description>The latest news on Tax Return from Business Insider</description>
        <image>
            <url>http://static3.businessinsider.com/assets/images/bilogo-250x36-wide-rev.png</url>
            <title>Business Insider</title>
            <link>http://www.businessinsider.com</link>
        </image>
                                    <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/turbotax-maker-linked-to-grassroots-campaign-against-free-simple-tax-filing-2014-4</guid>
                    <title>TurboTax Maker Linked to Grassroots' Campaign Against Free, Simple Tax Filing</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/turbotax-maker-linked-to-grassroots-campaign-against-free-simple-tax-filing-2014-4</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 14:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Liz Day</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static5.businessinsider.com/image/52e6b5baecad04513401afa1-1200-924/3372646.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;girl taxes documents paper&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last year, a rabbi, a state NAACP official, a small town mayor and other community leaders wrote op-eds and letters to Congress with remarkably similar language on a remarkably obscure topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each railed against a long-standing proposal that would give taxpayers the option to use pre-filled tax returns. They warned that the program would be a conflict of interest for the IRS and would especially hurt low-income people, who wouldn't have the resources to fight inaccurate returns. Rabbi Elliot Dorff wrote in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jewishjournal.com/opinion/item/irs_return_free_bad_for_most_vulnerable&quot;&gt;Jewish Journal&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jewishjournal.com/opinion/item/irs_return_free_bad_for_most_vulnerable&quot;&gt;op-ed&lt;/a&gt; that he &quot;shudder[s] at the impact this program will have on the most vulnerable people in American society.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;It's alarming and offensive&quot; that the IRS would target the &quot;the most vulnerable Americans,&quot; two other letters said. The concept, known as return-free filing, is a government &quot;experiment&quot; that would mean higher taxes for the poor, two op-eds argued.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The letters and op-eds don't mention that, as &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propublica.org/article/how-the-maker-of-turbotax-fought-free-simple-tax-filing&quot;&gt;ProPublica laid out last year&lt;/a&gt;, return-free filing might allow tens of millions of Americans to file their taxes for free and in minutes. Or that, under proposals authored by several federal lawmakers, it would be voluntary, using information the government already receives from banks and employers and that taxpayers could adjust. Or that the concept has been endorsed by Presidents Obama and Reagan and is already a reality in some parts of Europe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, where did the letters and op-eds come from? Here's one clue:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rabbi Dorff says he was approached by a former student, Emily Pflaster, who sent him details and asked him to write an op-ed alerting the Jewish community to the threat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What Pflaster did not tell him is that she works for a PR and lobbying firm with connections to Intuit, the maker of best-selling tax software TurboTax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;I wish she would have told me that,&quot; Dorff told ProPublica.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website of Pflaster's firm, JCI Worldwide, had &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propublica.org/documents/item/1109201-jci-pr-what-we-do-intuit.html#document/p1/a153391&quot;&gt;listed Intuit among its clients&lt;/a&gt;, but removed it after ProPublica contacted them. Pflaster said Intuit had been listed by mistake, but added that the firm does work for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ccianet.org/&quot;&gt;Computer &amp;amp; Communications Industry Association &lt;/a&gt;(CCIA), a trade group of which Intuit is a member. Pflaster also said her firm has reached out to multiple groups and encouraged them to share information about the &quot;flaws&quot; of return-free filing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ccianet.org/about/members/&quot;&gt;only CCIA member&lt;/a&gt; that's involved with tax preparation software is Intuit, and it's also the only member of the group that has taken a public position on return-free tax filing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intuit has &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propublica.org/article/how-the-maker-of-turbotax-fought-free-simple-tax-filing&quot;&gt;long worked against return-free filing&lt;/a&gt;. The company has said in &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propublica.org/documents/item/621233-intuit-10k#document/p18/a95901&quot;&gt;filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission&lt;/a&gt; that it views free government tax preparation as a risk to its business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, the company spent more than $2.6 million on lobbying, some of it to lobby on four bills related to the issue, federal lobbying records show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both Intuit and CCIA declined to answer questions about their connections to the letters and op-eds. An Intuit spokeswoman, Julie Miller, said in an emailed statement that Intuit works with many types of groups to support &quot;taxpayer empowerment,&quot; and &quot;we feel all points of view deserve to be heard.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Return Free minimizes the taxpayers' voice and instead maximizes revenue collection for government,&quot; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propublica.org/documents/item/1105522-intuit-statement-2014-return-free-opeds.html&quot;&gt;Miller wrote&lt;/a&gt;. &quot;That kind of anti-consumer policy does not advance taxpayer rights.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CCIA President Ed Black &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propublica.org/documents/item/1105521-propublica-2014-statement-of-ed-black.html&quot;&gt;said in a statement&lt;/a&gt;, &quot;We think it's important to help policymakers and the public understand what many already know: ReturnFree is unfair, unworkable and unwise.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The letters and op-eds 2014 there have been at least eight of them 2014 also appear on a new website, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fairtaxrefunds.com&quot;&gt;www.FairTaxRefunds.com&lt;/a&gt;, which Pflaster said her company created for CCIA. It resembles a similar previous site, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.stopirstakeover.org&quot;&gt;www.StopIRSTakeover.org&lt;/a&gt;, which was also sponsored by the CCIA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://projects.propublica.org/graphics/tax-letters&quot;&gt;Op-Eds and Letters Opposing Return-Free Tax Filing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another instance in which CCIA solicited a letter wasn't successful. Angela Martin, director of an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.economicfairnessoregon.org/&quot;&gt;Oregon nonprofit&lt;/a&gt;, said a PR professional gave her &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propublica.org/documents/item/1105600-efo-tax-letter.html&quot;&gt;a sample anti-return-free filing letter&lt;/a&gt; last year for her organization to send to Sen. Ron Wyden, D-Ore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Martin knew the caller, Colin Cochran, who works for the firm Hilltop Public Solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cochran used &quot;a lot of words that advocates would be sympathetic to, like 'oh, it'll hurt people with English as a second language,'&quot; Martin said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Martin was skeptical. So she asked Cochran who he was representing. He said he was working for the CCIA and, when asked, said yes, that Intuit is a member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cochran confirmed the details of his discussion with Martin, including that he was working for the CCIA. His firm boasts on its website of a &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hilltoppublicsolutions.com/grasstopscampaigns/grasstops.htm&quot;&gt;winning grasstops approach&lt;/a&gt;&quot; 2014 &quot;grasstops&quot; is industry lingo for recruiting the support of community leaders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two other letter-writers told ProPublica they were approached by lobbyists, though it's not clear who the lobbyists were representing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One letter-writer, Richard Smith, the president of the NAACP Delaware State Conference, was approached by a longtime acquaintance with information about how return-free filing would take dollars out of poor people's pockets. Smith felt so strongly &lt;a href=&quot;http://fairtaxrefunds.com/2014/02/03/naacp-delaware-state-conference/&quot;&gt;he fired off a letter&lt;/a&gt; to Sen. Tom Carper, D-Del., and encouraged other local NAACP leaders to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smith said the acquaintance, Anne Farley, told him that if return-free filing was adopted, the government would stop offering free tax filing help to low-income communities. (In fact, none of the bills on return-free filing propose that.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When ProPublica told Smith that Farley is also a &lt;a href=&quot;https://egov.delaware.gov/lobs/Explore/LobbyistDetails/1394&quot;&gt;registered lobbyist&lt;/a&gt;, he said he was now questioning the information she gave him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;We may have to retract so far based on my research,&quot; Smith said. &quot;I didn't question her.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lobbying records for Farley's firm, First State Strategies, do not list Intuit or the CCIA among its clients. The firm's website does advertise &quot;grass tops advocacy campaigns.&quot; Farley and First State Strategies did not respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dennis Huang, executive director of the L.A.-based Asian Business Association, also told ProPublica he was solicited by a lobbyist to write about return-free filing. When the lobbyist sent him a suggested op-ed last summer and told him the proposal would hurt small businesses, Huang wrote &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.propublica.org/documents/item/1106550-asian-journal-op-ed.html&quot;&gt;an op-ed in the Asian Journal&lt;/a&gt; that claimed Asian-owned businesses would not only spend more time paying taxes, but they'd also get less of a refund each year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huang declined to disclose the lobbyist's name, but acknowledged he didn't really do his own research. &quot;There's some homework needed,&quot; he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oregon's Martin did some research on return-free filing and now supports it. She also &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.blueoregon.com/2014/04/return-free-filing-good-oregonians/&quot;&gt;co-published a post&lt;/a&gt; about the issue and the PR efforts related to it because, she says, she was alarmed that other nonprofits could easily agree to endorse a position they did not fully understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;You get one or two prominent nonprofits to use their name, and busy advocates will extend trust and say sure, us too,&quot; Martin said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;http://pixel.propublica.org/pixel.js&quot; async=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/turbotax-maker-linked-to-grassroots-campaign-against-free-simple-tax-filing-2014-4#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/52e6b5baecad04513401afa1/turbotax-maker-linked-to-grassroots-campaign-against-free-simple-tax-filing.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-tax-rate-joe-scarborough-class-warfare-2013-4</guid>
                    <title>Joe Scarborough Goes On Huge Rant Over Obama's Tax Rate: 'The Hypocrisy Is Mind-Boggling'</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-tax-rate-joe-scarborough-class-warfare-2013-4</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 10:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Brett LoGiurato</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/516c06db69bedd4709000005-400-/joe-scarborough-obama-tax-rate.png&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Joe Scarborough Obama tax rate&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;hidden_link&quot; href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/msnbc&quot;&gt;MSNBC&lt;/a&gt; host &lt;a class=&quot;hidden_link&quot; href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/joe-scarborough&quot;&gt;Joe Scarborough&lt;/a&gt; ripped into President Barack Obama on Monday &amp;mdash; Tax Day &amp;mdash; after learning that Obama &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reuters.com/article/2013/04/13/us-obama-taxes-idUSBRE93B0Y420130413&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;paid only an 18.4 percent effective federal tax rate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scarborough noted the conflict between Obama's statements on the campaign trail last year &amp;mdash; when he routinely blasted Republican &lt;a class=&quot;hidden_link&quot; href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/mitt-romney&quot;&gt;Mitt Romney&lt;/a&gt; for his low tax rate &amp;mdash; and Obama's effective rate last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;He's paying a tax rate far lower than what a teacher pays. I'm speaking slowly so this sinks in. The hypocrisy is mind-boggling,&quot; Scarborough said. &quot;This president does class warfare for a year and a half on the campaign trail. He attacks Mitt Romney repeatedly. ... And yet this president, after demagoguing this issue for a year and a half, pays an 18 percent tax rate.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other MSNBC panelists pointed out that much of the reason Obama paid such a low rate was because of his charitable contributions. But Scarborough pushed back on that, noting that Romney also had sizeable contributions to charity. He accused Obama of &quot;lecturing&quot; hypocritically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Barack Obama has been championing raising taxes on small-business owners for years,&quot; Scarborough said, his voice getting louder. &quot;And he's paying 18 percent, because raising those taxes don't affect him. And he talks about fairness? This guy &amp;mdash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;this guy&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; talks about fairness? ... Barack Obama, class warrior, is paying 18 percent in taxes.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watch the clip below, courtesy of MSNBC:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;object id=&quot;msnbc984c28&quot; classid=&quot;clsid:D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000&quot; codebase=&quot;http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=10,0,0,0&quot; width=&quot;420&quot; height=&quot;245&quot;&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;movie&quot; value=&quot;http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/32545640&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;FlashVars&quot; value=&quot;launch=51541399&amp;amp;width=420&amp;amp;height=245&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowScriptAccess&quot; value=&quot;always&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowFullScreen&quot; value=&quot;true&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;wmode&quot; value=&quot;transparent&quot; /&gt;&lt;embed name=&quot;msnbc984c28&quot; src=&quot;http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/32545640&quot; width=&quot;420&quot; height=&quot;245&quot; flashvars=&quot;launch=51541399&amp;amp;width=420&amp;amp;height=245&quot; allowscriptaccess=&quot;always&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; wmode=&quot;transparent&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; pluginspage=&quot;http://www.adobe.com/shockwave/download/download.cgi?P1_Prod_Version=ShockwaveFlash&quot; /&gt;&lt;/object&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;font-size: 11px; font-family: Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #999; margin-top: 5px; background: transparent; text-align: center; width: 420px;&quot;&gt;Visit NBCNews.com for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nbcnews.com&quot;&gt;breaking news&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/3032507&quot;&gt;world news&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/3032072&quot;&gt;news about the economy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-tax-rate-joe-scarborough-class-warfare-2013-4#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/516c06db69bedd4709000005/joe-scarborough-goes-on-huge-rant-over-obamas-tax-rate-the-hypocrisy-is-mind-boggling.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/tax-filing-mistakes-could-ruin-refunds-2013-3</guid>
                    <title>How To Screw Up Your Tax Refund In 7 Steps</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/tax-filing-mistakes-could-ruin-refunds-2013-3</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 19:04:22 -0500</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Mandi Woodruff and Daniel Goodman</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s almost too easy to screw up a tax return these days. And trust us, you don&amp;rsquo;t want to go there. Not only could mistakes lead to a slower or smaller refund, but you could be begging for a visit an IRS auditor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are seven easy ways to screw up your refund.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;http://player.ooyala.com/v3/6e12e8b3387a44daacfb73afba25a76e&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;ooyalaplayer&quot; style=&quot;width: 618px; height: 347px;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[
OO.ready(function() { OO.Player.create('ooyalaplayer', 'VmcnN4OTqYxaIVGE7H8aP370U30OZO0S'); });
// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;noscript&gt;&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;lt;div&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;gt;Please enable Javascript to watch this video&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;lt;/div&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Produced by Daniel Goodman&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEE ALSO:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/how-to-dispute-a-credit-report-error-2013-2&quot; &gt;Here's The Fool-Proof Way To Fix Errors On Your Credit Report &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEE ALSO:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/how-to-customize-your-tumblr-2013-3&quot; &gt;How To Make Your Tumblr Look Incredible&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/tax-filing-mistakes-could-ruin-refunds-2013-3#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/5130c9be6bb3f7040e00002d/how-to-screw-up-your-tax-refund-in-7-steps.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/tips-for-e-filing-taxes-2013-1</guid>
                    <title>Here's How To E-File Your Taxes Without Mucking Everything Up</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/tips-for-e-filing-taxes-2013-1</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 12:09:27 -0500</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Dan Caplinger</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 15px; line-height: 1.5em;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/4f6cf3c269bedd3a1f000024-400-300/stylecaster-party-bi-dng-img_4220.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;catch bar, stylecaster, march 2012, party, fun, bi, dng&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;If you want to get your tax refund as soon as possible, forget about paper.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best way to get your money moving in your direction pronto is to e-file your return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But if you don't do it right, electronic tax filing can cause some big problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not to worry:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DailyFinance is here to help you avoid those pitfalls. Here's how e-filing works, and how to get it done right.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Wait Just a Bit Longer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ordinarily, you'd already have been able to e-file your return by now. But because of the&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dailyfinance.com/2012/12/31/fiscal-cliff-deal-details/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; new tax laws in the fiscal cliff deal,&lt;/a&gt; which was passed the day after New Year's, the IRS had to update forms and make sure that its e-filing acceptance computer software would properly reflect the new legislation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a result, the IRS said that it wouldn't start accepting returns until Jan. 30.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The delay has been bad news for those who've come to rely on early e-filing to speed up their refunds. According to the IRS, nearly 100 million taxpayers chose to e-file their tax returns in 2011, and many of them did so in the hopes of reducing tax-return processing and turnaround time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The difference can be huge, with refunds available in as little as seven days in some cases through direct deposit into your bank account, compared to several weeks for paper returns in many cases.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;The Benefits of E-Filing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Apart from letting you get your refund faster, e-filing can help you avoid common mistakes on your tax returns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Error rates on paper returns are extremely high, and simple math errors are one of the major culprits. Tax software &amp;mdash; which many people who e-file use to prepare their returns &amp;mdash; tends to keep those calculations more accurate. But even if you want to do your taxes on your own, the fillable forms that you can find on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.irs.gov/Filing&quot;&gt;the IRS filing website&lt;/a&gt; automatically double-check basic calculations to make sure your numbers add up correctly.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Moreover, e-filing no longer has to be expensive. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.irs.gov/uac/Free-File:-Frequently-Asked-Questions&quot;&gt;Free File tax software&lt;/a&gt; is available to taxpayers with gross income of $57,000 or less, and it provides comprehensive assistance through a network of tax-preparation companies to help you make sure you get your returns done in an accurate and timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even those who earn more than that can use Free File fillable forms, although they won't provide you with any of the assistance and resources that full-blown tax software packages offer.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;E-Filing and Identity Theft&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; One downside of the rise in popularity of e-filing is that it has massively increased &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dailyfinance.com/2013/01/25/identity-theft-tax-refund-scammers/&quot;&gt;tax-related identity-theft&lt;/a&gt;. Between 2008 and 2011, the number of identity-theft cases involving taxes rose 20-fold to more than 1.1 million.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; If criminals are able to get your name and Social Security number, then they can forge other documents necessary to e-file a tax return and arrange to have your refund sent to them on a prepaid debit card, which can easily be converted into cash for a clean getaway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, bogus web sites offering free e-filing have proliferated, luring unsuspecting taxpayers into giving away sensitive personal information that fraudsters can use to do massive financial damage.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;To protect yourself, follow some simple tips:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Worried about whether your preparer is legit?&lt;/strong&gt; Let the IRS tell you who's on its approved list by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.irs.gov/uac/Authorized-IRS-e-file-Providers-for-Individuals&quot;&gt;entering your zip code here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to sign your return.&lt;/strong&gt; You won't actually provide a signature, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://sa2.www4.irs.gov/irfof-efp/start.do&quot;&gt;setting up a personal identification number&lt;/a&gt; is a smart move to protect your identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch for an acknowledgment notice from the IRS that it has received your return. &lt;/strong&gt;If you don't get an email back within 48 hours, you'll know to check into whether something may have gone wrong.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Be Smart About E-Filing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; More generally, there are some other things you should do to make the e-filing process go smoothly.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Make sure you have all your tax documents and records ready &lt;em&gt;before &lt;/em&gt;you sit down to e-file your return, as having everything ready will make the whole process a lot simpler. Also, it's usually a bad idea to try to e-file before you have all of your tax forms in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many financial companies don't send out forms for certain types of investment income until February, so you'll give an inaccurate statement of your income if you file Wednesday as soon as the e-filing doors are open.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; To get more information on e-filing and free options for submitting your electronic return, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.irs.gov/Filing&quot;&gt;the IRS website here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEE ALSO:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/10-of-americas-wackiest-tax-laws-2013-1&quot; &gt;10 of America's strangest federal tax laws &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/tips-for-e-filing-taxes-2013-1#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static1.businessinsider.com/image/4f6cf3c269bedd3a1f000024/heres-how-to-e-file-your-taxes-without-mucking-everything-up.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-stolen-tax-returns-case-2012-11</guid>
                    <title>A Suspect In The Romney Blackmail Investigation Was Identified Using This Cat Picture</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-stolen-tax-returns-case-2012-11</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 10:49:52 -0500</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Abby Rogers</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/509d233669beddf358000018-400-300/romney-tax-return-cats.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;romney tax return cats&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Tennessee man accused of stealing Mitt Romney's tax returns to blackmail him says two grainy pictures of cats led federal agents to him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back in September a group of hackers claimed &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/hackers-claim-to-have-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;it had stolen Mitt Romney's tax returns&lt;/a&gt; from PriceWaterhouseCoopers' offices in Franklin, Tenn. Someone then mailed a thumb drive to Romney's accounting office demanding $1 million in exchange for the documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And on Sept. 14, authorities &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wsmv.com/story/20006705/secret-service-investigate-franklin-man-in-romney-tax-return-theft&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;thought they found their guy&lt;/a&gt; when they showed up at Michael Brown's house at 6:14 a.m., WSMV reported Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;They said they're here to serve a search warrant for Romney's tax returns,&quot; Brown told the TV station. &quot;My first reaction was, 'You've got to be kidding me.'&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The feds said they suspected Brown after discovering two grainy, black-and-white pictures of cats that believe belong to Brown on the illicit thumb drive, according to Brown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;They didn&amp;rsquo;t want to show anything to me,&quot; Brown told &lt;a class=&quot;hidden_link&quot; href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/the-daily&quot;&gt;The Daily&lt;/a&gt;. &quot;They did it to my wife. They said, &amp;lsquo;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thedaily.com/article/2012/11/09/110912-news-romney-tax-raid/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;These are your cats&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;rsquo; When she objected, they were like, &amp;lsquo;Yes, they are.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agents even took pictures of Brown's cats to compare to the ones in the blackmail offer, according to Brown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Brown insists the cats in question aren't his and actually belong to a former client.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My daughter did recognize one of the cats. They belonged to a friend of my wife,&amp;rdquo; Brown told The Daily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn't the first time Brown has run into trouble with the feds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Secret Service raided his house in 2009 after someone stole encrypted customer information from a Farm Bureau website, according to WSMV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No charges were ever brought in that case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DON'T MISS: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/joke-about-killing-obama-on-instagram-2012-11&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Teen Billionaire Jokes About Killing Obama On Social Media &amp;gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-stolen-tax-returns-case-2012-11#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static3.businessinsider.com/image/509d233669beddf358000018/a-suspect-in-the-romney-blackmail-investigation-was-identified-using-this-cat-picture.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-tax-returns-libya-october-surprise-2012-10</guid>
                    <title>A New Mystery Website Says It Will Drop An 'October Surprise' That Will Change The Election</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-tax-returns-libya-october-surprise-2012-10</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 15:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Grace Wyler</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;A mysterious new microsite promising an &quot;October Surprise&quot; for the presidential race popped up online this week, and is promising to release damning documents related to one of the two candidates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far, we don't know much about the site, octsurprise.com, which went live Monday with a linked &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/twitter&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; feed &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/OctSurprise&quot;&gt;@OctSurprise&lt;/a&gt;. The site warns that &quot;one of your presidential candidates isn't being honest with you,&quot; and subsequent tweets say that the site will unveil six pages of &quot;irrefutable&quot; documents at 5:30 p.m. on Monday. &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/tPOO8.jpg&quot;&gt;Blurred images of the documents&lt;/a&gt;, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/OctSurprise/status/258671389098254336&quot;&gt;all &lt;span&gt;allegedly&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;relate to the same topic&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;have also been posted online.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here's what the site looks like:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/5080503decad043175000010-500-388/october-surprise.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;october surprise&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, there is an outsized possibility that the &quot;October Surprise&quot; is just an elaborate troll. &lt;a href=&quot;http://politicker.com/2012/10/meet-two-of-the-developers-behind-the-internet-october-surprise/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The New York Observer&lt;/em&gt; reports&lt;/a&gt; that the site is run by two developers who work for the Discovery Channel, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.buzzfeed.com/rosiegray/october-surprise-run-by-same-guys-who-did-great&quot;&gt;BuzzFeed reports&lt;/a&gt; that the two developers were behind an Internet prank known as &quot;The Greatest Rick Roll Ever.&quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-tax-returns-libya-october-surprise-2012-10#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/508056dd69bedd9f57000000/a-new-mystery-website-says-it-will-drop-an-october-surprise-that-will-change-the-election.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-tax-returns-rate-plan-poll-2012-10</guid>
                    <title>One Of The Obama Campaign's Major Talking Points Has Turned Into A Flop</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-tax-returns-rate-plan-poll-2012-10</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 12:54:13 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Brett LoGiurato</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/5069c10769bedd7543000018-400-300/obama.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Obama&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the Obama campaign's major talking points throughout the summer months &amp;mdash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Mitt Romney's tax returns&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;mdash; have disappeared as an issue that voters care about, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.langerresearch.com/uploads/1141a1IntotheDebates.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;according to a new&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;/ABC poll&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The poll finds that since February, there has been a huge swing in the proportion of voters that believe Romney has paid his fair share in taxes, which &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-2012-9&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;comes just more than a week after the ho-hum release of his 2011 returns&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, 46 percent of voters now believe that Romney is &quot;paying his fair share in taxes,&quot; compared with 48 percent that thinks he is not. That's a wild,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;34-point swing from February,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;when only 30 percent thought he was paying his fair share and 66 percent thought he was not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a look at the disparity:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static1.businessinsider.com/image/5069c30d69bedd5b4e000001-362-218/mitt-romney-taxes.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Mitt Romney taxes&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The result is notable because the Romney campaign appears to have quietly blunted any effect the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-tax-returns-prove-release-offshore-accounts-2012-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Obama campaign's repeated attacks had on Romney&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new poll also shows that most voters view Romney's wealth as a positive rather than a negative, reversing the trend shown in a February poll. According to the latest survey, more people (51 to 42 percent) view Romney's wealth as a sign that he has &quot;achieved the American dream,&quot; rather than viewing it as a sign he &quot;benefited from opportunities that are not available&amp;nbsp;to most people.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going forward, it's likely that Obama will continue to tie Romney's wealth and his tax returns to his recent comments about the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-47-percent-obama-victims-dependent-2012-9&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&quot;47 percent&quot; of people that will vote for Obama&lt;/a&gt; because of government dependence, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-taxes-ad-47-percent-video-2012-9&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;strategy that his campaign used last week in a new television ad airing in Ohio&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-tax-returns-rate-plan-poll-2012-10#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static5.businessinsider.com/image/5069c10769bedd7543000018/one-of-the-obama-campaigns-major-talking-points-has-turned-into-a-flop.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-taxes-ad-47-percent-video-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>Obama's Ad Destroys Mitt Romney Over Tax Returns And The '47%' </title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-taxes-ad-47-percent-video-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 06:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Grace Wyler</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;Just one week after the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/live-full-romney-fundraiser-video-2012-9&quot;&gt;leaked video of &lt;strong&gt;Mitt Romney&lt;/strong&gt;'s campaign fundraiser&lt;/a&gt; surfaced, &lt;strong&gt;President Barack Obama's&lt;/strong&gt; presidential campaign is out with a new television ad &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/if-these-videos-are-real-they-look-horrible-for-mitt-romney-2012-9&quot;&gt;slamming the Republican presidential candidate for his now-infamous &quot;47 percent&quot; remarks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ad, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ojpl-JzPDkg&quot;&gt;titled &quot;No Taxes,&quot;&lt;/a&gt; opens with a clip from the video, as a narrator explains that Romney &quot;attacked&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;47% of Americans who pay no income tax &amp;mdash; including veterans, elderly, the disabled,&quot; before asking &quot;&lt;span&gt;Doesn&amp;rsquo;t the President have to worry about everyone?&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It then takes the attack one step further by tying Romney's comments to the candidate's personal tax returns, pointing out that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-2012-9&quot;&gt;the Romneys paid an effective rate of 14.1 percent on their tax returns in 2011,&lt;/a&gt; and that the Republican nominee still refuses to release additional tax returns.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Maybe instead of attacking others on taxes,&amp;nbsp;Romney should come clean on his,&quot; the ad concludes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 30-second spot will go on air today in Ohio, where Romney and Republican vice presidential candidate &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/paul-ryan&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Paul Ryan&lt;/a&gt; will campaign this week.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watch the whole thing below:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/Ojpl-JzPDkg&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-taxes-ad-47-percent-video-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/5060386f69beddf92d000015/obamas-ad-destroys-mitt-romney-over-tax-returns-and-the-47.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-tax-returns-low-rate-60-minutes-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>Mitt Romney Admits He Pays A 'Low Rate' On His Income Taxes, But Says It's Still Fair</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-tax-returns-low-rate-60-minutes-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 22:56:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Grace Wyler</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;embed src=&quot;http://cnettv.cnet.com/av/video/cbsnews/atlantis2/cbsnews_player_embed.swf&quot; scale=&quot;noscale&quot; salign=&quot;lt&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; background=&quot;#333333&quot; width=&quot;425&quot; height=&quot;279&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; allowscriptaccess=&quot;always&quot; flashvars=&quot;si=254&amp;amp;&amp;amp;contentValue=50131817&amp;amp;shareUrl=http://www.cbsnews.com/video/watch/?id=7422764n&amp;amp;tag=contentBody;storyMediaBox&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Appearing on &lt;em&gt;60 Minutes&lt;/em&gt; Sunday night after a rocky week on the campaign trail, &lt;strong&gt;Republican presidential candidate &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/mitt-romney&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Mitt Romney&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; defended paying a relatively low effective rate on his federal income taxes, arguing that it is fair for people to pay lower rates on capital gains.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Although the interview was filmed before the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-2012-9&quot;&gt;Romney campaign released the candidate's 2011 tax returns on Friday,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;the first questions focused on Romney's tax plans, and on his own individual income tax rate. Romney, who makes most of his income from capital gains,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-2012-9&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;paid an effective tax rate of just 14.1 percent last year.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;It&amp;nbsp;is a low rate,&quot; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cbsnews.com/video/watch/?id=7422764n&amp;amp;tag=contentBody;storyMediaBox&quot;&gt;Romney told CBS' News Scott Pelley&lt;/a&gt;. &quot;One of the reasons why the capital gains tax rate is lower is because capital has already been taxed once at the corporate level, as high as 35%.&quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Pressed on whether it is fair that he pays a lower effective rate than people who earn much less than he does, Romney replied affirmatively.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&quot;I think it's&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;the right way to encourage economic growth &amp;mdash; to get people to invest, to start businesses, to put people to work,&quot; he added.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Romney went on to reiterate that, under his tax plan, income tax rates would be cut by 20 percent across the board, and families earning less than $200,000 a year would no longer be taxed on interest, dividends, and capital gains. The loss in revenue, he said, would be offset by eliminations in loopholes and deductions in the tax code, especially for those making over $200,000. But he would not divulge what specific deductions would be eliminated.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&quot;T&lt;span&gt;hat's something Congress and I will have to work out together,&quot; he said, adding later: &quot;&lt;span&gt;The devil's in the details. The angel is in the policy, which is creating more jobs.&quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;DON'T MISS:&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-2012-9&quot;&gt; Romney Paid More Taxes Than He Had To Last Year, But He Can Get The Money Back Later&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-tax-returns-low-rate-60-minutes-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/505fcb7969beddc233000011/mitt-romney-admits-he-pays-a-low-rate-on-his-income-taxes-but-says-its-still-fair.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>Mitt Romney Paid Extra Taxes Last Year, But He Can Get The Money Back After The Election </title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 16:47:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Grace Wyler</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/505cd265ecad046b2f00001b/mitt-romney.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Mitt Romney&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mitt Romney's presidential campaign &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/disclosure&quot;&gt;released his 2011 tax returns&lt;/a&gt; Friday afternoon, revealing that the Republican presidential candidate deliberately paid more in federal income taxes last year.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brad Malt, the trustee of Romney's blind trust, explains in a campaign &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/blogs/mitts-view/2012/09/note-trustee-brad-malt&quot;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;that on their 2011 returns, the Romneys artificially kept their tax rate above 13 percent by claiming deductions for just over half of their $4 million charitable donation. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Romney has previously said that he never paid less than 13 percent on his federal income taxes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/blogs/mitts-view/2012/09/note-trustee-brad-malt&quot;&gt;Malt writes:&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;The Romneys&amp;rsquo; generous charitable donations in 2011 would have significantly reduced their tax obligation for the year. The Romneys thus limited their deduction of charitable contributions to conform to the Governor's statement in August, based upon the January estimate of income, that he paid at least 13% in income taxes in each of the last 10 years.&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Romney could still opt to recoup the money sometime in the future. Tax experts told &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/business-insider&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Business Insider&lt;/a&gt; Friday that Romney can amend his returns any time within the next three years, and request the full deduction from the U.S. government.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Romney, who filed for an extension on his 2011 returns, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/learn/mitt/tax-return/2011/wmr-adr-return&quot;&gt;said in April that he would release the returns after they were finalized and submitted to the IRS.&lt;/a&gt; He released his 2010 tax returns earlier this year, but has said he will not release any additional years of returns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The campaign does appear to have made a concession on that front however. Along with the candidate's 2011 tax returns, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/sites/default/files/shared/pwc_letter_for_tax_website2.pdf&quot;&gt;the campaign has posted a letter from Romneys tax preparer, PriceWaterhouseCoopers, summarizing Romney's tax rates from 1990 to 2009.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The letter claims that Romney's average federal income tax rate over those 20 years was 20.20%; that the lowest rate Romney paid was 13.66%; and that there were no years during which Romney did not owe both federal and state income taxes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Romney and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/sites/default/files/shared/pdr_dr_letter.pdf&quot;&gt;his running mate Paul Ryan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;also released &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/sites/default/files/shared/wmr_dr_letter.pdf&quot;&gt;letters from physicians&lt;/a&gt;, declaring the candidates to be in preternaturally good health.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/disclosure&quot;&gt;You can check out all of the new docs here &amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/disclosure&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*This post has been updated&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/505cd265ecad046b2f00001b/mitt-romney-paid-extra-taxes-last-year-but-he-can-get-the-money-back-after-the-election.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-2011-tax-returns-release-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>Mitt Romney Releasing 2011 Tax Returns TODAY</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-2011-tax-returns-release-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 13:44:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Grace Wyler</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;Mitt Romney's campaign announced today that it will be releasing the Romneys full 2011 tax returns online today at 3 p.m.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a blog post this afternoon, Brad Malt, the trustee of Romney's blind trust, said that the Romneys filed their 2011 tax return with the IRS today. Notably, the returns will be posted with a letter from PriceWaterhouseCoopers giving a summary of the Romneys tax rates for the period between 1990 and 2009.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The letter is a shift from &lt;span&gt;Romney's past stance on releasing tax returns, and is an&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;apparent concession to demands for more tax returns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Romney has always pledged to release his 2011 tax returns, in addition to the 2010 returns that he has already disclosed. He and his wife released a summary of the 2011 returns earlier this year after filing for an extension with the IRS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's Malt's full blog post:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;This morning, Gov. and Mrs. Romney filed their 2011 tax return with the IRS. At 3:00pm today, the Romney for President campaign will be posting the 2011 return online.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The complete 2011 tax return, with full schedules, statements, and attachments, will be made available with all other previously-disclosed information at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/disclosure&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;www.mittromney.com/disclosure&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Also posted will be a notarized letter from the Romneys&amp;rsquo; tax preparer, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/pricewaterhousecoopers&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;PricewaterhouseCoopers&lt;/a&gt;, LLP (PWC), giving a summary of tax rates from the Romneys&amp;rsquo; tax returns for the 20-year period of 1990-2009.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;In advance of the posting of these new documents, I wanted to provide some top-line details.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Regarding the newly-filed 2011 Tax Return:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;In 2011, the Romneys paid $1,935,708 in taxes on $13,696,951 in mostly investment income.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The Romneys&amp;rsquo; effective tax rate for 2011 was 14.1%.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The Romneys donated $4,020,772 to charity in 2011, amounting to nearly 30% of their income.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The Romneys claimed a deduction for $2.25 million of those charitable contributions.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The Romneys&amp;rsquo; generous charitable donations in 2011 would have significantly reduced their tax obligation for the year. The Romneys thus limited their deduction of charitable contributions to conform to the Governor's statement in August, based upon the January estimate of income, that he paid at least 13% in income taxes in each of the last 10 years.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;As with the 2010 tax return, the 2011 tax return will appear as four separate documents. It includes Governor and Mrs. Romney's Form 1040 as well as three underlying Massachusetts trusts detailing the sources of their income. Those are The W. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/mitt-romney&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Mitt Romney&lt;/a&gt; Blind Trust, The Ann D. Romney Blind Trust, and The Romney Family Trust.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The investments within the trusts are managed on a blind basis by me, the trustee. I have sole responsibility for making, holding and disposing of the investments.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Regarding the PWC letter covering the Romneys&amp;rsquo; tax filings over 20 years, from 1990 &amp;ndash; 2009:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;In&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;each year&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;during the entire 20-year period, the Romneys owed both state and federal income taxes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Over the entire 20-year period, the average annual effective federal tax rate was 20.20%.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Over the entire 20-year period, the lowest annual effective federal personal tax rate was 13.66%.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Over the entire 20-year period, the Romneys gave to charity an average of 13.45% of their adjusted gross income.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Over the entire 20-year period, the total federal and state taxes owed plus the total charitable donations deducted represented 38.49% of total AGI.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;During the 20-year period covered by the PWC letter, Gov. and Mrs. Romney paid 100 percent of the taxes that they owed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Finally, in addition to new documents related to tax filings, the campaign will also be posting on the same website physician letters for both Gov. Romney and Rep. Ryan, making public their current state of health.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;After you have reviewed all of the newly-posted documents, you may have further questions. The campaign asks that you direct them to an e-mail account set up for that purpose. That e-mail address is&amp;nbsp;returns @&lt;a href=&quot;http://mittromney.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;mittromney.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thank you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;R. Bradford Malt is a partner at Ropes &amp;amp; Gray, LLP. He has been the trustee of the Romney&amp;rsquo;s blind trust since 2003.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-2011-tax-returns-release-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static5.businessinsider.com/image/4ff2e7aaecad045d15000001/mitt-romney-releasing-2011-tax-returns-today.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-fundraising-video-leak-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>Now The Romney Video Leaker Is Threatening To Release His Tax Returns</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-fundraising-video-leak-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 16:52:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Grace Wyler</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;Anne Onymous, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/youtube&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt; user who anonymously circulated the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/live-full-romney-fundraiser-video-2012-9&quot;&gt;now-infamous video of Mitt Romney speaking at a private fundraiser&lt;/a&gt;, now appears to be threatening to release the Republican candidate's tax returns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a tweet, sent Tuesday afternoon by a user with the handle&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AnneOnymous670/status/248159998587305986&quot;&gt;AnneOnymous670&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static3.businessinsider.com/image/5058de74eab8ea462b00000d-502-247/anne-onymous-tweet.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;anne onymous tweet&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very little is known about the source who leaked the video of Romney's fundraiser, so the credibility of the new threat is unclear.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what we do know:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On May 17, Romney spoke with donors at a private fundraiser in Boca Raton, Fla., hosted by private equity executive Marc Leder.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A clip, reportedly from the fundraiser, surfaced online three months ago, featuring Romney describing the working conditions at a factory he visited in China during his years at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/bain-capital&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Bain Capital&lt;/a&gt;. The clip, posted by a user named Rachel Maddow, was taken down because the user was not the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/msnbc&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;MSNBC&lt;/a&gt; host. It was reposted by another user, RomneyExposed, along with three other clips from the fundraiser. On June 10, a commenter named RomneyExposed started promoting the clips on the Huffington Post.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three weeks ago, six additional clips were posted on YouTube by the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/channel/UChMTCCC6dzR-VkgTDWo7H_A/videos?flow=grid&amp;amp;view=0&quot;&gt;user Anne Onymous.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AnneOnymous670&quot;&gt;Twitter user by the same name started tweeting out the YouTube links&lt;/a&gt; on August 28, reaching out via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/twitter&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; to Mother Jones reporter David Corn, Democratic strategist Donna Brazile, Democratic National Chairwoman Debbie Wasserman Shultz, Obama's campaign press secretary Ben LaBolt and northeast regional press secretary Michael Czin, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/abc&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;ABC&lt;/a&gt; reporter Emily Friedman, and union leader Steven Tolman, president of the Massachusetts AFL-CIO.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Huffington Post&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;James Carter, a Democratic opposition researcher who also happens to be former President Jimmy Carter's grandson&lt;/strong&gt;, reached out to the source of the videos. &lt;strong&gt;Carter subsequently connected the source of the videos with David Corn of &lt;em&gt;Mother Jones.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height: 19.5px;&quot;&gt;Anne Onymous appears to be primarily concerned with the clip of Romney talking about his visit to the Chinese factory. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/u/0/112320646106945080287/about&quot;&gt;Google + page for the user Anne Onymous&lt;/a&gt;, which uses the same picture as the YouTube channel and the Twitter user, &lt;strong&gt;describes the user as living in Dongguan, China, and working at Global Tech Appliances, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt;, the company that owns the factory Romney is reported to have visited. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height: 19.5px;&quot;&gt;Here's the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/google&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; + About Me page:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height: 19.5px;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/5058e5e8ecad04ea1b000006/anne-onymous.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;anne onymous&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height: 19.5px;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Interestingly, the full video posted Tuesday, which Mother Jones claims has not been edited, does not contain the clip of Romney discussing his visit to the factory in China.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-fundraising-video-leak-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static6.businessinsider.com/image/5058df12ecad04ba12000002/now-the-romney-video-leaker-is-threatening-to-release-his-tax-returns.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/americans-obsession-with-presidential-candidates-tax-returns-goes-back-to-1968-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>Americans' Obsession With Presidential Candidates Tax Returns Goes Back To 1968</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/americans-obsession-with-presidential-candidates-tax-returns-goes-back-to-1968-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 10:56:49 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Stacey Bumpus</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static3.businessinsider.com/image/5051e8fa6bb3f78768000009-400-300/mitt-romney.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Mitt Romney&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent months, we&amp;rsquo;ve heard a lot of noise about Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gobankingrates.com/tax/tax-returns/&quot; title=&quot;Tax Returns&quot;&gt;tax returns&lt;/a&gt; &amp;mdash; and his hesitance in releasing them. But what&amp;rsquo;s the big deal? Surely there are other issues that need to be discussed outside of &lt;strong&gt;presidential candidates&amp;rsquo; tax returns&lt;/strong&gt;, so why is everyone so concerned?&lt;span id=&quot;more-223856&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apparently, a presidential candidate&amp;rsquo;s income, including how and where his or her money is invested, says a lot more than we could ever imagine. In fact, it seems we believe the numbers on a tax return actually predict the likelihood of a candidate becoming a good president.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Presidential Candidates Tax Returns Build Trust&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve been paying attention to the 2012 presidential campaigns, you&amp;rsquo;ve noticed the discussion about the &lt;strong&gt;Mitt Romney tax return&lt;/strong&gt;. While he has released his 2011 and 2010 returns, he has chosen not to release the rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what does releasing a tax return really mean to the American public? What is really at stake?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The primary reason parties want their opponents&amp;rsquo; returns released is for trust-building. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to share how much you&amp;rsquo;ve earned, you&amp;rsquo;re implying you have something to hide. Maybe you are evading taxes, even have money in &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gobankingrates.com/tax/romney-isnt-the-only-one-avoiding-taxes-how-pirate-banks-work/&quot; title=&quot;Offshore Accounts&quot;&gt;offshore accounts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this tough economy, many people are sensitive about their tax rates and some argue that the wealthy receive too many tax breaks compared to the average American citizen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To ease voters&amp;rsquo; minds and show they have nothing to hide, many candidates have begun releasing their tax returns, even though they are not required to do so. Ironically, the first person to do so was George Romney, Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s father. He made 12 years of returns available as he prepared his fight against Richard Nixon and Lyndon Johnson in 1968.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since then, the issue of releasing tax returns has sparked heated debates. Ronald Reagan and George H. W. Bush fought over tax returns until the 1980 Republican convention, and Geraldine Ferraro&amp;rsquo;s tax returns caused controversy in the 1984 presidential campaign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What Do Romney&amp;rsquo;s and Obama&amp;rsquo;s Tax Returns Show?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since controversy erupted over Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s tax returns, he willingly released returns from the past two tax years. An &lt;strong&gt;Obama tax return&lt;/strong&gt; for each year of the past decade is also available. So what do they show?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obama&amp;rsquo;s 2011 tax return showed he paid an effective federal income tax rate of 20.5 percent. His return shows that about half of his $789,674 reported income came from his &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gobankingrates.com/presidential-salary-barack-obama/&quot; title=&quot;President's salary&quot;&gt;President&amp;rsquo;s salary&lt;/a&gt;, while the other half came from book sales proceeds. In total, the Obamas paid a total of $152,074 in taxes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An estimate of his 2011 return showed Romney and his wife, Ann, reported earning $21 million while paying $3.2 million in taxes. According to his filed 2010 tax return, he paid a relatively low income tax rate of 13.9 percent on $21.7 million in earnings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason for this low tax rate is reportedly his significant investment income, which is taxed at 15 percent.&amp;nbsp; He also had extensive itemized deductions that lowered his tax liability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So do these figures determine who will be a better president? Better yet, do they show who we are more likely to elect? Nope. No presidential election has been decided by a tax return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some even argue that focusing on tax returns diverts attention from the real issues, while others contend that seeing a tax return not only provides insight into the candidate&amp;rsquo;s personal life, but the types of policies he or she is likely to push as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For instance, Reagan strongly opposed government taxes. Could it have been because his 1979 tax return showed he paid nearly 50 percent of his income in taxes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If Obama wants to raise taxes for the wealthy, could it be that he wants to punish individuals significantly wealthier than him? Or could &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gobankingrates.com/tax/flat-tax-pros-cons-would-work-us/&quot; title=&quot;Romney's Push to Lower Taxes&quot;&gt;Romney&amp;rsquo;s push to lower taxes&lt;/a&gt; for the wealthy (and everyone else) be because he wants to reward his friends?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How voters feel about the connection between candidates and their wealth may make a difference at the polls. According to an analysis conducted by TheStreet.com, the candidates with the most net worth often don&amp;rsquo;t have the best success in presidential elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, four of the five wealthiest candidates in recent years &amp;mdash; Ross Perot, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/steve-forbes&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Steve Forbes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/al-gore&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Al Gore&lt;/a&gt; and John Kerry &amp;mdash; didn&amp;rsquo;t make it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s net worth resting at an estimated $250 million, some wonder if his tax return will hurt more than help his chances of winning. But it won&amp;rsquo;t be until November, when voters head to the polls, that the real fate of these candidates will be determined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/jeanne-marie-laskas-uncovers-the-secrets-of-hidden-america-2012-9&quot;&gt;DON'T MISS: What one woman learned travelling through &quot;Hidden America&quot; &amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/americans-obsession-with-presidential-candidates-tax-returns-goes-back-to-1968-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/5051e8fa6bb3f78768000009/americans-obsession-with-presidential-candidates-tax-returns-goes-back-to-1968.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/these-15-events-could-decide-who-wins-the-election-in-november-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>15 Events That Could Decide Who Wins The Election In November</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/these-15-events-could-decide-who-wins-the-election-in-november-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 15:25:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Eric Pianin and Josh Boak</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dropCap&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static1.businessinsider.com/image/4ecd7def6bb3f7ed7000000a/mitt-romney-barack-obama.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;mitt romney barack obama&quot; /&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;ith a mere 58 days to go, the political calendar is destiny, and a handful of key dates and events could profoundly impact the outcome of a rough and tumble and remarkably close race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fact that Republican presidential nominee &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/mitt-romney&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Mitt Romney&lt;/a&gt; spent last week prepping for the first presidential debate with President Obama while Democrats held their national convention tells a lot about the remaining forces that could decide the Nov. 6 election.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These include four candidate debates, possible action by the Federal Reserve, government reports on unemployment and third-quarter economic growth, and what &amp;mdash; if anything &amp;mdash; Congress decides to do in advance of the general&amp;nbsp; election to blunt tough spending cuts and tax increases scheduled to take effect next January that could carry the country over a fiscal cliff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last Friday, Obama was thrown a curve ball when the August jobs report showed a mere 96,000 jobs were created even though the unemployment rate had dropped to 8.1 percent from 8.3 percent.&amp;nbsp; The reason:&amp;nbsp; 368,000 Americans dropped out of the labor force last month and another 213,000 never joined it at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas Mann, a congressional scholar with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/brookings-institution&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Brookings Institution&lt;/a&gt;, said last week he expects little substantive action from the sorely divided Congress before the election, but thinks that last minute actions by the Fed and the release of more government economic analysis could tip the balance of the election by altering &amp;ldquo;voter perceptions of the economy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s more, international events, such as further debt-related&amp;nbsp; turmoil in the euro zone or a crisis in the Middle East could move the political needle one way or another. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that Israel is going to launch an attack on Iranian nuclear facilities, but that certainly could be a wild card,&amp;rdquo; Mann said. &amp;ldquo;I would say the most important unknowables&amp;nbsp; are really developments in the economy, and stories about it.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter Hart, the Democratic pollster, said there are some things the candidates can control, such as their performances in the presidential and vice presidential&amp;nbsp; debates and other carefully planned major campaign events,&amp;nbsp; but they will have little choice but to&amp;nbsp; roll with the consequences in many situations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Most of the big [potential developments] are international and congressional and are not in the president&amp;rsquo;s control, and they&amp;rsquo;re more likely to splatter on the president&amp;rsquo;s windshield than on the Romney windshield,&amp;rdquo; Hart told The Fiscal Times. &amp;ldquo;When you&amp;rsquo;re in office it&amp;rsquo;s up to you to be able to say, &amp;lsquo;Here&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m going to do and here&amp;rsquo;s how we&amp;rsquo;re going to solve it.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While there is always the possibility of an &amp;ldquo;October surprise&amp;rdquo; in the campaign, here are more than a dozen key dates or events in the political calendar leading up to the election:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/504e3bd36bb3f7025e000006/dnu.png&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;DNU &quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/504e3bfd69bedde85200000c/dnu.png&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;DNU&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;More from The Fiscal Times&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;recommendationsList_0_dual&quot; class=&quot;outbrain_dual_reg_ul_class recommendations_ul&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;outbrain_rec_li&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefiscaltimes.com/Articles/2012/08/28/Sexy-Social-Robots-Go-Gaga-at-a-Tokyo-Cabaret.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;rec-link&quot; data-bitly-type=&quot;bitly_hover_card&quot;&gt;Sexy Social Robots Go Gaga at a Tokyo Cabaret&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;outbrain_rec_li&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefiscaltimes.com/Articles/2012/09/09/Obamas-Lead-Over-Romney-Widens-Despite-Jobs-Data.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;rec-link&quot; data-bitly-type=&quot;bitly_hover_card&quot;&gt;Obama's Lead Over Romney Widens Despite Jobs Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;outbrain_rec_li&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefiscaltimes.com/Articles/2012/09/02/The-Obama-Presidency-Why-Partisanship-Prevails.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;rec-link&quot; data-bitly-type=&quot;bitly_hover_card&quot;&gt;The Obama Presidency: Why Partisanship Prevails&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;outbrain_rec_li&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefiscaltimes.com/Articles/2012/09/06/Woodward-Congress-Snubbed-Obama-in-Debt-Talks.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;rec-link&quot; data-bitly-type=&quot;bitly_hover_card&quot;&gt;Woodward: Congress Snubbed Obama in Debt Talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;outbrain_rec_li&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefiscaltimes.com/Articles/2012/09/09/Romney-on-the-Attack-Over-Grim-Jobs-Numbers.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;rec-link&quot; data-bitly-type=&quot;bitly_hover_card&quot;&gt;Romney on the Attack Over Grim Jobs Numbers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;outbrain_rec_li&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefiscaltimes.com/Articles/2012/08/29/10-Public-Colleges-with-Insanely-Luxurious-Dorms.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;rec-link&quot; data-bitly-type=&quot;bitly_hover_card&quot;&gt;10 Public Colleges with Insanely Luxurious Dorms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;outbrain_container_0_dual&quot; class=&quot;div-wrapper&quot;&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;OutbrainVoterDiv_0_dual&quot; class=&quot;voterDiv&quot;&gt;
&lt;p id=&quot;outbrain_dual_divider_0_dual&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;overflow: hidden; color: #000000; background-color: transparent; text-align: left; text-decoration: none;&quot;&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;overflow: hidden; color: #000000; background-color: transparent; text-align: left; text-decoration: none;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/these-15-events-could-decide-who-wins-the-election-in-november-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static1.businessinsider.com/image/4ecd7def6bb3f7ed7000000a/15-events-that-could-decide-who-wins-the-election-in-november.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/pwc-there-is-no-evidence-hackers-took-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>PwC: No Evidence Hackers Took Mitt Romney's Taxes  Secret Service And FBI Now Investigating</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/pwc-there-is-no-evidence-hackers-took-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 16:43:02 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Julia La Roche</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static3.businessinsider.com/image/503f640869beddda38000010/keyboard-hacker-close-up.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;keyboard hacker close-up&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some anonymous hackers are&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/hackers-claim-to-have-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9&quot;&gt;claiming to be in possession of Mitt Romney's tax returns&lt;/a&gt; saying they took them in the night on August 25th from PriceWaterhouseCoopers' offices in Franklin, Tennessee, according to a&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://pastebin.com/zdU1TK40&quot;&gt;release on Pastebin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;dated Sept. 2.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In another &lt;a href=&quot;http://pastebin.com/1j1yzQ9&quot;&gt;Pastebin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;post dated Sept. 4, the hackers threaten to release Romney's tax returns unless they receive a payment of $1 million bitcoins.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We expect that it's total nonsense.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, PriceWaterhouseCoopers released a statement this afternoon saying there's no evidence of any theft of Romney's tax records and they're working with the U.S. Secret Service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the statement&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;[via&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.wsj.com/washwire/2012/09/05/pwc-no-evidence-of-theft-of-romney-tax-returns/&quot;&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;]:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&quot;We&amp;rsquo;re aware of the allegations that have been made about improper access to our systems. We are working closely with the United States Secret Service, and at this time, there is no evidence that our systems have been compromised or that there was any unauthorized access to the data in question,&quot; PwC said in a statement.&quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to political journalist Marc Ambinder, &lt;a href=&quot;https://es.twitter.com/marcambinder/status/243441486765625345&quot;&gt;the FBI and the Secret Service are both investigating &quot;extortion&quot; attempt&lt;/a&gt; by the hackers to release Romney's tax records.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEE ALSO: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/hackers-claim-to-have-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9&quot;&gt;OH PLEASE! This Story About Hackers Having Mitt Romney's Tax Return Is Almost Certainly Nonsense &amp;gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/pwc-there-is-no-evidence-hackers-took-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static6.businessinsider.com/image/503f640869beddda38000010/pwc-no-evidence-hackers-took-mitt-romneys-taxes--secret-service-and-fbi-now-investigating.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/hackers-claim-to-have-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9</guid>
                    <title>OH PLEASE! This Story About Hackers Stealing Mitt Romney's Tax Return Is Almost Certainly Nonsense</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/hackers-claim-to-have-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 14:29:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Julia La Roche</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static5.businessinsider.com/image/50229285ecad04ef0f00000e/mitt-romney.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Mitt Romney&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This has got to be total nonsense, but it's getting tweeted around a bunch, so we'll just mention it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A group of hackers claim to be in possession of Mitt Romney's tax returns after they took them in the night from PriceWaterhouseCoopers' offices in Franklin, Tennessee, according to a &lt;a href=&quot;http://pastebin.com/zdU1TK40&quot;&gt;release on Pastebin&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that's not all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They also said they are holding the tax returns for a ransom of $1 million bitcoins, according to another post on &lt;a href=&quot;http://pastebin.com/1j1yzQ9&quot;&gt;Pastebin&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An anonymous post on Pastbein asking for Bitcoins? That's basically a parody of hackers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the description of how the tax returns were purloined is implausible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the Sept. 2 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pastebin.com/zdU1TK40&quot;&gt;Pastebin release&lt;/a&gt;: (emphasis ours)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;PWC Office @ 830 Crescent Centre Drive, Suite 260, Franklin, TN 37067&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Telephone: [1] (615) 503-2860&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Romney's 1040 tax returns were taken from the PWC office 8/25/2012 by gaining access to the third floor via a gentleman working on the 3rd floor of the building. Once on the 3rd floor, the team moved down the stairs to the 2nd floor and setup shop in an empty office room. During the night, suite 260 was entered, and all available 1040 tax forms for Romney were copied. A package was sent to the PWC on suite 260 with a flash drive containing a copy of the 1040 files, plus copies were sent to the Democratic office in the county and copies were sent to the GOP office in the county at the beginning of the week also containing flash drives with copies of Romney's tax returns before 2010. A scanned signature image for Mitt Romney from the 1040 forms were scanned and included with the packages, taken from earlier 1040 tax forms gathered and stored on the flash drives.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;The group will release all available files to the public on the 28 of September, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;This line is on all the package letters for authenticity of the email being sent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;all these considerations did not deter me from the path of duty&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the Sept. 4th &lt;a href=&quot;http://pastebin.com/1j1yzQ9S&quot;&gt;Pastebin release:&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; (emphasis ours)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Dear &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/pricewaterhousecoopers&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;PricewaterhouseCoopers&lt;/a&gt; LLP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Using your Office @ 830 Crescent Centre Drive, Suite 260, Franklin, TN 37067 &amp;nbsp;Telephone: [1] (615) 503-2860 we were able to gain access to your network file servers and copy over the tax documents for one Willard M Romney and Ann D Romney. We are sure that once you figure out where the security breach was, some people will probably get fired but that is not our concern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;All major news media outlets are going to be sent an encrypted copy of the most recent tax years that your company had on file since you did not have them all in a convenient electronic form. The years before 2010 will be of great interest to many. If the parties interested do not want the encrypted key released to the public to unlock these documents on September 28 of this year then payment will be necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The deal is quite simple. Convert $1,000,000 USD to Bitcoins (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/google&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; if if you need a lesson on what Bitcoin is) using the various markets available out in the world for buying. Transfer the Bitcoins gathered to the Bitcoin address listed below. It does not matter if small amounts or one large amount is transferred, as long as the final value of the Bitcoins is equal to $1,000,000 USD at the time when it is finished. The keys to unlock the data will be purged and what ever is inside the documents will remain a secret forever.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Failure to do this before September 28, the entire world will be allowed to view the documents with a publicly released key to unlock everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Address to Stop Release:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;1HeF89wMjC48bWNgWvVo7Wu3RaLW8XVsE8&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;And the same time, the other interested parties will be allowed to compete with you. For those that DO want the documents released will have an different address to send to. If $1,000,000 USD is sent to this account below first; then the encryption keys will be made available to the world right away. So this is an equal opportunity for the documents to remain locked away forever or to be exposed before the September 28 deadline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Who-ever is the winner does not matter to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Address to Promote Full Release&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;12AP6iCwRNFQqKLStH3A4b4hw3SL6RaNgB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;Reference to avoid Fakes that only you will have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;1.all these considerations did not deter me from the path of duty&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;2.he moment I understood the will of my Heavenly Father&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; CNBC's Eamon Javers Tweeted that the Romney campaign &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/EamonJavers/status/243422013266485248&quot;&gt;is aware of hackers' claim and &quot;authorities are investigating.&lt;/a&gt;&quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;[Hat Tip:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://mashable.com/2012/09/05/hacker-ransom-romney-tax-returns/&quot;&gt;Mashable.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;]&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/hackers-claim-to-have-mitt-romneys-tax-returns-2012-9#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static6.businessinsider.com/image/50229285ecad04ef0f00000e/oh-please-this-story-about-hackers-stealing-mitt-romneys-tax-return-is-almost-certainly-nonsense.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-tax-returns-rate-policy-release-mormon-tithes-2012-8</guid>
                    <title>Mitt Romney Says That The Reason He Won't Release His Tax Returns Has To Do With His Religion</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-tax-returns-rate-policy-release-mormon-tithes-2012-8</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 16:09:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Brett LoGiurato</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static3.businessinsider.com/image/50368d1beab8ea7e2d000067/mitt-romney.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Mitt Romney&quot; /&gt;Mitt Romney&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-tax-returns-romney-says-he-will-not-release-any-more-2012-7&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;has said he won't release more than two years of tax returns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;because &quot;you&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;can never satisfy the opposition research team of the Obama organization.&quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;But in a forthcoming interview with&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Parade&lt;/em&gt; magazine, Romney revealed a new reason why he's hesitant to release more returns: &lt;strong&gt;He does not want to make public his donations to the&amp;nbsp;LDS Church&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what Romney told&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Parade&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/politics/54744938-90/romney-says-church-tithing.html.csp&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;according to The Salt-Lake Tribune&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;TEXT_w_Indent&quot; style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;Our church doesn&amp;rsquo;t publish how much people have given. This is done entirely privately. One of the downsides of releasing one&amp;rsquo;s financial information is that this is now all public, but we had never intended our contributions to be known. It&amp;rsquo;s a very personal thing between ourselves and our commitment to our God and to our church.&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id=&quot;inlineContent&quot; class=&quot;left doubleWide&quot;&gt;Romney has released one year of tax returns and plans to release another before the election. He has come under fire from the Obama campaign and Democrats like&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/harry-reid-mitt-romney-tax-returns-offshore-accounts-hiding-reince-priebus-2012-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/harry-reid-mitt-romney-tax-returns-offshore-accounts-hiding-reince-priebus-2012-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;who charged that Romney did not pay taxes for 10 years&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;left doubleWide&quot;&gt;His one year of released returns shows that Romney donated just less than $4.1 million to the LDS Church on an income of more than $40 million.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;left doubleWide&quot;&gt;In bringing up a new reason for not releasing the returns, however, Romney may have thrust the subject back into the news cycle for the next few days as the Republican National Convention prepares to start up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-tax-returns-rate-policy-release-mormon-tithes-2012-8#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/50368d1beab8ea7e2d000067/mitt-romney-says-that-the-reason-he-wont-release-his-tax-returns-has-to-do-with-his-religion.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-ryan-medicare-paul-vp-health-care-obamacare-2012-8</guid>
                    <title>Obama Unleashes On Medicare: Under Mitt Romney And Paul Ryan, 'You Could Not Count On Health Care'</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-ryan-medicare-paul-vp-health-care-obamacare-2012-8</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 16:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Brett LoGiurato</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/502ff3daecad04fa50000002/barack-obama.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Barack Obama&quot; /&gt;WINDHAM, N.H. &amp;mdash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;President Barack Obama today used his harshest attack line yet on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/mitt-romney&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Mitt Romney&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/paul-ryan&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Paul Ryan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;'s Medicare plan, warning a New Hampshire crowd here that they would not be able to &quot;count on health care&quot; under the Romney-Ryan plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The words were the sharpest attack yet in a fiery campaign speech here to a packed crowd of 2,300 in Windham High School's gymnasium. Obama added a personal warning to his usual stump speech, which claims that Romney and Ryan would &quot;end Medicare as we know it.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&quot;My&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;il&quot;&gt;plan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;has already extended the life of Medicare by nearly a decade,&quot; Obama said. &quot;Their&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;il&quot;&gt;plan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;would put Medicare on track to be ended as we know it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&quot;It would be an&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class=&quot;il&quot;&gt;entirely&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class=&quot;il&quot;&gt;different&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class=&quot;il&quot;&gt;plan&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;mdash; a&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class=&quot;il&quot;&gt;plan&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;in which you could not count on health care because it would have to be coming out of your pocket. That&amp;rsquo;s the real difference between our plans on&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Medicare.&quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a day in which &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-taxes-1-percent-paul-ryan-budget-plan-2012-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Obama saved his deepest criticism for Ryan&lt;/a&gt;, newly added to the Republican ticket as Romney's running mate last weekend.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Later in his speech, he hit the Romney-Ryan ticket on taxes, saying that Romney would pay only 1 percent in taxes under Ryan's plan. That comment drew a sharp rebuke from the Romney campaign.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But in a week in which the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/mitt-romney-whiteboard-medicare-obama-paul-ryan-budget-2012-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;conversation on the campaign trail has been dominated by Medicare&lt;/a&gt;, Obama hit the Republican ticket hardest on the subject.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;:The latest thing they&amp;rsquo;ve been trying is to talk about Medicare,&quot; Obama said. &lt;strong&gt;Now, you would think they would avoid talking about Medicare, given the fact that both of them have proposed to voucherize the Medicare system.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But I guess they figure the best defense is to try to go on offense.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;So, New Hampshire, here is what you need to know:&amp;nbsp; Since I have been in office, I have strengthened Medicare. I have made reforms that have extended the life of the program, that have saved millions of seniors with Medicare hundreds of dollars on their prescription drugs.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meanwhile, on the Republican side&lt;/strong&gt;, Ryan appeared at a campaign stop in Florida with his mother, a 78-year-old Floridian who Ryan said has been on Medicare for 10 years. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jLqb4Zj5y3k&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ryan charged Obama&lt;/a&gt; with &quot;raiding Medicare&quot; to &quot;pay for Obamacare.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-ryan-medicare-paul-vp-health-care-obamacare-2012-8#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static1.businessinsider.com/image/502ff3daecad04fa50000002/obama-unleashes-on-medicare-under-mitt-romney-and-paul-ryan-you-could-not-count-on-health-care.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-taxes-1-percent-paul-ryan-budget-plan-2012-8</guid>
                    <title>Obama Unveiled A Blistering New Attack On Mitt Romney's Taxes</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-taxes-1-percent-paul-ryan-budget-plan-2012-8</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 15:18:00 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Brett LoGiurato</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/502fe8aeecad045e38000010/barack-obama.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Barack Obama&quot; /&gt;WINDHAM, N.H. &amp;mdash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;President Barack Obama unveiled a brand new attack on&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/blackboard/mitt-romney&quot; class=&quot;hidden_link&quot;&gt;Mitt Romney&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;'s taxes here in New Hampshire today, charging that Romney will only pay 1 percent under vice presidential nominee&amp;nbsp;Paul Ryan's budget plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the key part of his speech to the enthusiastic crowd in Windham High School:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The centerpiece of my opponent&amp;rsquo;s entire economic plan is a new, $5 trillion tax cut, a lot of it going to the wealthiest Americans.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;And his new running mate, Congressman Ryan, put forward a plan that would let Governor Romney pay less than 1% in taxes each year&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the kicker: he expects you to pick up the tab. Governor Romney&amp;rsquo;s tax plan would actually raise taxes on middle-class families with children by an average of $2,000.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; Not to reduce the deficit, or grow jobs, or invest in education &amp;shy;but to give another tax cut to people like him.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-left: 30px;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ask Governor Romney and his running mate when they&amp;rsquo;re here in New Hampshire on Monday if they think that&amp;rsquo;s fair.&amp;nbsp;Ask them how it&amp;rsquo;ll grow the economy, or strengthen the middle-class.&amp;nbsp;They have tried to sell us this trickle-down fairy dust before.&amp;nbsp;It didn&amp;rsquo;t work then and it won&amp;rsquo;t work now.&amp;nbsp;It&amp;rsquo;s not a plan to create jobs.&amp;nbsp;It&amp;rsquo;s not a plan to cut the deficit. And it&amp;rsquo;s not a plan to move our economy forward.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bolded lines drew a sharp rebuke from the crowd, which seemed somewhat stunned at Obama providing them with the information.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The charge comes from Ryan's description of his budget plan&lt;/strong&gt;, which proposes to eliminate&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;taxes on interest, capital gains, and dividends &amp;mdash; most of Romney's sources of income.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two separate analyses from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rollcall.com/news/Ryan-Tax-Plan-Would-Slash-Romney-Tax-Rate-to-1-Percent-216837-1.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Roll Call&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2012/08/mitt-romney-would-pay-082-percent-in-taxes-under-paul-ryans-plan/261027/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;found that Romney's tax rate would have been cut to about 1 percent in 2010, the only full-year return Romney has made public.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it's important to remember that Romney is the name at the top of the ticket running for president, and he has said that he supports &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mittromney.com/issues/tax&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;maintaining current tax levels&lt;/a&gt; on interest, capital gains and dividends.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Romney campaign spokesman Ryan Williams responded to news of Obama's comments by saying that Romney would eliminate these types of taxes on the middle class.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&quot;The fact is President Obama wants to raise taxes on private investment and job creators, which will lead to higher unemployment and fewer jobs,&quot; Williams said. &lt;strong&gt;&quot;The Romney-Ryan Plan eliminates taxes for the middle class on interest, dividends and capital gains and implements pro-growth policies to deliver more jobs and more take-home pay for middle-class families.&quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-taxes-1-percent-paul-ryan-budget-plan-2012-8#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static2.businessinsider.com/image/502fe8aeecad045e38000010/obama-unveiled-a-blistering-new-attack-on-mitt-romneys-taxes.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                                               <item>
                    <guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-tax-returns-prove-release-offshore-accounts-2012-8</guid>
                    <title>The Obama Campaign Dares Mitt Romney To 'Prove' His Tax Claims Are True</title>
                    <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-tax-returns-prove-release-offshore-accounts-2012-8</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 16:43:20 -0400</pubDate>
                                            <dc:creator>Brett LoGiurato</dc:creator>
                                        <description>
                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;float_right&quot; src=&quot;http://static5.businessinsider.com/image/502d5b31eab8ead078000005/mitt-romney.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;Mitt Romney&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Obama campaign wouldn't let&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Mitt Romney&lt;/strong&gt; off the hook after he said today that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-returns-obama-2012-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;he has never paid less than a 13 percent tax rate&lt;/a&gt;. Ben LaBolt, the campaign's national press secretary, challenged Romney to &quot;prove his claim.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&quot;We would say, 'Prove it, Gov. Romney,&quot;&lt;/strong&gt; LaBolt said this afternoon on a conference call with reporters.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier on Thursday, Romney said during a press conference that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/romney-taxes-returns-obama-2012-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;he went back and looked at his taxes&lt;/a&gt; over the past 10 years, in response, partly, to a wild allegation from&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/harry-reid-mitt-romney-taxes-returns-bain-capital-offshore-2012-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Romney hasn't paid&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; taxes over the past 10 years&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;I did go back and look at my taxes and over the past 10 years I never paid less than 13 percent. I think the most recent year is 13.6 or something like that,&amp;rdquo; Romney said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;So I&amp;rsquo;ve paid taxes every single year. Harry Reid&amp;rsquo;s charge is totally false,&amp;rdquo; Romney added. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m sure waiting for Harry to put up who it was that told him what he says they told him. I don&amp;rsquo;t believe it for a minute by the way.&quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then again, it's impossible to verify even Romney's claims without seeing any of the returns. On the conference call, LaBolt noted that Romney's personal financial disclosure forms did not reveal specifics into his offshore holdings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p1&quot;&gt;&quot;He has the ability to prove his claim,&quot; LaBolt said. &quot;This is a candidate who has defied bipartisan precedent&quot; by not releasing more than two years of tax returns, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-romney-tax-returns-prove-release-offshore-accounts-2012-8#comments&quot;&gt;Join the conversation about this story &amp;#187;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    </description>
                                            <media:thumbnail url="http://static6.businessinsider.com/image/502d5b31eab8ead078000005/the-obama-campaign-dares-mitt-romney-to-prove-his-tax-claims-are-true.jpg" />
                                                        </item>
                       </channel>
</rss>

