http://www.businessinsider.com/mtgox-statement-on-withdrawals-2014-2/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Tue, 22 Jul 2014 15:07:33 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: local (via varnish1)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 54867
X-Varnish: 451900653
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 23.20.30.63
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>Bitcoin Just Completely Crashed As Major Exchange Says Withdrawals Remain Halted</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/mtgox-statement-on-withdrawals-2014-2/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 11:07:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Joe Weisenthal</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fc4f8f69beddb45f905b66</guid>
				<title>Morgana</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 23:52:31 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fc4f8f69beddb45f905b66</link>
				<description>This story is presented in an alarmist light and, down to the misleading opening graphic that appears to how bitcoin crashing to nothing, shows it reaching a minimum, at a poin I have yet to see on any exchange personally, still above $600 where its hanging tough. Its hanging tough because its not crashing and burning as this story alludes. Its hanging tough because it has enough confidence behind it not o crash. This is an article that seeks to keep you ill informed and scared. Cryptocurrency is a remarkable invention and, when understood clearly and plainly, makes perfect sense as a currency, thats the entire point of it.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa5a0f69bedd8b60f92b2d</guid>
				<title>wizened</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 12:12:47 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa5a0f69bedd8b60f92b2d</link>
				<description>@BTC_is_a_joke it may be true that Mt Gox was operating a ponzi scheme, but that does not make BTC in and of itself a ponzi scheme.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa5328ecad040361f92b30</guid>
				<title>Carlos Osuna</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 11:43:20 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa5328ecad040361f92b30</link>
				<description>&quot;Withdrawals in actual currency are working&quot;.... you made me laugh... Bitcoin is an actual currency to the point people are giving it value. In the current market crazed world where most world economies are pushing to devalue, just to see exports rise, Bitcoin is one of the only places where real supply and demand push the price up and down with none government intervention.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa4c06eab8ea0a38f92b2d</guid>
				<title>Dominic Amann</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 11:12:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa4c06eab8ea0a38f92b2d</link>
				<description>The headline and first line are completely sensationalized. Many, many people will read only that and take it that Bitcoins are now worthless. In fact, this kind of reporting is liable to devalue bitcoins.

The conclusion (and most of the article) is valid, but please, that kind of cheap attention grabbing is positively misleading.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa3cc66bb3f7a301f92b2e</guid>
				<title>Rassah</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 10:07:50 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa3cc66bb3f7a301f92b2e</link>
				<description>This time it's not different in a sense that this time the crash is just like the tons of other crashes bitcoin has gone through: minor blips with quick recoveries.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa3574ecad044d7825ada1</guid>
				<title>Rassah</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 09:36:36 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa3574ecad044d7825ada1</link>
				<description>Oh joe, you silly media monkey. Are you lying with graphs again, showing a big &quot;crash&quot; with the bottom scale starting all the way at 600 instead of 0? $700 to $600, and back to $700 within a day or two isn't much of a crash. Sorry you didn't bother do to any actual investigative reporting on this topic, either, since, if you had, you would've been able to report a much more scandalous story abouut how MtGox is trying to divert attention from their own problems, by blaming them on an insignificant bug that's been known since 2011.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa355869bedda950f6350d</guid>
				<title>Hoosier Daddy</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 09:36:08 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa355869bedda950f6350d</link>
				<description>Did he mention his salary was in bitcoins?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa18a46da8119d4578ca19</guid>
				<title>Jashan</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 07:33:40 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa18a46da8119d4578ca19</link>
				<description>Oh well, once again Bitcoin loses a bit of ground. So what? Of course, if you look only at the chart of the last few days, it looks terrible. But take the longterm-perspective - 6 months, 12 months, 3 years ... and it's just a little bump in the road, like we've had a few before. I remember when people screamed &quot;oh noes, it crashed, it's the end of the world&quot; a few years ago when it was at 30 $/BTC ... it dropped down to about 3 $/BTC for a while. Well, but it came from 0.5 $/BTC. Then, a year or two later, it rose to 1000+ $/BTC.

It's in officially in beta - reasonable people say &quot;use with caution&quot;. Problems will arise. Problems will be discovered. Problems will be solved. For a global currency, BTC's the way to go. For local business, there's more appropriate solutions. Money as we know it today will disappear. If you disagree - let's talk in 30 years and we'll see ;-)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa07d2ecad04575a25ada7</guid>
				<title>Jc Morin</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 06:21:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52fa07d2ecad04575a25ada7</link>
				<description>First, a bitcoin crash is something we are used to because there is not that much liquidity. If someone want to buy or sell for a couple millions, the price will skyrocket or drop for a couple hours until arbitrage kicks-in properly.

Next the price on MtGox is not relevant that much, yes it was the first and biggest exchange service but for almost a year now, it's price was disconnected from reality because of long withdrawal delays. The real price of Bitcoin can be found from average of exchangers and remain fairly stable to 700 before and after the MtGox bug.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9dcd269bedd6c7dbea1f3</guid>
				<title>mario.tenkis</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 03:18:26 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9dcd269bedd6c7dbea1f3</link>
				<description>It would be good to inform yourself before you write misleading article like this which is basicly full of MtGox lies.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9c8726da8113f72bea1eb</guid>
				<title>BItcoin</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 01:51:30 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9c8726da8113f72bea1eb</link>
				<description>TLDR: what their statement is really saying: We're making scary statement to point blame elsewhere because we're trying to cover our assess legally and financially.

The back story: Mt.Gox runs buggy custom software that was creating bad transactions so their support staff was having to constantly re-send payments. Some people probably took advantage of this by using a long-known, minor issue with Bitcoin ( and an issue that Gox has known about) to trick their support staff into manually re-sending some successful payments twice. They probably lost money, so to try covering their asses legally and probably in the hopes of tanking the market so they can buy the missing coins back at a lower price they're trying to throw the whole Bitcon protocol under the bus.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9bab16da8118a2dbea1eb</guid>
				<title>urdiculous</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 00:52:49 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9bab16da8118a2dbea1eb</link>
				<description>Bitcoin crashes, Dogecoin goes to the moon! The people that bought Dogecoin didn't lose anything.... Dogecoin halves in 5 days from today meaning it will cost twice as much energy to mine the same amount of Dogecoin. This means the price on Dogecoin will go up even more after the 15th....﻿</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9b4dfeab8ea6103bea1f0</guid>
				<title>projas</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 00:27:59 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9b4dfeab8ea6103bea1f0</link>
				<description>@Good Luck: actually, it has been mostly the other way around. It has been more difficult for a long time to withdraw real currency from Mt.Gox than to withdraw Bitcoin. So now that they have problems on both ends the situation is getting more attention.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9b3406da811bd07bea1e9</guid>
				<title>projas</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 00:21:04 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9b3406da811bd07bea1e9</link>
				<description>@BTC_is_a_joke: don't make a full of yourself. Sending bitcoins can done free, meaning, if I have 10 bitcoins, I can send al 10 of them to someone else, without fee. But normally a small fee (0.0001 to 0.000001) is donated to miners to prioritize the transaction, that is just a few cents to less than a cent. 

If you want to move USD to your neighbor by converting USD to BTC, them sending them to him, then having him convert BTC to USD, I agree it is surely not the way to go. Just don't be lazy and walk to his door and give him his money.

But if you want to send money around the world to a person, in the order of a few hundred USD, traditional money services can cost more than 10% to some places (considering transmission an captive conversion). In these situations bitcoin is currently being used by real people in order to save money. I don't do it (don't need to), but I have met people that are doing it from over a year. 
Remittance is one example were traditional solutions are a worst ripoff.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9af1decad04c42abea1ed</guid>
				<title>projas</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 00:03:25 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9af1decad04c42abea1ed</link>
				<description>Yep, even Mark Karpeles (executive from Mt.Gox) owns the Bitcoin Wiki where they documented this behavior over a year ago. It seems they forgot to implement it in their custom code:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Transaction_Malleability&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Transaction_Malleability&lt;/a&gt;

It is known a known issue with the SSL protocol used by all browsers and has been taken in account in the standard bitcoin software.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9adef69beddbe59bea1e7</guid>
				<title>projas</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 23:58:23 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9adef69beddbe59bea1e7</link>
				<description>Why is it not a hedge against fiat currencies?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f995baeab8ea1d1ebea1e7</guid>
				<title>Frank L</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 22:15:06 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f995baeab8ea1d1ebea1e7</link>
				<description>MtGox has everyone fooled-
How can such an intelligent community not see this...
Due to their financial incompetence and losing millions of dollars, Mark and his team schemed a plan to stay in business and make a killing. Here are the details:

Sorry about the grammar and lack of edit. 

1. MtGox needed fresh money from new accounts and keep the existing ones with them so they devised a plan to artificially inflate their exchange rate over the other exchanges. This would attract new money and by devising an excuse that their having banking challenges; nonetheless their statement that it's taking &quot;a month or more&quot; to withdraw funds would be just enough for new money to come in and the little inconvenience could be rationalized as a good trade off benefit for the higher btc price. MtGox could control and manipulate their own market. I have no doubt there is inside trading taking place and certain people are allowed to withdraw to benefit from the higher bitcoin price on MtGox, go to another exchange to buy at a lower price and repeat again at MtGox. 

Part 2. MtGox would stretch their cash withdraw excuse as long as they could and then make another killing on the fall of btc by coming up with some technical idiotic excuse why people can't withdraw their bitcoin. They had to initiate a panic to motivate account holders who have been waiting for months to withdraw their funds to convert it into btc and also potentially attract fresh money because of the MtGox lower btc price. Greed causes blindness. MtGox sat, waited and watch account holders convert their cash into bitcoin as it started to slide with the hope they could eventually transfer them to a wallet. MtGox (inside traders) would buy up the cheaper bitcoin and moved it to other exchanges to sell at a higher price...but not quite yet...
Part 3. How do get account holders to convert their btc back to cash? Easy. Announce they can cash out. So by some miracle, MtGox banking problems have disappeared and people are now allowed to withdraw cash but not bitcoins. So now people rush to covert their bitcoin into cash, taking on huge losses in the process (not to mention all the commissions MtGox has made). By now people are just desperate to get out of the exchange with what ever they have left. 
Part 4. No way out. MtGox will no doubt halt cash withdraws as well with some other lame excuse such as their has been to much stress on our banks from all the withdraws that we need more time to work on a better system.....

Conclusion: the bitcoin and cash people had at MtGox never belonged to them - its all an illusion. MtGox relied on peoples greed to attract money and use that money to manipulate their market so they could benefit from inside trading by allowing certain people to sell high at MtGox and buy low elsewhere. This is nothing more than a ponzi scheme, the most disgusting inside trading, market manipulation and theft ever to take place.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9516a6da811a45691e350</guid>
				<title>biff</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 17:23:38 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9516a6da811a45691e350</link>
				<description>Bob Longmire, if you bought your Bitchcoins at $1,200 per Bitchcoin and now they're only worth $600 per Bitchcoin with no way to cash out, I would call that a CRASH!!! 

Seriously, though, how would I get real tangible money in any currency if I wanted to sell my Bitchcoins right fucking now? (on 2/10/2014 at 5:30 p.m., EST). Would I have to find some other sucker to sell my Bitchcoins to and convince that rube that the value would only go up? That's the one hard question that Bitchcoiners seem to gloss over all the time. I'm in a casino; I want to cash out my chips right fucking now; where's the cashier? How long to I have to wait before I can go buy my family some groceries? 

Anyone?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f95110eab8eabb2791e350</guid>
				<title>HoustonedTexan</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 17:22:08 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f95110eab8eabb2791e350</link>
				<description>Add to this the fact that the State of Florida is taking the position that merely buying and selling Bitcoins is a crime in and of itself due to their anonymous nature and has charged two people already under money laundering statutes. More states are sure to follow and that will be the end of Bitcoin.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f949cceab8ea17083b95fd</guid>
				<title>Daniel Andrews</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 16:51:08 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f949cceab8ea17083b95fd</link>
				<description>He's talking about checks, not just wire transfer. Banks escrow checks for at least a business day collecting the interest. If they didn't the fees for overdrawn balances would be enormous.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9483deab8ea52037adf6d</guid>
				<title>gosugenji</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 16:44:29 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9483deab8ea52037adf6d</link>
				<description>Bitcoin is a crock, their system is outdated and failing miserably. Blockchain has sent out a rebuttal of mtgox's claims and most updated bitcoin platforms have methods of dealing with this issue known as &quot;double spends&quot;. Please check the blog posting on their site as this article is spreading misinformation by solely relying on a burning ships address of a problem(mtgox).</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f947d469beddff4edcb100</guid>
				<title>Bob Longmire</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 16:42:44 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f947d469beddff4edcb100</link>
				<description>&quot;Completely crashed&quot; and it's still worth over $600? If BTC truly &quot;fell out of bed&quot; why didn't it hit the floor? The resilient value actually shows how strong the BTC valuation is. Apple yanks their wallet from their store, Russia tries to outlaw it and Mt Gox goes down, all within three days and BTC is still trading at $600-700. 
So you can pronounce this thing dead but your ignorance is clearly on display. You have no idea.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f946056da811cb142ca69f</guid>
				<title>Thelorax</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 16:35:01 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f946056da811cb142ca69f</link>
				<description>Why are the people around Financial Times and Business Insider so down on bitcoin? Joe Weisenthal garbles up the media that says bitcoin is a ponzi scheme and keeps pushing the idea on BI. 

Every time there is a crash, people like you &quot;itsme&quot; and the writers of FT and BI pull out the ponzi scheme BS. 

Every time, bitcoin bounces back.

This time its not different? it has already retraced half of its loss this morning.

Please, if you don't like bitcoin thats fine. But stop running around calling it a ponzi scheme when its not.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f928d6ecad04236162f203</guid>
				<title>Bob Longmire</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 14:30:30 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f928d6ecad04236162f203</link>
				<description>I can't touch my MP3's, Oh My God, there's no physical tape to hold on to, I'm going to lose them all! This must not be music of any kind! What if I lose my IPod? WE ALL NEED TO GO BACK TO THOSE EDISON CYLINDERS!!!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9282069bedd5056a51b95</guid>
				<title>Bob Longmire</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 14:27:28 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9282069bedd5056a51b95</link>
				<description>If one falls out of bed they hit the floor. BTC is trading at 600-700 USD and you think it &quot;Completely Crashed?!?&quot;
We hear this all the time from central bankers, Visa processors and their dupes. As if talking it down will suppress it. 
Mt Gox has problems that will be barely a ripple (pun intended) for the long term value.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9281aeab8eab205d15ccf</guid>
				<title>Bob Longmire</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 14:27:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f9281aeab8eab205d15ccf</link>
				<description>If one falls out of bed they hit the floor. BTC is trading at 600-700 USD and you think it &quot;Completely Crashed?!?&quot;
We hear this all the time from central bankers, Visa processors and their dupes. As if talking it down will suppress it. 
Mt Gox has problems that will be barely a ripple (pun intended) for the long term value.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ffae6da811f97b092e40</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 11:34:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ffae6da811f97b092e40</link>
				<description>&quot;If you can't touch it, you don't own it.&quot; - Can you touch the euros on your bank account? (or rubles, or dollars, or whatever virtual play money your particular bank uses)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ff0f6da811d374092e40</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 11:32:15 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ff0f6da811d374092e40</link>
				<description>Mining? What are you talking about. Mining is for geeks and nerds. I don't mine. Don't need to. I simply buy my bitcoins, or offer products and services and let people pay me directly in bitcoins. 
 
So all that crap about power generators does not apply. Dedicated L3 connection, again what are you talking about? Any common household internet connection will do just fine, thank you. 
 
As for business or people in Moldova or Ukraine or whatever bogus places you come up with, well if you *insist* on doing business with them, by all means go ahead. I know I won't. I simply buy my bitcoins at established, verified companies in my own country, who fall under jurisdiction and legislation like any proper business. 
 
I've had exactly ZERO issues in all these years. 
 
Now, tell me again, what costs am I omitting, exactly? 
 
Oh and as for the inventor being anonymous. Do you know who invented gold, and if not, does that make it dubious or worthless?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8fd8ceab8ea2a70092e40</guid>
				<title>Brick</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 11:25:48 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8fd8ceab8ea2a70092e40</link>
				<description>This problem has been known for over two years. It is a problem easily solved by programming code on the side of the third party server. Bitcoin programming experts such as Andreas M. Antonopoulos have publicly called out bugs in Mt. Gox's code and said it was a system not meant to handle high volume trading. In other words, Mt. Gox called out a problem not well known to scare the public to hide the fact that they ran a horrible exchange. Unless something further will be revealed this isn't really news.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8fb596da811fb5a092e44</guid>
				<title>Luke-Jr</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 11:16:25 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8fb596da811fb5a092e44</link>
				<description>This PR, while literally true, is mostly FUD in its wording. The &quot;issue&quot; has been known for years, and ignored because it doesn't pose a threat to properly implemented services. The only exploit here is in MtGox's poor handling of withdrawl transactions.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8fa56ecad04c73e092e40</guid>
				<title>CoinHeavy</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 11:12:06 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8fa56ecad04c73e092e40</link>
				<description>According to their latest press release:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mtgox.com/press_release_20140210.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://www.mtgox.com/press_release_20140210.html&lt;/a&gt;
The issue has to do with transactional malleability and it is a technical issue particular to their implementation of the bitcoin code.
&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Transaction_Malleability&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Transaction_Malleability&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/1xieb9/keep_calm_transaction_malleability_is_not_double/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/1xieb9/keep_calm_transaction_malleability_is_not_double/&lt;/a&gt;

There was a panic right after they released the announcement. A single large sell order executed on one other exchange for ~3000 BTC at ~100 USD per. Otherwise, trading was in a band of 600-650 just after the announcement (already back to 680 at time of writing).

Follow the fun here:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=458074.140&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=458074.140&lt;/a&gt;

A few shekels, if you please! 1HvX7axkQM7XqWGgXaG8jq4kKJFMWGxnJY</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8f62969beddea0d092e4b</guid>
				<title>Doug in Virginia</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 10:54:17 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8f62969beddea0d092e4b</link>
				<description>Many of the systems you describe predate the Internet and have no dependence on it. (All except Paypal.) But I can see you're not really that interested in precision or facts.

Bitcoin is critically dependent on third parties to validate the block chain, which doesn't occur instantly. Again, you're not that interested in facts.

Bitcoin is primarily a way to securely exchange answers to math problems. Any purported value as a payment system is critically dependent on a number of other things, including the acceptance of those math problem answers as &quot;payment.&quot; And that is woefully limited, particularly in the absence of exchanges. Which would be yet more third parties.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8f4236bb3f76615092e40</guid>
				<title>biff</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 10:45:39 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8f4236bb3f76615092e40</link>
				<description>Oh, you Bitchcoiners--Kashmir--Bitchoiners pay plenty for their transactions, just not directly at the point of sale. if you are a Bitchcoin miner, you have to pay for the initial investment in computer hardware. Then you have to pay for electricity, redundancy (back-up power and generators), your ISP (I would be satisfied with nothing less than a Level III -type closed loop LAN system dedicated solely to MY network for extra cost of course), and continually upgrade your hardware. Not cheap since a basic set-up unit will run you $5K-$6K at minimum, the cheapest generators run about $600.00, and a dedicated T1 line (provided you don't want to build your own fiber networks) starts at about $300/month. 

Then there is the trouble of tracking down the &quot;owner&quot; of an exchange and getting the cash they promised you, but never paid. How exactly do you do that? In the US, if a bank stiffs you, you have a legal recourse; do you have ANY rights to go after a transmitter of faux money for taking your real money and giving you nothing in return? What if they live in Moldava? Ukraine? Vanuatu? China? Good luck tracking down any authorities, civil or criminal, who will give a shit about the real money you spent to buy fake money because it sounded like a good investment at the time. 

Kashnmir, you are omitting all the costs and work YOU must take on to cut out the banks and trade in your new &quot;store of value&quot;. Bitchcoins are not free, just like the veggies you grow in your backyard are not &quot;free&quot; nor are the cookies you make to sell at a church social. They cost money and they cost you just as much, if not more than using a bank to send money. For less security. And no way to lawfully recoup even if you're lucky enough to ever find a thief in your &quot;anonymous&quot; network. 

Bitchcoins are the Beanie Babies, &quot;vintage&quot; baseball cards, and Cabbage Patch dolls of today. They are dubious stores of value that look utterly ridiculous in hindsight. The only thing valuable about Bitchcoins might be the first computer used to mine Bitchcoins (as a collection of pieces intended to show the anachronisms of an era)--even that will be dubious as the inventor is &quot;anonymous&quot; and therefore can never very his or her claim that their machine was the first step on the systematic fleecing of libertarian nerds and geeks.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8edab69bedd5975092e40</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 10:18:03 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8edab69bedd5975092e40</link>
				<description>@Doug in Virginia: I'm saying *all* of these systems require internet. On top of that, the other ones (except Bitcoin) *also* require all sorts of other prerequisites, trust, dependencies, 3rd parties, etc. 
 
Serisouly, I don't see how people keep ignoring or even denying the HUGE advantages of a payment system that is world wide, instant, virtually free, open source, fully transparent yet secure, independent of any administrators or authorities, doesn't require any 3rd parties, transactions cannot be blocked, no accounts that can be frozen (in fact you don't need to register an account anywhere or with anyone), can process online payments within 1 second, and is suitable for micro-payments as well as huge sums. 
 
If people don't consider that a big improvement upon banks or credit cards or paypal, I don't know what will.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ec9e69bedd5870d72efb</guid>
				<title>phillip.wooten.5</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 10:13:34 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ec9e69bedd5870d72efb</link>
				<description>Agree, people looking for a get-rich-quick scheme are about to get scammed, cyber currencies are a fake - you need real money to buy it, then you might not get your real money back - or, if the &quot;Bitcoin&quot; goes down in &quot;value&quot; (which is generated out of thin air), you'll get less. Bitcoins is a payment-system software, nothing more - no backing, no insurance - nothing but a software program. Invest at your own risk.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e98769bedd195fd72f01</guid>
				<title>Doug in Virginia</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 10:00:23 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e98769bedd195fd72f01</link>
				<description>Anonymous posters better with other anonymous posters, and then trying to collect.

What could possibly go wrong with that?

Maybe you could just post your bitcoin address.

Mine's 1933phfhK3ZgFQNLGSDXvqCn32k2buXY8a</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e92beab8ea99271190f9</guid>
				<title>ScottyB</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 09:58:51 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e92beab8ea99271190f9</link>
				<description>yawn this site is BORING</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e66decad04057b1190f9</guid>
				<title>tmgotech</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 09:47:09 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e66decad04057b1190f9</link>
				<description>Maybe they can pay you in BTC :)

AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e15aeab8ea2d0211910f</guid>
				<title>Doug in Virginia</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 09:25:30 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e15aeab8ea2d0211910f</link>
				<description>Unless you bought at, say, $800 last week.

Then $670 would be less good.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e1096bb3f75a501190fd</guid>
				<title>Doug in Virginia</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 09:24:09 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8e1096bb3f75a501190fd</link>
				<description>Your comment about payment system dependence &quot;the internet&quot; is not literally true, but that's a quibble. The broader point is that you can't bash other systems because they depend on preconditions, and then ignore the same for Bitcoin.

You need availability to validate transactions. If you don't have any connectivity, which is the case for much of the globe in developing economies, then the fact that you only needed it for a short duration is small comfort.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ded3eab8ea2f021190fb</guid>
				<title>Again?</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 09:14:43 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ded3eab8ea2f021190fb</link>
				<description>How many times has bitcoin &quot;collapsed&quot;, &quot;cratered&quot;, &quot;crashed&quot;, &quot;imploded&quot;, etc, etc? And yet, yet, there it is still trading around USD630 on the reliable exchanges. Mt. Gox, although large, has been increasingly irrelevant for a while. And they made a mistake in coding their exchange system when they failed to account for the malleability of TXIDs. Other exchanges did not.

So end of bitcoin yet again. Orly.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d714ecad045e471190fb</guid>
				<title>mje</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 08:41:40 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d714ecad045e471190fb</link>
				<description>Quick call GATA, to demand the arrest of the Free Masons, the Buildberg Group and Illuminati. They must have sabotaged Bitcoin...the new new fad that will replace the funny money printed the by Creature from Jecklyll Island.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d5c86bb3f7932a119102</guid>
				<title>bitjedi</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 08:36:08 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d5c86bb3f7932a119102</link>
				<description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/1x93tf/some_irc_chatter_about_what_is_going_on_at_mtgox/cf99yac&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/1x93tf/some_irc_chatter_about_what_is_going_on_at_mtgox/cf99yac&lt;/a&gt;

This is the comment that the Bitcoin Dev posted 3 days ago indicating what Mt. Gox's issue is. Gox basically rewrote their own wallet software which was less flexible in handling the known exceptions on the Bitcoin protocol. If Gox ran Bitcoind / BItcoin-qt instead (yes it doesn't scale for their volume but that's a different story) the tx-id problem would not be an issue. Gox just made some bad assumptions.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d5b969beddb219d72efe</guid>
				<title>itsme</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 08:35:53 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d5b969beddb219d72efe</link>
				<description>Feels like the music have stopped on the bitcoin titanic.
Ponzi's always end in crash and burn.
This time it's NOT different...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d40f69beddfb0dd72f01</guid>
				<title>jaymes.watts</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 08:28:47 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d40f69beddfb0dd72f01</link>
				<description>Joe &quot;TOPTICK Weisenthal, the authority on bitcoin</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d3bbeab8ea2d551190ff</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 08:27:23 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d3bbeab8ea2d551190ff</link>
				<description>You do realize that banking, wire transfers, credit card payments, paypal, are all 100% dependent on internet, right?

As for &quot;continuously available&quot;: no, not for Bitcoin. You only need a second of internet connection to send a payment or check your current balance. Just like banking, wire transfers, credit card payments, paypal (although Bitcon is way faster and more efficient).</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d1dfecad0472341190fc</guid>
				<title>btcisajokeisgay</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 08:19:27 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d1dfecad0472341190fc</link>
				<description>You create the account just to bash btc? You are a shill.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d13fecad043b2a1190fe</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 08:16:47 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8d13fecad043b2a1190fe</link>
				<description>Gee, I wonder... Would it be Bitcoin's fault, or MtGox's?
Hint: &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/edOnkZ2.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://i.imgur.com/edOnkZ2.jpg&lt;/a&gt; :)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8cfb46da8114460d72f03</guid>
				<title>Doug in Virginia</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 08:10:12 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8cfb46da8114460d72f03</link>
				<description>I don't think you can tout the broad global availability of something that depends on a continuously available Internet to validate transactions.

And, of course, 99% of the world has no idea what Bitcoin is, something like that.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8cb0969beddfa61d72f00</guid>
				<title>Good Luck</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 07:50:17 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8cb0969beddfa61d72f00</link>
				<description>&quot;And double spending is not possible unless an exchange is irresponsible.&quot;

Maybe it was double selling. And the other seller was MtGox.

People who bought bitcoins from MtGox will have their bitcoin transaction cancelled but not the corresponding dollar transaction. That's the difference between a virtual currency and a real one.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c9db69bedd5e5fd72f03</guid>
				<title>Holly Hedgehog</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 07:45:15 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c9db69bedd5e5fd72f03</link>
				<description>I am a completely fascinated by Bitcoin. I think the technology is a huge breakthrough in transferring money over the internet. It is certainly being used as a currency on a usefull level, because volatility is only a problem in relation to time and with computers being very fast these days, transactions can be made in timespan that negates the negative effects.

However, I still agree with pretty much everything you said. There are still major risks involved. Even the part where you don't really own it. It is intellectual property.... only when you are able to create a transaction in exchange for value, can the ownership retroactively be attributed to you.

However, that said... MtGox is technically incompetent and are flat out misleading people to believe that there is a flaw in Bitcoin. They made a mistake in implementing the protocol and now they are blaming the technology instead of their own understanding. They should never have used the transaction-id as a unique identification in they way they did. &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/edOnkZ2.jpg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://i.imgur.com/edOnkZ2.jpg&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c917eab8eafe2e1190f9</guid>
				<title>BitcoinRat</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 07:41:59 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c917eab8eafe2e1190f9</link>
				<description>.
It's so sad to see yet another 'obituary to bitcoin' article , based on a dubious &quot;explanation' from Mt Gox.
this so-called 'code glitch' has been successfully addressed within the community since 2011. Sadly it was Mt Gox's own wallet system that caused the errors ( that were not verified by other nodes on the chain, thus disrupting their exchange.) This is not an issue with the blockchain itself but lies within the management of one exchange. 

as the infrastructure of the Bitcoin Community grows ; more exchanges will come on stream and the community will not forget this statement from Mt Gox.

So , as the phrase goes .. Bitcoin is Dead; Long live Bitcoin ! 
.
.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c6ad6bb3f7ad6f1190fd</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 07:31:41 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c6ad6bb3f7ad6f1190fd</link>
				<description>Bank transactions, are you kidding? 
 
I said world wide, instantly, and virtually free of charges. 
 
For starters, almost half the world doesn't even have access to a normal banking infrastructure. 
 
Here within West Europe, the banking system works somewhat reasonable (although still far behind Bitcoin). In the U.S. it's already worse, and in the rest of the world it's mostly utter crap or nonexistent. 
 
Credit cards and paypal: same story, and don't forget about their *ridiculous* fees. 
 
Anyway, apparently you're see hooked to your traditional banking system, you won't see the advantages of a decentralized world wide open source alternative, no matter what. Well, enjoy sir, while I hop on the train to the future.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c61069bedd5559d72f00</guid>
				<title>Ben Nash</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 07:29:04 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c61069bedd5559d72f00</link>
				<description>So this so called bug is not new. In fact its been an improving situation for 3+ years now. And double spending is not possible unless an exchange is irresponsible. MtGox is just now learning this. That is the real story here &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/1xieb9/keep_calm_transaction_malleability_is_not_double/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/1xieb9/keep_calm_transaction_malleability_is_not_double/&lt;/a&gt; 
Shame on MtGox.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c4aa6bb3f784731190f9</guid>
				<title>Dean Wormer</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 07:23:06 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c4aa6bb3f784731190f9</link>
				<description>Blah Blah Blah. this is how all ponzis end. withdrawals exceed deposits.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c2da69beddc650d72efb</guid>
				<title>barbacoa</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 07:15:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8c2da69beddc650d72efb</link>
				<description>Bank transactions don't always take a day. Only when the potential exists for fraud. I transfer money to people all the time. I receive money from people all the time. If these are routine transfers, they are instantaneous. In the event they aren't they receive added scrutiny, to preclude fraud and error. If I am transferring a large sum of money in a transaction (e.g., purchasing a house), I damn sure want people involved to ensure the money goes to the correct place. And if it goes to the wrong place, I want the ability to correct that. So in other words, I want the ability to prevent mistakes, or rectify them if they occur. That can't be done when total anonymity exists. So you are cursed to living in a zero fault tolerant system where your money can just disappear down some rathole if a transaction goes wrong.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8be36eab8eaa9021190fa</guid>
				<title>Mt Gox closing</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:55:34 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8be36eab8eaa9021190fa</link>
				<description>&quot;but it's just a mistake on their eind&quot;

Maybe it's just their planned coverup. Their money was confiscated and the false confirmation trick could have been used to keep the trading going on when they needed real cash by double selling bitcoins. Now they are closing the exchange using the same trick and blaming &quot;outsiders&quot;.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8bcb26bb3f71f4b119100</guid>
				<title>Ben Nash</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:49:06 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8bcb26bb3f71f4b119100</link>
				<description>I see $670 on Coinbase. All is good</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8bc4d6bb3f7474c1190fc</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:47:25 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8bc4d6bb3f7474c1190fc</link>
				<description>Educate yourself and read into Bitcoin before spreading F.U.D. please. 
 
You can manually set any transaction fee you want (or even none) with Bitcoin transactions. I set my wallet to use something like 0.01 mBTC or 0.005 mBTC transaction fees. That's less than a tenth of a dollar cent per transaction. They always get processed immediately. 
 
Even just the time you have to wait before your bank wire transfer gets processed is already WAY more expensive. 
 
Bank wire transfer = just sending some bits from one server to another. Yet they claim this takes &quot;at least one business day&quot; (meanwhile harvesting your interest, of course). Really, that's just pathetic.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8bac86da811b871d72efb</guid>
				<title>Somer Tupmak</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:40:56 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8bac86da811b871d72efb</link>
				<description>Check your chart again.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8baa069bedda432d72efb</guid>
				<title>Ben Nash</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:40:16 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8baa069bedda432d72efb</link>
				<description>Hey haters, do you own any Bitcoin? Or are you speculating from the outside? In the mean time most investors are salivating at the momentary lower price. Time to buy!!!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ba22ecad041a5e1190f9</guid>
				<title>BTC_is_a_joke</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:38:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8ba22ecad041a5e1190f9</link>
				<description>Well, well, well. It looks like I've been right all along. Bitcoin will never return to 1000, and you fools who are holding are idiots. At the beginning of 2013 bitcoin was trading for $13...hmmmm, why does everyone think that bitcoin is going up forever? People are greedy, and generally stupid. Bitcoin, the puuuurfect modern scam.

Get out while you can kiddos, its over.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b97a6da8114b61d72efc</guid>
				<title>BTC_is_a_joke</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:35:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b97a6da8114b61d72efc</link>
				<description>No. Ponzi scheme.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b95b6da811d061d72efb</guid>
				<title>BTC_is_a_joke</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:34:51 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b95b6da811d061d72efb</link>
				<description>Stop lying! You bitcoiners always say that transferring bitcoins is &quot;vitually free&quot; when in reality it is MORE expensive than any debit card transaction and MORE expensive than any bank wire. Bitcoin fees, bid/ask spreads, exchange fees...bitcoin is a ripoff that says its FREE...you lying sacks.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b76aeab8eaa96e1190f9</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:26:34 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b76aeab8eaa96e1190f9</link>
				<description>Oh really? Many ways to transfer money world wide, instantly, virtually free of charge? Do tell please.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b73069beddc21fd72efd</guid>
				<title>Steve G</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:25:36 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b73069beddc21fd72efd</link>
				<description>Capitulation</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b6fdeab8ea076f119101</guid>
				<title>Kazimir</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:24:45 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b6fdeab8ea076f119101</link>
				<description>MtGox claim there is a vulnerability in Bitcoin, but it's just a mistake on their eind. They verify transactions by awaiting confirmation for a specific tx ID, rather than just waiting for a confirmation of the address receiving the coins (no matter through what tx).</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b5beeab8ea1a6e1190f9</guid>
				<title>barbacoa</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:19:26 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b5beeab8ea1a6e1190f9</link>
				<description>There are many ways to transfer money at low cost. So I still haven't seen any advantage to using bitcoin, or any other cryptocurrency, unless one is seeking to purchase illegal substances or services. It appears to be inherently zero fault tolerant, and will remain so as long as complete anonymity is maintained. Currently, you are depending upon anonymous parties to act as honest brokers in the transaction. That being the case, there is always going to be an incentive for theft, including counterfeiting (anonymity also ensures the guilty are never punished).</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b5366da811ab46d72efe</guid>
				<title>Goodtimes Jerry</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 06:17:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52f8b5366da811ab46d72efe</link>
				<description>The conclusion was misleading... here's a realistic conclusion:

- Bitcoin is not yet a currency, it's a speculative digital hypothetical form of money designed for gamblers, high-end programmers and other speculative traders.
- Bitcoin is not a way to preserve or protect your wealth
- Bitcoin is not a hedge against fiat currencies
- Bitcoin is very volatile, more volatile than your average stock and much more volatile than a mutual fund

And lastly,

If you can't touch it, you don't own it.</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

