http://www.businessinsider.com/is-bitcoin-money-2013-4/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Wed, 23 Jul 2014 18:27:03 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: web2 (via varnish3)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 26689
X-Varnish: 892905414
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 54.91.135.161
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>What The Rise Of Bitcoin Teaches Us About Money</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/is-bitcoin-money-2013-4/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 14:27:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Cullen Roche</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515e79fe69bedd883f000006</guid>
				<title>reallly</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 03:15:10 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515e79fe69bedd883f000006</link>
				<description>How do is the bitcoin system protected for counterfit bitcoins?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515c27e769bedd4d62000001</guid>
				<title>from india</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 09:00:23 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515c27e769bedd4d62000001</link>
				<description>how does this prevent the computer or who ever controls the computer to tweak the money supply in his / her favour or interests? yea yea the govt may do it..all accept that.. but we dont think we would like individuals or corporations to control 'money supply'. the current money supply process itself is so confusing and convoluted to the common man. This thingy is worse and you never know it may be blindly accepted due to peer social pressure. The creators of Bitcoin will never need to mine for it as they will steal from the honeypot one way or the other.. u are replacing the government with something more sinister</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515a878cecad04376c000051</guid>
				<title>Utuxia Cons</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 03:23:56 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515a878cecad04376c000051</link>
				<description>Great article. Thanks for doing the research into bitcoin before you hypothesize about it. This is one of the best articles I've read about bitcoin lately, most articles the author doesn't even understand it. You share some of the same concerns as a lot of people -- if it does become popular enough it will be outlawed, much like p2p file sharing has become.

Its not only used for criminal activity, although that was a lot of its appeal in the beginning. Not having to be subject to rules and regulations has its benefits. Ultimately its up to the individual what they choose to do with their bitcoin. If it does take off, which it certainly looks that way judging from the past 2 months, then this could be the next big thing since the Internet went mainstream 15 years ago.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515a4a5c69bedd252f000006</guid>
				<title>Michael Hardy</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 23:02:52 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515a4a5c69bedd252f000006</link>
				<description>It inevitably competes with the present banking system, but is it not possible that banks themselves want to get in on it? I've seen some hints of this on the web.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515a1aaaecad04ef71000005</guid>
				<title>ErikVoorhees</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 19:39:22 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515a1aaaecad04ef71000005</link>
				<description>1) Bank-issued currency has counter party risk (the bank). Bitcoin does not. This is unprecedented.
2) Walmart could double it's profit margin from online sales by removing the 2.9% merchant fee they pay on every transaction to Visa/MasterCard. We'll see how long it takes them to realize this.
3) You just said Bitcoin's value comes from the inability to regulate it. So government makes it &quot;illegal&quot;... See the value now?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515a01e5eab8eaf271000019</guid>
				<title>Satoshi</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 17:53:41 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515a01e5eab8eaf271000019</link>
				<description>Bitcoin will never be regulated.
You can not regulate nor destroy Bitcoin - similar to BitTorrent.
It will exist as the Internet exists.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159e598ecad04d120000009</guid>
				<title>Anne Arquiste</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 15:52:56 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159e598ecad04d120000009</link>
				<description>None Shall Question America and it's System of Mighty Banks!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159d98469beddef51000007</guid>
				<title>Frank Koster</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 15:01:24 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159d98469beddef51000007</link>
				<description>Only the owner of the bitcoin can see its transaction.
If you dont understand bitcoin dont use it.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159c7aa6bb3f79159000011</guid>
				<title>Frank Koster</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 13:45:14 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159c7aa6bb3f79159000011</link>
				<description>Non sense
1 No law has ever stoped a market price , look at ilicite drugs.
2 Bitcoin is decentralised even shutting down the us internet will not help.
3 monney talks , this means when bitcoin is forbidden in the us comany will move to places were they can use it freely.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159a090ecad04841d000002</guid>
				<title>Kiril Gantchev</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 10:58:24 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159a090ecad04841d000002</link>
				<description>1. Bitcoins IS something new as it is the first decentralized currency that we've ever encountered.
2. The more people have Bitcoins the more reasons for WalMart accept it and that's not even considering all the other benefits of Bitcoin.
3. Sure they can make it illegal like they made torrents illegal, but torrents haven't seen a decline in use: there are PLENTY of people to sustain the Bitcoin system and those who don't use it will find themselves at a great competitive disadvantage. The best example is the Clipper Chip in 1993, look it up to see how the government failed to control encryption.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51599ff36bb3f73f11000009</guid>
				<title>Vlak</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 10:55:47 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51599ff36bb3f73f11000009</link>
				<description>Though if someday Bitcoin's market cap eclipses the USD, Wal-mart will simply stop being a business if they don't accept a currency everyone else does.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515997466bb3f7cd7f00000f</guid>
				<title>ThinkingFactual</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 10:18:46 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515997466bb3f7cd7f00000f</link>
				<description>1. Bitcoin is better. It is not run by a bank that gambles with depositor funds

2. Walmart will do anything to make more profits. Just like any other multinational company. 

3. Bitcoin is peer-2-peer and cannot be killed by any single government. It is part of the internet and you would literally have to shut down the entire internet to stop the transactions.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51599716ecad04540b000001</guid>
				<title>&lt;&lt;</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 10:17:58 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51599716ecad04540b000001</link>
				<description>&quot;I won’t get into the way the Bitcoin money supply is automated because the computer based growth is WAY over my head&quot;

If you can't explain it then your article is useless and I don't trust it more than a piece of advertising!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159964969bedd3e1e000001</guid>
				<title>GollyGee</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 10:14:33 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159964969bedd3e1e000001</link>
				<description>please enlighten the world to your revelations, insights, and logic. 

anonymous Blog posts without any supporting information is useless.

Thank you.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515990dd6bb3f75a70000026</guid>
				<title>FactualThinking</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 09:51:25 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515990dd6bb3f75a70000026</link>
				<description>1) BitCoins is nothing new. Pre-Civil War many US Banks printed their own version of money.
2) BitCoins main value is as unregulated money for illegal activity. WalMart will never accept it because it has no reason to.
3) BitCoins will become illegal if it becomes too popular.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51598cececad04d87500000a</guid>
				<title>skintnick</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 09:34:36 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51598cececad04d87500000a</link>
				<description>This analysis is contained well and truly by &quot;the box.&quot;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515988e7eab8eafb3d00001f</guid>
				<title>TightTransport</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 09:17:27 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515988e7eab8eafb3d00001f</link>
				<description>It is best to hedge yourself in many markets and economies. 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitbillions.com?refid=1JLb2hrECqSMfNhM32cskCqCUvkufK1bp5&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.bitbillions.com?refid=1JLb2hrECqSMfNhM32cskCqCUvkufK1bp5&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515981f669bedd0561000029</guid>
				<title>Maarten</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 08:47:50 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515981f669bedd0561000029</link>
				<description>One aspect of Bitcoin that few seem to understand is that all your account details are public. Not just the amount of Bitcoins you own, but all your past transactions as well. This means that collecting taxes on transactions can potentially be a lot easier than it is for cash. I think the government will love this system!
&lt;a href=&quot;http://ecurrency-news.com/2013/03/31/why-the-talk-about-e-currencies-being-outlawed-is-fud/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://ecurrency-news.com/2013/03/31/why-the-talk-about-e-currencies-being-outlawed-is-fud/&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515981426bb3f7bd55000010</guid>
				<title>A S Fries</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 08:44:50 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515981426bb3f7bd55000010</link>
				<description>One flaw in argument: why can't the US Government tax Bitcoin earnings?
If they want to, they can.
And they too can happily accept Bitcoin payments for people's Bitcoin-denominated earnings.
Should they want to, of course.
But a rather powerful lobby, whose members do quite well off of the charges they levy for using US dollars, would fight against that, tooth and nail. 
Maybe the US Govt wouldn't acknowledge Bitcoin as legal tender, after all...
:)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159809b69bedd2b5e000017</guid>
				<title>adegiulio</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 08:42:03 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159809b69bedd2b5e000017</link>
				<description>These people have no idea what bitcoin is, how it works, or why it's useful.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597eafecad040257000012</guid>
				<title>Ben Nash</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 08:33:51 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597eafecad040257000012</link>
				<description>You are assuming someone would trade bitcoins for dollars. This is not needed to enjoy the value of bitcoins. You can enjoy the value of bitcoins without anyone knowing. Yes, Exchanges trading bitcoins-to-USD can be taxed like today's exchanges. But why would we ever want dollars in a bitcoin economy?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597e6decad040157000014</guid>
				<title>Milly Bitcoin</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 08:32:45 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597e6decad040157000014</link>
				<description>Wrong on both counts. The Bitcoin transactions are on the personal computers of everyone running the software, not some centralized server hence the term &quot;Vires In Numeris&quot; or &quot;strength in numbers.&quot; US currency is not backed by gold, it is backed by decree of the US government which is why it is called fiat. The comparison is that you have many individuals setting the rules via the software they run on their computer vs. the politicians and federal reserve in Washington. Which do you trust more?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597d4969bedd445500000e</guid>
				<title>Milly Bitcoin</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 08:27:53 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597d4969bedd445500000e</link>
				<description>But Bitcoin is not an investment products. You can use Bitcoin to transfer money and make payments without holding it or investing in it. Investing is a side issue, not the primary purpose so you are comparing apples and oranges.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597c1d69bedd125200000d</guid>
				<title>Milly Bitcoin</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 08:22:53 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597c1d69bedd125200000d</link>
				<description>Greta article but I don't see how it would be possible to make accepting Bitcoin illegal. Bitcoin itself cannot be intrinsically illegal because it is just a software program and a ledger database. I don't see how a law could single out one form of barter while allowing other types.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597b7469bedd504f000008</guid>
				<title>BitcoinThai</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 08:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51597b7469bedd504f000008</link>
				<description>I don't see any issue with regards to taxes and Bitcoin. The only difference would be that the government would not be able reach their hand into your bank account and helps themselves to taxes. And I would think the large majority of taxes are not collected in that manner, and collected by people voluntarily paying the correct amount.

As for Trust; the current regulated systems really allows people to think they can throw their money all over the place and feel like it's some else's job to make sure they don't get cheated. With Bitcoin it would put a lot more responsibility back onto the spender to make sure they are dealing with trustworthy people. Is the average person ready for that kind of responsibility; I'm not sure, but we'll find out.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159768decad04a24700003c</guid>
				<title>Frank Koster</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 07:59:09 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159768decad04a24700003c</link>
				<description>Its the opposide of a pizy scheme ,, :)

It's a giant ponzi scheme

In a Ponzi Scheme, the founders persuade investors that they’ll profit. Bitcoin does not make such a guarantee. There is no central entity, just individuals building an economy.

A ponzi scheme is a zero sum game. In a ponzi scheme, early adopters can only profit at the expense of late adopters, and the late adopters always lose. Bitcoin has an expected win-win outcome. Early and present adopters profit from the rise in value as Bitcoins become better understood and in turn demanded by the public at large. All adopters benefit from the usefulness of a reliable and widely-accepted decentralized peer-to-peer currency. 

&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Myths#It.27s_a_giant_ponzi_scheme&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Myths#It.27s_a_giant_ponzi_scheme&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596d48eab8eae67800001a</guid>
				<title>Frank Koster</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 07:19:36 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596d48eab8eae67800001a</link>
				<description>Market can not be stoped by laws.
look at the valuu of ilicite drugs , warez , etc..
Iprohibition of alcohol was canceled for this reason.
Comanys will sertanly leave the US if they can not make mony there.
and do no langer want to beasociated with the us instead of bitcoin.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596be469beddf72a000016</guid>
				<title>HELL YES IS MONEY</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 07:13:40 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596be469beddf72a000016</link>
				<description>.....as long as the internet is up that is . With world governments getting ready to pass bills that will allow banks to cover their fuckups with depositors money, more and more people will turn to this. This is not only in Cyprus or Europe. Canada is liking the idea

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.globalresearch.ca/depositor-haircuts-spreading-canada-endorses-cypriot-financial-harshness-ottawas-proposed-bail-in-regime-for-important-banks/5329175&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.globalresearch.ca/depositor-haircuts-spreading-canada-endorses-cypriot-financial-harshness-ottawas-proposed-bail-in-regime-for-important-banks/5329175&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596a7469bedd8f25000010</guid>
				<title>itsme</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 07:07:32 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596a7469bedd8f25000010</link>
				<description>How can the power that be not embrace Bitcoin...
It's the same as fiat money, created out of nothing, just dumb confidence in the system.
Until the system crumble on the believers...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596a41eab8ea1b76000021</guid>
				<title>jamesxxxxxxxx</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 07:06:41 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596a41eab8ea1b76000021</link>
				<description>If Bitcoin is banned in the US it will have dramatic effect on the value of Bitcoin.

Most multinationals do 1/2 their business in the US, they don't want to have anything to do with it.

Besides - why on earth would anyone want to own Bitcoins? Why not use Gold, Euros, Oil, Bananas - they are all less risky than Bitcoin.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515969b069bedd092b000001</guid>
				<title>jamesxxxxxxx</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 07:04:16 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515969b069bedd092b000001</link>
				<description>What 'bitcoin' teaches us - is that people don't understand currency.

There is absolutely no need for bitcoin, it does not make sense that it exists.

Sure - you could say that you wanted a 'hard currency' - not controlled by a central bank - for this we have Gold.

You could say 'I can't wire gold over the Internet' - of course you can't - but you can certainly trade ownership of Gold.

You could argue the banks are idiots and make it too hard to make currency transactions, sure, but they are getting better.

This leaves Bitcoin down to an interesting novelty.

Other than novelty, and some minor bits of pragmatism - can anyone name an actual, hard economic reason for the existence of Bitcoin?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159687beab8ea6d6e000023</guid>
				<title>Frank Koster</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 06:59:07 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159687beab8ea6d6e000023</link>
				<description>If the us would make bitcoin iligal would not have anyu effect.
Reason
1 if this happens $250.000 is no bit deal for bitcoin owners.
2 monny talks , if this monny is bitcoin the dollar will just be droped also by the workers of the fbi.
3 the US is not a island.
4 if you hide your wibsite via the tor network the FBI will not be able to find the shop owner.
good examle is the silkroad (ilicite drug store)
5 aresting poeple for reciving mail is very risky because you can not know what mail you recived and it can noty be proven that you had knolige about the mail you recive.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515967efecad04c62d000014</guid>
				<title>jamesxxxxxxxx</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 06:56:47 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515967efecad04c62d000014</link>
				<description>I don't think you grasped my comment.

'Credibility' is not the technical reliability or 'strength of cryptography' or 'integrity of the payment network' - it's the faith that the real business community has in the currency.

If transactions based on bitcoin are not contractually and commercially enforceable, if there are legal issues or question marks around it's validity as a currency (remember in the US only the Fed is allowed to issue 'currency) then it does not have 'credibility'.

Nobody will want to touch it on any scale.

Also - if it does have a par value then it can definitely be taxed and regulated, it could be considered an asset like any other.

Are you really so naive to think that if you are being paid in Liras, Pounds, Gold, grain, oil, or 'bitcoins' the IRS won't tax you if there is there is tangible asset values?

You could very well start an economy using bananas as currency and the IRS would still tax you in equivalent USD.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515967d2eab8eaa67300001f</guid>
				<title>freipool</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 06:56:18 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515967d2eab8eaa67300001f</link>
				<description>so i mine bitcoin, i sell them for usd, go to the shop and buy bread.
us gov makes it's tax money.
or
yen, aud, rub, ind all converted to bitcoin,
it makes sense for the us gov to make it as easy as possible to allow the conversion of bitcoin back into usd, and you effectively reduce the value of all other currencies in on foul swoop.
which ever gov around the world allows the easiest conversion of bitcoin into there currency will have the upper hand in any currency war. 

bitcoin will be embraced by the powers that be, if it can be used in tool in currency warfare.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596630eab8eaa56700000e</guid>
				<title>itsme</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 06:49:20 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/51596630eab8eaa56700000e</link>
				<description>Bitcoin the new digital... PONZI.
It's that easy.
What do you expect ? haven't you read history books ?
OH, yeah, I get it: THIS TIME IS DIFFERENT, is what you're probably thinking, again...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159603b69bedd9e0c000014</guid>
				<title>jamesxxxxxxxx</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 06:23:55 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/5159603b69bedd9e0c000014</link>
				<description>If bitcoin can be traded at some public par value, then it has monetary correlation, it's an 'asset' can be taxed, regulated without even monetary policy implications.

Also, it's difficult to build real credibility if it can't be held up in commercial courts ... so ... will likely only gai appeal in small terms

Now a GOLD backed digital currency.

*That* would have balls.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515954906bb3f75779000016</guid>
				<title>freedom4citizens</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 05:34:08 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/515954906bb3f75779000016</link>
				<description>The author is incorrect about taxation. A 100% Bitcoin economy still allows for sales taxes to be levied on merchants. This would cut government revenues by 50% or more. Government is too big and needs slashing anyway. Win/win for the public.</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

