http://www.businessinsider.com/here-are-all-the-details-about-the-upcoming-new-york-bitcoin-hearings-2014-1/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Mon, 14 Jul 2014 02:21:47 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: web3 (via varnish3)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 4178
X-Varnish: 197305872
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 54.83.227.138
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>Here Are All The Details About The Upcoming New York Bitcoin Hearings</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/here-are-all-the-details-about-the-upcoming-new-york-bitcoin-hearings-2014-1/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 22:21:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Rob Wile</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d1e9046bb3f7b74f27f199</guid>
				<title>Rassah</title>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 19:59:48 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d1e9046bb3f7b74f27f199</link>
				<description>Rassah from Bicoin100.org here. I've never heard of this &quot;charity.&quot; No other info is given, either. Please don't send any money to that address until RC Fund actually provides supporting information.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d1db3069beddef385890cf</guid>
				<title>blaqfather</title>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 19:00:48 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d1db3069beddef385890cf</link>
				<description>Yes, I think it's time to take at least some steps, to Acknowledge Bitcoin is actually there. Remember please, that the banks will always try to condemn Bitcoin to death, in any way they can, or by any means at their disposal. They are the same banks that are &quot;too big to fail&quot; and tell us that Bitcoin is a &quot; bubble &quot; and that &quot; bubbles &quot; can't happen under their watch.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d15b1e6bb3f71f3d27f1a5</guid>
				<title>PRMan</title>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 09:54:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d15b1e6bb3f71f3d27f1a5</link>
				<description>First, I seriously doubt this is actually a Red Cross bitcoin address. Secondly, since the Red Cross barely gives any money to the causes they specify, I wouldn't donate to them anyway.

Please beware of this address, it is probably enriching a scammer.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d077676da8111168b1392b</guid>
				<title>RC Fund</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 17:42:47 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d077676da8111168b1392b</link>
				<description>PLEASE JOIN US IN OUR EFFORT TO NOT ONLY HELP CHARITY BUT TO SPREAD THE KNOWLEDGE AND HELP THE GROWTH OF BITCOIN: We are now raising funds for the Red Cross' disaster relief branch. All donations, no matter how large or small, are greatly appreciated and will be put to the best use possible. Thank you for your time and kindness. ALL DONATIONS ARE TO BE SENT TO: 13fct3pxxdH67Mn44EvzYJVbHR2w74KcsP</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d03db46da811a8410b643b</guid>
				<title>SS</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 13:36:36 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d03db46da811a8410b643b</link>
				<description>GC to order Jersey switch to bitcoin!!

Breaking News on BI 

Governor Chris Christie though belabored by fussy New York drivers on their way home, &quot;get out of Jersey, if you don't like the traffic,&quot; says the Guv, is, nevertheless, taking measures to lighten the impact of his states finances on the average Jersyian. Switching to bitcoins will allow me to get rid of on average a tenth of a pound of loose change in my pocket, making me tip the scales at a - 0.0001 lbs; a small loss for humanity but a big step for a hungry guy!</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

