http://www.businessinsider.com/chris-dixon-why-silicon-valley-is-obsessed-with-the-bitcoin-2013-4/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Thu, 24 Jul 2014 07:29:55 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: web2 (via varnish3)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 13873
X-Varnish: 912334727
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 54.83.238.48
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>Top Silicon Valley VC: I'm Investing In Bitcoin Startups</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/chris-dixon-why-silicon-valley-is-obsessed-with-the-bitcoin-2013-4/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 03:29:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Alyson Shontell</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517f773cecad04634d00000a</guid>
				<title>4thaugust1932</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 03:48:12 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517f773cecad04634d00000a</link>
				<description>I'm working towards an Independent Nation for 300 million India's Untouchable People.
&lt;a href=&quot;http://rediff.com/news/2007/may/03touch.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://rediff.com/news/2007/may/03touch.htm&lt;/a&gt;
Please send your bitcoin donations to: 18A5He5QooTfyG1sFGq3qFndiBkojBvmm8

And please sign &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com/IndependentNationFor300MillionIndiasUntouchable&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://facebook.com/IndependentNationFor300MillionIndiasUntouchable&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517f7697ecad04cf4e00000a</guid>
				<title>4thaugust1932</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 03:45:27 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517f7697ecad04cf4e00000a</link>
				<description>What's the fastest, cheapest way to send $1000 from America to Ho Chi Minh?
&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hawala&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hawala&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517f7634ecad04314b000004</guid>
				<title>4thaugust1932</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 03:43:48 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517f7634ecad04314b000004</link>
				<description>You can do &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hawala&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hawala&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517f6d45ecad04df3900000c</guid>
				<title>Javan Japeth</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 03:05:41 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517f6d45ecad04df3900000c</link>
				<description>This article doesn't share Chris Dixon's exuberance:

&quot;Should you join the Gold Rush? Bitcoin is the Wild Wild West of finance at the moment. Unless you have lots of guns or a really big posse you might want sit this one out, wait for the gunfire to die down, and the smoke to clear. On the other hand, you might miss this narrow window of opportunity if you don’t act quickly.&quot;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://financesonline.com/the-many-sides-of-bitcoin/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://financesonline.com/the-many-sides-of-bitcoin/&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517ef7a2ecad044563000005</guid>
				<title>Marke T</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 18:43:46 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517ef7a2ecad044563000005</link>
				<description>If you are in the UK, please check this process about how to get BTC with low fees: howtogetbitcoinsuk.blogspot.com</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517eed306bb3f7714c000006</guid>
				<title>Rejerate </title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 17:59:12 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517eed306bb3f7714c000006</link>
				<description>The Silk Road / drug dealers meme is misleading.
It may have been true back in 2011, but today it is a lie.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517eec6369bedd9e7b000026</guid>
				<title>Rejerate</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 17:55:47 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517eec6369bedd9e7b000026</link>
				<description>When Bitcoin becomes easier than fiat,
those who don't accept Bitcoin will simply
crumble to dust, as the consumers will
stop dealing with them. Effortlessly.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517ee74369bedde371000012</guid>
				<title>ErikVoorhees</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 17:33:55 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517ee74369bedde371000012</link>
				<description>What can you do with Bitcoin that you can't do with dollars? This: Send any amount of money anywhere in the world, instantly, with no restriction, and no fee.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517ebbacecad04d571000002</guid>
				<title>KYC</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 14:27:56 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517ebbacecad04d571000002</link>
				<description>KYC is a bitch when most of the business accepting bitcoin are drug dealers. Money laundering charges don't sound so hot but hey it's Silicon Valley where they are special and don't have to follow laws like the rest us.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517eac3f6bb3f7d050000003</guid>
				<title>I'll Try</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 13:22:07 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517eac3f6bb3f7d050000003</link>
				<description>What's the fastest, cheapest way to send $1000 from America to Ho Chi Minh?

If you used your bank, you'd have to physically walk inside of a local bank branch- if you can find one, and they're open during business hours. You'd then need to sign half a dozen forms, prove your identity, and practically give up your first born child before they allow you to, God forbid, send your own money to a friend overseas. If by some miracle you're able to send the money, you'll probably need to pay a $15 wire transfer fee at the minimum, and then wait days and days before your payment clears. Where is the money during this period of time? Maybe you should try calling up your bank's customer support number! That'll surely be a productive conversation.

If you used PayPal, it would probably take days before your payment cleared, and then you wouldn't even be sending the full $1000. PayPal would want at the very least charge a 2.5% fee ($25) and change for your trouble. Furthermore, how are you getting PayPal $1000 in the first place? You need to link your bank account to PayPal, which takes time, or you need to fund your account manually, which also takes time. Even then, PayPal may decide to arbitrarily freeze your money for weeks, assuming you accidentally set off any number of &quot;flags&quot; that would cause PayPal to scrutinize your account or that of your friend.

Now, there's less incentive for you, as a user, to use Bitcoin for domestic transfers. But let's say you're a small business with an online storefront: One does not simply charge credit cards over the Internet. Either you're back to using PayPal for your shopping cart, or you have to sign up for a merchant account, and integrate a payment gateway, and manage the relationship with your merchant account because even Authorize.net will freeze your funds if too much money starts coming in all at once. PayPal has been known to do the same thing.

The bottom line is, money transfers are extremely complicated, especially online transfers, and especially online transfers to people located in other countries. It severely hampers the global marketplace, and Bitcoin disrupts that dynamic in a big way.

The underlying problem is, credit cards were designed for an era before the Internet. Credit cards work well face-to-face, because with a face-to-face interaction, the merchant can know with near certainty whether the user of the credit card is the rightful owner. But on the Internet, the merchant has no way of doing this. This incentivizes credit card fraud and identity theft. Your credit card contains your name, credit card number, CVV, and expiration date; which is nearly everything an identity thief needs to know to use your credit card under your name. Every single time you give up your credit card information to ANY business or retailer, you risk having your identity stolen. This is particularly true online.

I hope you're beginning to see the practical problems with the banking system as it applies to ecommerce and international trade. This is not even considering the ethical and practical issues with fractional reserve banking, or the benefits of using Bitcoin as a hedge against currency and sovereign risk; nor is it considering the benefit to just having an open source global currency that works just as well in Vietnam as it does in the United States. I find almost universally, people don't care about these issues, so I often end up making the pure financial and business case for Bitcoin.

Bitcoin eliminates the risk of identity theft by removing the need to submit your personally identifiable information with your payments. Additionally, Bitcoin payments are instantaneous, and publicly verifiable. For all intents and purposes, whenever a Bitcoin is sent from person A to person B, person B instantly knows he has received person A's Bitcoin. This is in direct contrast to a credit card payment, which doesn't clear for 30 days or more, during which time the payment can be reversed, usually at the merchant's expense. Finally, Bitcoin payments are virtually free of fees, the default fee being 0.0002 BTC in Electrum - which is the easy and secure Bitcoin wallet everyone should be using.

As you can see, online payments are a catastrophe for everyone but the middleman. No matter what happens, the middleman gets paid. Bitcoin removes the middleman, and that's part of what makes it controversial. Bitcoin is anonymous, but so are $100 bills. In any case, most people don't care about their privacy. Bitcoin's most important innovation is removing the middleman. However, the more people realize they don't need banks or PayPal to conduct themselves commercially, the more pressure these middlemen come under to provide actual value to people.

Who knows, maybe Bitcoin will encourage banks to hire better customer service reps.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517ea08669bedd913c000003</guid>
				<title>Bill Carstens</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 12:32:06 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517ea08669bedd913c000003</link>
				<description>We really do need a way to bypass the tax system in the internet world, because it is truly a global market, and should serve no corrupt taxation system. Bitcoin is decentralized and represents true free trade in opposition to the established monopolies, and central banks. We truly need to balance the commercial game, it is drastically top heavy in favor a small elite, this is unsustainable. I truly like bitcoin and even its games etc, because it represents a fair economy. Games like Satoshi Dice, are different than traditional Casinos in that they are provably fair, there's even a game called Bitcoin Prophet that allows you to predict the major indexes in a completely fair manner. Try and get that out of these fee laden brokerages in the traditional investment space.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517e9c8eecad045339000002</guid>
				<title>Open My Mind</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 12:15:10 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517e9c8eecad045339000002</link>
				<description>Open my mind a bit here, if you would: What can you do with Bitcoin tha you can't do with dollars and cents? Is there a place for this in my daily activities?

I understand it as a new currency or as a possible store of value, but how does it translate into more than that? How does it become an industry? 

Won't it be swallowed up by the same houses that process dollar-pound-yen-euro transactions, ie by Wall Street?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517e7df86bb3f7f177000004</guid>
				<title>original insider</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 10:04:40 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/517e7df86bb3f7f177000004</link>
				<description>listening to corrupt silicon valley captains of crony capitalism complain about regulation is more than anyone can stand. wall street is corrupt, he says? silicon valley IS wall street. VCs are in the business of making new securities, not material or lasting innovation -- which is why VC has had such piss poor returns for more than a decade, atomizing dollars from teachers and firefighters pensions, while GPs like Mr Dixon get fabulously wealthy on fees. oh, and wall street is too heavily regulated? what a joke</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

