http://www.businessinsider.com/220-million-sheep-marketplace-bitcoin-theft-chase-2013-12/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Thu, 24 Jul 2014 11:34:04 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: web4 (via varnish2)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 12189
X-Varnish: 1682553611
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 54.196.198.241
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>Two Guys On Reddit Are Chasing A Thief Who Has $220 Million In Bitcoins</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/220-million-sheep-marketplace-bitcoin-theft-chase-2013-12/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 07:34:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Jim Edwards</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52a150a96bb3f7b92f593a9b</guid>
				<title>Rustomen</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 23:20:57 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52a150a96bb3f7b92f593a9b</link>
				<description>I doubt anyone would use their time to read this but if anyone is, thank you. The point of this post is to ask for bitcoin donations. I had 10 btc a year back when one only cost $13 &amp; now i'm sitting here regretting the fact that i no longer have any idea where they are. Spent most of them back then on the &quot;deepweb&quot;, which i ended up being scammed. If anyone is selfless enough to donate as small as a btc or less i'd really appreciate it. Currently trying to make a couple btc's in hope to buy a Bitcoin Miner, unlike most people nowadays, i'm really mining for the fun of it and spreading the word about bitcoin. I love seeing high number of hashing ( Ghash/s ) hence i need a mining device. Please help, &amp; we will keep on spreading the excitement of bitcoin ! And trade without the pain of banking fees. 

Btc Address - 1kymLZJQFrsPwx9g5cnhQujzGE2c4jqSR</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52a041006bb3f7e524db238f</guid>
				<title>A Random German</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 04:01:52 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52a041006bb3f7e524db238f</link>
				<description>One thing I dont get. He has 200million in BTC at current rate. He stole it. He can send and spend money everywhere. He is monitored by a single guy or maybe a bunch of. This money is stolen from criminals so they can not use legal actions etc.

So here is what I would do (just came up while reading this criminal complaining about a criminal):

1. I would determine the rate of 'cashing out' - lets say we are greedy and all we do is cashing for 50k$ per month so we can keep more for our self. That makes 50*12 = 600K per year. That is our loss in operation.
2. Now I would create lets say 1000 wallets and distribute the money evenly. That makes 200k$ in each wallet.
3. Now I would send small fractions randomly from each wallet to random wallets buying stuff for random persons I dont know along the internet.
4. Since all those wallets are random I want to see one non-gov organisation to visit all those people that I brought things in their name and check if those are the thief.

So in the end he is giving away money for free. But this pays him security. Noone can ever watch those people we transfer goods or money too. And if he do it wisely he can pay maybe 25% to 75% for security (throwing it away) and keep the 25% to 75% for himself.

The idea is simply giving those hobby detectives enough to digist (1000ends of randomly choosen wallets that move money to some known wallets of those money or goods for bitcoin sites) and then they need to come up and investigate what real address or bank account is the target destination of the money / goods.

So there is no way that these ciminal maniacs would be able to follow the thief around. And if he sends 0.000666 BTC to track wallets guess what I would do. I would send 0.000666 BTC randomly to 100k accounts and let him track all those, too. There is no way a single person or a bunch of with computers even with large database can pull this off, when the other side has 200million to spend to keep 50million for himself.

Sooner or later they have to lose tracks since its totally insane even if you are building software to track those. Just move around in motels and send goods or money to motels and hotels and while you do it send the same stuff to others so those need to follow every package to just get to you and that is random. And maybe you send yourself nothing at all or to locations you know noone is there.

Or you just use a big shop. If they do not have an insider who can match bitcoin transactions to address the goods are send, I want to see those guys being faster then the package. 

And remember there are those businesses you can use to get things annonymously like renting a bank annonymous account transfer money to it. From it transfer money to another account, close both instantly. A world wide FBI action whould be able to trace the money but three criminals sitting on their computer? Ok... funny.

And guess what I would launder my money and send it to some criminal organisation and they have to think that those are the takers. Have fun with it. Remember we have 150million to lay false tracks and they have nothing then a computer and maybe some dark siders to help.

The next thing I can think of is buying virtual goods. Like pay a software firm to create software I want to have. And this software gets delivered and done. Or even better start a crowd funded non-profit software firm that is creating software for some charity organisations. 

And guess what the biggest donator of the second season (the first is crowedfunded) is yourself donating stolen bitcoin money. You just donate from multiple accounts just like you donate towards greenpeace and the republican party. And the other side is seeing nothing. Remember you just donate lets say 2000$ a month towards your non-profit organisation that covers your life cost and most likely after you delivered your first software to amnesty international and got some news coverage you can just draw in more money and make this a real business.

But in your closet you are just having 1.7 billion in bit coin (it climbed up in the mean time) to full your war on criminals by donating money to random people. Every time you see a heart breaking story of someone needing an operation to save his life or a bunch of doctors helping the african population in their freetime and need some medical equitment, just send money.

I guess this is among the best he can do with the money. Donate to himself along with others to get a living and a career impossible if he would not have stolen it in the first place. See bitcoin raise and also your other peoples money. Do something good (or to please yourself) while you do not profit from it directly so its untraceable.

Maybe he founds his career in founding something like wikipedia but in another sector. Hey the posibilities are endless.

But since both criminals are average criminals without phantasie it might end in this scenario: 
1. Buy a random criminal a new watch and let it send it to him. If he is dead within the next six month ok they still follow the money.
2. Buy another random criminal a hore online and watch what happends.
3. repeat step one to three until they know you are teasing them and they do not kill off the criminals.
4. Raise the bar send more money to more criminals.
5. Laugh at them in your closet and just do not withdraw your money and watch its value grow.
6. Find a way to withdraw the money or profit from it while noone can track you. Once Amazon or Paypal accepts bitcoins I guess it is game over and the theft won.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529fcac1eab8ea586ddb23a1</guid>
				<title>Steve Otis</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 19:37:21 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529fcac1eab8ea586ddb23a1</link>
				<description>Please sign the bitcoin petition that I started today on the White House's We the People website. 

You can sign at the petition at &lt;a href=&quot;http://wh.gov/lkF6o&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://wh.gov/lkF6o&lt;/a&gt;

It says:

&quot;WE PETITION THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION TO:
We petition the Obama administration to expedite SEC clearance for the IPO for the Winklevoss Bitcoin Trust.
The Winklevoss twins (of Facebook fame) are trying to start an ETF that would allow ordinary Americans to invest in bitcoins, as easily as investing in stocks. However, their attempt to do so is bogged down in regulatory inertia. On July 1, 2013, the Winklevoss Bitcoin Trust submitted a S-1 to the Securities Exchange Commission for an IPO. Months later, the SEC has still not given the go-ahead. The Obama Administration should direct the SEC to greatly expedite its processing of IPO requests by bitcoin ETF's, such as the Winklevoss'. The delay by the SEC is inexcusable. In a world in which innovation occurs at lightning speed, the SEC needs to move quickly. Their failure to do so creates a risk that the U.S. will fall behind.&quot;

Reason this is important: A bitcoin ETF is the single fastest way to bring bitcoin to the mainstream.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529fab4d6da8116470db2395</guid>
				<title>Me ...</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 17:23:09 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529fab4d6da8116470db2395</link>
				<description>So Bitcoin is not FTC guaranteed up to 100,000? ; )</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f9b03eab8ea8d0ddb2387</guid>
				<title>Dr. Mario</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 16:13:39 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f9b03eab8ea8d0ddb2387</link>
				<description>This kind of tracking has to be done in real time. As long as no one is consistently monitoring you, you can launder your bitcoins without being tracked.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f982f6da8119e37db2398</guid>
				<title>Aqua Buddha</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 16:01:35 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f982f6da8119e37db2398</link>
				<description>Here we chase the coin not the perp! When they get to the finish the perp will have sold the wallets not the coins in them.

end of story!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f9517ecad049578db2387</guid>
				<title>shoe</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 15:48:23 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f9517ecad049578db2387</link>
				<description>This is getting interesting. It's only a matter of time for the thief. I surmise they will get him in a sting to buy bit coins in person or for art. That's when he'll get nailed as it looks to be his only out.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f950a69bedddb08db2389</guid>
				<title>timmer452000</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 15:48:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f950a69bedddb08db2389</link>
				<description>Seeing how DPR spent some of his bitcoins trying to knock people off might be a good idea to be a little less public about your chase and methods.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f93706da8114b28db2392</guid>
				<title>rp</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 15:41:20 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/529f93706da8114b28db2392</link>
				<description>So the anonymity of bitcoin disappears if when you can track cash in/out movements as I'm sure all governments can?</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

