http://www.reddit.com/user/rjromero/.rss
HTTP/1.0 200 OK
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=UTF-8
Last-Modified: Tue, 08 Jul 2014 21:01:34 GMT
x-frame-options: SAMEORIGIN
x-content-type-options: nosniff
x-xss-protection: 1; mode=block
Vary: accept-encoding
Content-Encoding: gzip
Content-Length: 7717
Server: '; DROP TABLE servertypes; --
Cache-Control: private, must-revalidate, max-age=0
Date: Thu, 10 Jul 2014 20:52:34 GMT
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>overview for rjromero</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/</link><description></description><image><url>http://www.redditstatic.com/reddit.com.header.png</url><title>overview for rjromero</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/</link></image><atom:link rel="self" href="http://www.reddit.com/user/rjromero/.rss" type="application/rss+xml" /><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/worldcup/comments/2a5i6g/match_thread_brazil_vs_germany/cirxt2c</guid><title>rjromero on Match Thread: Brazil vs. Germany</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/worldcup/comments/2a5i6g/match_thread_brazil_vs_germany/cirxt2c</link><dc:date>2014-07-08T21:01:34.072140+00:00</dc:date><description>Exactly this, they reminded me of Spain but with a solid defense.</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/27npb0/which_ad_network_is_this_super_fast_interstitials/ci2owrm</guid><title>rjromero on Which ad network is this? Super fast interstitials.</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/27npb0/which_ad_network_is_this_super_fast_interstitials/ci2owrm</link><dc:date>2014-06-09T03:25:07.844424+00:00</dc:date><description>Yeah that one does say iAd, but I know he uses more than iAd as sometimes when iAd doesn&#39;t supplement an ad a Google Ad is there. But haha it&#39;s alright I was asking about the, interstitial, the main ad on the screen it popups and can be closed by the user. The one that says &amp;quot;Pet Rescue Saga.&amp;quot;</description></item><item><title>Which ad network is this? Super fast interstitials.</title><category>iosdev</category><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/27npb0/which_ad_network_is_this_super_fast_interstitials/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/27npb0/which_ad_network_is_this_super_fast_interstitials/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 00:31:03 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;md&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The interstitials on this ad load incredibly fast. I&amp;#39;ve tried sniffing the traffic from this app but the developer seems to have a looot of useless networking going on (over the most simple drag/tap game) including kiip.me, calls to &amp;quot;AppFireworks,&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Leadbolt.&amp;quot; Kiip seems to be analytics, AppFireworks seems to offer analytics/ads but seems so sketchy and awful at marketing themselevs that I don&amp;#39;t even quite understand what services they offer, and Leadbolt has an advertising program but the signup page is not fully functional and the site is very glitchy lol.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So does anyone know which ad network this is? Quick-loading interstitials that call in more data after tapped on, gray X in top right corner? I&amp;#39;m asking because I&amp;#39;m currently trying out Admob and not only do the interstitials take at least 5-10 seconds to load, but they are completely irrelevant to my category of app. These interstitials load in less than 2-3 (and they aren&amp;#39;t preloaded, Appfireworks/Leadbolt/are called right before it displays) and are pretty relevant to the app I&amp;#39;m playing. (For anyone wondering, this is the Stay in Line app that topped the Free section of the App Store a little over a week ago).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://imgur.com/a/PdrW0&#34;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/PdrW0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; submitted by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/user/rjromero&#34;&gt; rjromero &lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/&#34;&gt; iosdev&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/27npb0/which_ad_network_is_this_super_fast_interstitials/&#34;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/27npb0/which_ad_network_is_this_super_fast_interstitials/"&gt;[3 comments]&lt;/a&gt;</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/277mb5/the_one_take_superhero_movie/chyecb0</guid><title>rjromero on The One Take Superhero Movie</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/277mb5/the_one_take_superhero_movie/chyecb0</link><dc:date>2014-06-03T21:41:50.522041+00:00</dc:date><description>wow how did you know?</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/277mb5/the_one_take_superhero_movie/chye278</guid><title>rjromero on The One Take Superhero Movie</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/277mb5/the_one_take_superhero_movie/chye278</link><dc:date>2014-06-03T21:31:36.215763+00:00</dc:date><description>what is that?</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/277mb5/the_one_take_superhero_movie/chyd8r8</guid><title>rjromero on The One Take Superhero Movie</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/277mb5/the_one_take_superhero_movie/chyd8r8</link><dc:date>2014-06-03T14:02:44.519772-07:00</dc:date><description>dude... You&#39;re still using this joke? Why are you so 2000 and late, Twilight is from 2008.. Literally more than 5 years ago.</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/274tad/swift/chxja48</guid><title>rjromero on Swift</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/274tad/swift/chxja48</link><dc:date>2014-06-02T14:58:15.778523-07:00</dc:date><description>I think Swift will be groundbreaking. The syntax/workflow of Obj-C was pretty clunky/Apple proprietary. Just last night I had to concatenate/insert a lot of values into strings and as I sat there typing [NSString stringWithFormat:@&amp;quot;&amp;quot;] and then forgot the @ sign the first time, and then had some problems where the types were in the wrong order etc... I knew something was going to change. It took nearly 3x longer than what you&#39;d expect from a high level language of today (ActionScript/PHP(ok lol)/JavaScript/Python) where you can just usually type something like &amp;quot;string1&amp;quot; + &amp;quot;string2&amp;quot; + number123 or &amp;quot;string1&amp;quot;.&amp;quot;string2&amp;quot; I&#39;m just excited for the feasibility of porting over code from other languages. As a web developer, I have a lot of games/applications, as well as standard functions and utilities I use universally throughout my programs. With Objective-C, you had to worry about how you would call a function, or, sorry, a method, for so many reasons. Who would send the message, how would it receive it, which arguments to send, would the arguments match up, same-named methods are different methods if they have diff arguments, etc... Just looking at Swift&#39;s documentation on func(tions) and generics made me nearly want to cry. Sure, you can still define primitive types but the language/compiler will handle most of these kind of tedious tasks for you, with functions accepting generic arguments if set up properly. Just this feature alone has made me already begin to download the new xCode so I can start having some fun w/ Swift. And that&#39;s another thing, it&#39;s fun. In Obj-C, you had the clunky interface w/ a bajillion autocomplete for method name and arguments coming up every 2.5 seconds, method declarations were a pain to handle between more than a few implementation files, the whole process just wasn&#39;t fun for me. I wished for a debugger or console to where I could manipulate my code live, but instead I had to wait every time I made a small difference in my code for it to compile and execute. The playground look so fun to write in, and the code looks fun and easy to write. Sure, it&#39;s pretty high-level, and at first you can start by writing funcs that accept generics/lay out the general structure of your application. But as you go back over your code after you simulate it in the playground, you can go back and define types, constants, etc, if you truly want the lowest-level coding solution possible. TLDR: Fun times. Swift looks really powerful. Just look at this: func simpleAssert(condition: @auto_closure () -&amp;gt; Bool, message: String) { if !condition() { println(message) } } let testNumber = 5 simpleAssert(testNumber % 2 == 0, &amp;quot;testNumber isn&#39;t an even number.&amp;quot;) // prints &amp;quot;testNumber isn&#39;t an even number.&amp;quot;</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/274hjo/wwdc_2014_chatreaction_post/chxex62</guid><title>rjromero on WWDC 2014 Chat/Reaction post...</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/274hjo/wwdc_2014_chatreaction_post/chxex62</link><dc:date>2014-06-02T12:30:52.888563-07:00</dc:date><description>says a lot about how poorly WWDC is now misunderstood :/</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/274hjo/wwdc_2014_chatreaction_post/chxepkj</guid><title>rjromero on WWDC 2014 Chat/Reaction post...</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/274hjo/wwdc_2014_chatreaction_post/chxepkj</link><dc:date>2014-06-02T19:23:49.696332+00:00</dc:date><description>What do you mean hybrid app? As in lots of primitive C compacted together throughout code and then called on with Obj C methods?</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/274tj3/apples_new_ios_programming_language_swift/chxek58</guid><title>rjromero on Apples new iOS programming language, Swift.</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/274tj3/apples_new_ios_programming_language_swift/chxek58</link><dc:date>2014-06-02T19:18:56.616352+00:00</dc:date><description>As a dude who knows Obj-C and felt like a mastermind for being able to conquer it, and seeing all the jobs/work available to Obj-C programmers, I really hope that Obj-C remains valuable. But the iOS development scene will unfortunately not be as exclusive as before. Which is fantastic for everyone, but makes things bittersweet for a greedy developer.</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/271ymp/todays_keyword_for_a_youtube_search_was_angry/chwxxez</guid><title>rjromero on Today's keyword for a Youtube search was &quot;Angry Girlfriend.&quot; This is what came up.</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/271ymp/todays_keyword_for_a_youtube_search_was_angry/chwxxez</link><dc:date>2014-06-02T04:42:13.504322+00:00</dc:date><description>so did she find her phone</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/26tqo9/whats_the_best_learning_path_to_programming_an/chvcfit</guid><title>rjromero on What's the best learning path to programming an iOS app for someone with little programming knowledge?</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/26tqo9/whats_the_best_learning_path_to_programming_an/chvcfit</link><dc:date>2014-05-31T01:33:20.832308+00:00</dc:date><description>Definitely learn C syntax, which shouldn&#39;t take you more than a few days. This is just for learning/declaring types, obj/method reference notation, etc... I&#39;m pretty sure you&#39;d need it, coming from I believe BASIC/Pascal?</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/26tqo9/whats_the_best_learning_path_to_programming_an/chue2k5</guid><title>rjromero on What's the best learning path to programming an iOS app for someone with little programming knowledge?</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/26tqo9/whats_the_best_learning_path_to_programming_an/chue2k5</link><dc:date>2014-05-29T22:55:18.450176+00:00</dc:date><description>I know Java and have a really good grasp on OOP. Honestly, as long as you what classes are/how inheritance works/methods/how to work with instances of a class and what an instance is, you should be fine. The hardest part of learning Obj-C for me was the syntax. It seems deceptively difficult, and then I ran through some documentation, and it seemed really easy at first, and then difficult again. If you know C (or quickly learn C, which I suggest, if you don&#39;t know it yet), you can write Obj-C, to an extent, but it&#39;s important to remember that you&#39;re going to have to use a lot of Apple-specific methods and their OOP/MVC style of programming. You will use C-style syntax in some areas of code, but for the majority of it, it will be proprietary and really there is nothing similar and nothing that could help you with learning it, other than Apple documentation/Obj-C tutorials/books. So I would say to just make sure you&#39;re learning the *right* way to code Obj-C. Becareful with following YT tutorials, as I want to say that 90% of them are absolute garbage that will show you how to make a primitive application with Storyboard/basic C and completely ignore the majority of Obj-C syntax. TLDR: If you know how a program works, OOP, and some C syntax, it will help. But Obj-C is pretty proprietary, and while learning Java could help, it didn&#39;t seem like it made much of a difference for me. Just learn the syntax, and learn the MVC development scheme, and you&#39;ll be fine.</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/26rkme/fonts_can_be_fatal/chtttr0</guid><title>rjromero on Fonts Can Be Fatal</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iOSProgramming/comments/26rkme/fonts_can_be_fatal/chtttr0</link><dc:date>2014-05-29T00:03:00.813013-07:00</dc:date><description>Better Fonts uses like weird iOS/Mac onboard Unicode characters for text instead of fonts I&#39;m pretty sure</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/26gdel/i_have_a_good_start_on_wireframing_my_app_but/chrv8qx</guid><title>rjromero on I have a good start on wireframing my app, but Xcode might be over my head considering I don't have much time around my work schedule to learn it all. If I want to hire a developer...</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/iosdev/comments/26gdel/i_have_a_good_start_on_wireframing_my_app_but/chrv8qx</link><dc:date>2014-05-27T01:20:32.560269+00:00</dc:date><description>Like 40% but I doubt he&#39;ll accept that. Try maybe 40% + $100-200 for his time. Depending on how complex the app is, this could maybe even be $500+. Good work is not cheap. Also, since it doesn&#39;t seem like you&#39;re a developer ( but not sure ) remember you must pay $100 for the ability to submit to the store. So, keep that in mind.</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/263vss/what_moment_in_your_life_can_you_look_at_and_say/chnt8d6</guid><title>rjromero on What moment in your life can you look at and say, &quot;that's when everything changed&quot;?</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/263vss/what_moment_in_your_life_can_you_look_at_and_say/chnt8d6</link><dc:date>2014-05-21T13:46:29.498448-07:00</dc:date><description>jw what video game it was if you don&#39;t mind mentioning that&#39;s insane how someone can throw away a real life over something virtual that will never matter to anyone</description></item><item><title>What's something your S.O. does that makes you happy inside?</title><category>AskReddit</category><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/263izs/whats_something_your_so_does_that_makes_you_happy/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/263izs/whats_something_your_so_does_that_makes_you_happy/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 05:34:05 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;md&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m talking about little things they may say all the time that make you really happy inside but you&amp;#39;ve never brought it up and they probably don&amp;#39;t have any idea how happy saying that thing made you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; submitted by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/user/rjromero&#34;&gt; rjromero &lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/&#34;&gt; AskReddit&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/263izs/whats_something_your_so_does_that_makes_you_happy/&#34;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/263izs/whats_something_your_so_does_that_makes_you_happy/"&gt;[8 comments]&lt;/a&gt;</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25zpvg/nyess/chmfxxq</guid><title>rjromero on Nyess</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25zpvg/nyess/chmfxxq</link><dc:date>2014-05-20T06:18:30.128714+00:00</dc:date><description>lmao wtf that kid&#39;s voice scared me it was a looot deeper and more mature sounding than I thought it&#39;d be</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25xkok/son_scares_the_st_out_of_his_dad_compilation/chmdihs</guid><title>rjromero on Son scares the S#!T out of his Dad compilation</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25xkok/son_scares_the_st_out_of_his_dad_compilation/chmdihs</link><dc:date>2014-05-19T21:09:08.863211-07:00</dc:date><description>maybe she&#39;s not easily scared and could just not understand &amp;quot;I&#39;m going to scare you now&amp;quot; in French?</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25v6ht/nazi_cab_driver_defends_wearing_swastika_armband/chlhznc</guid><title>rjromero on Nazi Cab Driver Defends Wearing Swastika Armband</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25v6ht/nazi_cab_driver_defends_wearing_swastika_armband/chlhznc</link><dc:date>2014-05-18T20:28:00.754704-07:00</dc:date><description>While I do not agree with him at all, I am proud of him practicing his rights to freedom of speech and it is 100% wrong for the reporter to harass him about it. If WBC can picket a veteran&#39;s funereal and not be locked up for it, he should be allowed his little wristband. Sure, his &amp;quot;independent website&amp;quot; might be an unreliable conspiracy site, but if that is what he believes, then he should be allowed to express it 100%. It&#39;s important that as a nation we retain the right to express the ideas the majority does not agree with, no matter how &amp;quot;offensive&amp;quot; it may be. One thing I found interesting was that the man never says that he loved the murder of jews or even Hitler. He simply believes in national socialism, a system of government. We all know what the Germans did with their national socialism, but that does not mean that national socialism should always be connected with Germany. There have been many groups to spring out across many nations, that had absolutely nothing to do with Germany. He gained my respect for saying &amp;quot;no comment&amp;quot; and not going more into detail. Because the media would have chopped up and edited his explanations to make him seem worse than they already have.</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25t9a2/portland_timbers_mls_fans_doing_their_best/chkiwfi</guid><title>rjromero on Portland Timbers (MLS) fans doing their best impression of a European fan base.</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25t9a2/portland_timbers_mls_fans_doing_their_best/chkiwfi</link><dc:date>2014-05-17T13:33:16.601493-07:00</dc:date><description>[relevant](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ubDIx3669Jw)</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/25lct9/colored_coins_give_away_btcblue/chid712</guid><title>rjromero on Colored Coins Give Away! BTC.Blue</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/25lct9/colored_coins_give_away_btcblue/chid712</link><dc:date>2014-05-14T20:46:11.110738-07:00</dc:date><description>this seems interesting! 16xNup61Ag8GpFb64miceVxUKSWxRggSHw</description></item><item><title>Do you believe in having a natural &quot;ear&quot; for production?</title><category>edmproduction</category><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/comments/25ie3b/do_you_believe_in_having_a_natural_ear_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/comments/25ie3b/do_you_believe_in_having_a_natural_ear_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 03:52:14 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;md&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such as being able to recognize good samples/synths/drum kits from bad ones. Or being able to tell when to break the rules w/ an EQ. Or being able to hear when to add harmonics/distortion. Those types of things.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I personally do. I hear a lot of producers who just use really low quality drum kits or use stock preset synths and EQ/compress/master everything perfectly, but their tracks still sound &amp;quot;cheesy&amp;quot; because they do not know how to make a coherent sound palette. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I feel like production is now becoming as much of an art form as the actual composition of music itself and that it requires creativity and a &amp;quot;ear&amp;quot; (whether natural or acquired after years of just replicating others w/ it) to produce a good sounding track. It&amp;#39;s not all about just following rules to EQ/compress perfectly.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; submitted by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/user/rjromero&#34;&gt; rjromero &lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/&#34;&gt; edmproduction&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/comments/25ie3b/do_you_believe_in_having_a_natural_ear_for/&#34;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/comments/25ie3b/do_you_believe_in_having_a_natural_ear_for/"&gt;[9 comments]&lt;/a&gt;</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25fx35/daily_life_of_a_major_league_soccer_player/chheur7</guid><title>rjromero on Daily Life of a Major League Soccer Player - Through the eyes of Google Glass</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/25fx35/daily_life_of_a_major_league_soccer_player/chheur7</link><dc:date>2014-05-14T02:36:06.834157+00:00</dc:date><description>Wow this video made me so happy in so many ways soccer is such a magical sport I truly find it impossible to play a game and not smile even just once. Look at how happy everyone looks to be there they are all living their dreams.. :&#39;)</description></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/25dpvw/ive_never_been_to_phoenix_before_today_and_now_i/chgczyi</guid><title>rjromero on I've never been to Phoenix before today and now I understand what hell is.</title><link>http://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/25dpvw/ive_never_been_to_phoenix_before_today_and_now_i/chgczyi</link><dc:date>2014-05-12T16:09:57.502319-07:00</dc:date><description>sigh I&#39;m a Phoenician and I thought it was nice today...</description></item></channel></rss>
