http://www.businessinsider.com/everyone-who-believes-in-bitcoin-should-try-to-answer-this-question-2013-12/comments.rss
HTTP/1.1 200 OK
Server: nginx
Date: Sat, 12 Jul 2014 13:15:23 GMT
Content-Type: text/xml; charset=utf-8
X-Served-By: local (via varnish3)
Cache-Control: public, max-age=300
Content-Length: 112179
X-Varnish: 980808095
Age: 0
Via: 1.1 varnish
X-Meta-Tbi-Varnish-Servers: www
X-Meta-Tbi-Final-Client-Ip: 54.83.243.165
Vary: Accept-Encoding
Connection: close

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

  <channel>
       <title>Everyone Who Believes In Bitcoin Should Try To Answer This Question</title>
       <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/everyone-who-believes-in-bitcoin-should-try-to-answer-this-question-2013-12/comments</link>
       <language>en-us</language>
       <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
       <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 09:15:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
       <description>Joe Weisenthal</description>

       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d7e2136bb3f7f531810fdb</guid>
				<title>OtmaneELRHAZI</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 08:43:47 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d7e2136bb3f7f531810fdb</link>
				<description>It is a good trading currency with contrast of precious metals like gold, silver, platinum or palladium. Virtual no storage cost no mining related bs. I think it should prosper.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d4b28b6da811643dc79b4a</guid>
				<title>Tigerpaw</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 22:44:11 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d4b28b6da811643dc79b4a</link>
				<description>Someone should aak what questions could be answered about Bitcoin after a daily injection from the Fed on the scale of $25 million per month for the next 5 years, for a fair comparison.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d38eee69bedd8f5ab54554</guid>
				<title>pungopete</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 01:59:58 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d38eee69bedd8f5ab54554</link>
				<description>By the way. If you don't have believe in Bitcoin you can send me yours and I'll actually appreciate them for what they are truly worth.

1E1ftX9ZpJYUcwbGcJF6aSHaUty8X5zQNf</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d38c7c6bb3f73e0a3ac609</guid>
				<title>pungopete</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 01:49:32 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d38c7c6bb3f73e0a3ac609</link>
				<description>I don't see the point in debating ideologies. Neither side will ever concede to the other. This is a perfect example. 
You fail to understand that Bitcoin is backed by a belief; just not by a belief in a single government.

There are certain truths about humanity which can't be disregarded. The truth to which I'm referring is that above all else, the greatest desire of all humanity is freedom. People will sacrifice life, wealth, love, even happiness for the pursuit of freedom.

What does this have to do with Bitcoin you might ask? This is the belief of which Bitcoin represents. If I choose to believe in Bitcoin then I have chosen to believe in the infallible idea that Bitcoin represents and further supports. People will support Bitcoin for as long as they desire freedom. A national government can regulate Bitcoin until the legislators are blue in the face but an unenforceable regulation is no regulation indeed. They have no power to enforce regulation of Bitcoin and the means to acquire said power would be unpalatable for a citizenry built upon freedom. The acquisition of that power alone would be Authoritarian and the government would do well to realize that such action would be crossing the line which serves it's own existence.

Simply to ask about the &quot;floor&quot; of Bitcoin is foolish. There is no floor to Bitcoin, but to assume there is ever a floor is only to admit how spoiled one has become having lived in a time where such a fail-safe could even be perceived to exist. There is no such fail-safe in anything of value; that I can assure you.

The only thing you can feel certain will ever retain value is the labor you can perform with your body or mind.

Bitcoin is the next evolutionary step in the history of money and it will be worth more than you will ever believe. Mark my words.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d373b6eab8ea610cb54552</guid>
				<title>RyN</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 00:03:50 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d373b6eab8ea610cb54552</link>
				<description>Vix-Trader, A more interesting question would be why are you so obsessed with such a stupid question? I can see by your handle and your comments that you've had your head stuffed so far up Wall Streets's ass for so long you look at things only under a certain perspective and cannot recognize that your obsession with &quot;the floor price of Bitcoin&quot; has different meaning's to different people. 

I'll assume when you are talking about price floor, you mean the highest exchange rate to USD on any given exchange at some point in time in the future as determined by the market. Of course it is zero. This would be zero for anything.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d369fe6da81159551b7e8a</guid>
				<title>Ryn</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 23:22:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d369fe6da81159551b7e8a</link>
				<description>I think you are confusing the term &quot;backed&quot; with &quot;propped up&quot; or &quot;enforced&quot;. In the event of a loss of confidence in the dollar or hyper inflation the US Government does not agree to allow holders of US dollars to redeem them for something that would possibly hold its value in that situation. Therefore, the US dollar is not backed by anything. Standing armies and tax enforcement doesn't mean much in the event of dollars losing their perceived value. 

The dollar requires standing armies, enforcement, the secret service, the threat of violence or prison all in an effort to maintain user confidence. Bitcoin makes use of cryptography and distributed network computing to accomplish the same thing. The biggest threat to Bitcoin is a technological flaw in the system that has yet to be discovered.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d363e56da8111f471b7e81</guid>
				<title>RyN</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 22:56:21 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d363e56da8111f471b7e81</link>
				<description>You do realize that you can buy a fraction of a bitcoin right? Price is not a barrier.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2eda9ecad0497521b7e83</guid>
				<title>coreychambers</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 14:31:53 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2eda9ecad0497521b7e83</link>
				<description>The Answer: The floor of Bitcoin and gold are both ultimately zero. Admittedly, Bitcoin is more likely to reach near zero than gold because it is less established and more easily replaced. That does not diminish the fact that Bitcoin is now well on its way to being the #1 currency in worldwide financial transactions.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2ec5369bedd5e51b54552</guid>
				<title>coreychambers</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 14:26:11 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2ec5369bedd5e51b54552</link>
				<description>God, I hope that nobody is actually believing Joe and his wacky economist friend DeLong. Gold makes pretty things. The answer to the question is that, believe it or not, Bitcoin makes prettier things, particularly relating to money, payments and transactions.

Bitcoin makes for easier, cheaper, more efficient transactions than gold. You can carry $10 million worth of Bitcoin with you when you travel. Try that with gold. You can do more complex faster and cheaper with Bitcoin that you can with any other payment method. It is so funny that Wiesenthal and his kooky economist cannot understand that. Makes me feel so smart. Or maybe I just took the time and effort to do my homework to find out what Bitcoin really does. -- Corey Chambers, The Bitcoin Blogs</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2add069bedd1140b5455a</guid>
				<title>Ken Danagger</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 09:59:28 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d2add069bedd1140b5455a</link>
				<description>Your argument for gold as a store of value:
&quot;If all else fails, you can make pretty things out of it&quot; - Great! Unfortunately that won't feed you, or keep you warm. If people won't trade real goods and services for it, it's useless. Granted, that is not likely to happen. Historically, it has NEVER happened. However, in our modern global economy, gold has a few drawbacks. Namely, lack of liquidity and transportability. Sure, you can trade paper or electronic promissory notes for gold, but then you have the same counter-party risk as fiat dollars. Even with the physical, you have debasement risk such as gold plated tungsten, etc.

Your argument for the USD as a store of value:
1) It is accepted by the gov't mob as &quot;protection money&quot; against being imprisoned. That isn't exactly what I'd call an attribute for a honest and fair currency. If given a choice, I think most people would choose to not use mobster money that the mob tracks every unit of so they can extract their &quot;cut&quot; by force.
2) The FED promises to &quot;buy them back&quot; - to intentionally deflate the money supply? AHHhhahah! Riiight. Propaganda. 
The FED can only do, and only does one thing now - INFLATE.
In theory the FED could try to reign in run-away inflation by drastically raising interest rates (as it did 35 years ago), but that trick will no longer work with our monstrous debt. The result would be a debt default - and the same destruction of the dollar end result.
The FED is powerless to do anything but further inflate now. It is trapped. The only thing keeping the inflation pressure cooker from exploding right now is our massive exports of USD around the world. There are clear signs that the USD is being increasingly rejected around world - and this will be the fuel for more war.

Back to bitcoin. What backs it? What makes it a reliable store of value? The answer is exactly the same as for gold or federal reserve promissory notes;

Consumer confidence and the productive capacity of the economy. 

That's it. Without a productive economy that produces the goods and services that people need, fiat paper, bitcoins, and gold are all worthless.
There is no debate that people worldwide are rapidly loosing confidence in paper promissory notes issued by criminal banksters and their gov't accomplices. This is nothing new however - all gov't fiat currencies eventually get abused and crash to zero.
Gold has historically been an outstanding as a store of value, but it is currently being crushed by the dilution of the paper markets.
Bitcoin can't be diluted because the algorithm itself prevents it. The entire decentralized network must agree on the addition of every new unit - and the limit is hard-coded at every node. You can try to tamper with a single node, or even a hundred nodes, or even a thousand nodes, but any efforts to circumvent the rules will be rejected by the overall network that exists globally - outside of the influence of government looters and criminals.

The utility of a currency as a reliable store of value basically comes down to public perception. Legal tender laws, world reserve currency status and propaganda have kept the USD at the forefront, but those tricks are failing. People are looking for a safe place to store their wealth that has the transaction utility that a modern digital global economy demands. The one that the free market chooses, will likely be the one that works best.
Further innovation and competition will keep things fluid. That is a very good thing. Bitcoin, nor any other form of currency should be forced upon people if something better, more secure, or more flexible comes along.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d0dd516da811b304b1392f</guid>
				<title>Kurt</title>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:57:37 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d0dd516da811b304b1392f</link>
				<description>Since the question is &quot;how is bitcoin a store of value&quot;? I would counter with, &quot;how is the federal reserve note a store of value?&quot; Answer, it isn't and has continually lost value. It would have no value but for the full threat of murder by those calling themselves &quot;The US Federal Gov't&quot;.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d027466bb3f7216a1354a8</guid>
				<title>betaadjusted</title>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 12:00:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52d027466bb3f7216a1354a8</link>
				<description>Surely the floor for bitcoin is the amazing IRR you can get from these mining computers you can buy? Of course its contingent on today's bitcoin price not falling substantially, but theres quite a buffer even at today's prices. Its like a ponzi-scheme: people will pile into those IRRs until they are no longer attractive. But for now, they are still very attractive, hence the risk/reward looks very attractive and will continue to lure people in. Or thats how it seems to me anyway.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c63d08ecad04b73ea579f8</guid>
				<title>peritter</title>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 23:31:04 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c63d08ecad04b73ea579f8</link>
				<description>The floor for BTC is ZERO.
It is just right that way. Fiat moneys have this nasty property.
Who says that the US Dollar cant go the way of the Zimbabwean Dollar? Just ask Hungarians of old.
It may take longer and bigger shocks but it is perfectly imaginable. 
As it is said: &quot;anyone can create money but having it accepted is a different thing.&quot;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c456636bb3f7787b7479aa</guid>
				<title>Junayd</title>
				<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 12:54:43 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c456636bb3f7787b7479aa</link>
				<description>You have brilliant communication skills. Say something in capitals. Say it again. Then act condescending. I'm convinced!

I pray for your co-workers.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c287086bb3f79904c23ca8</guid>
				<title>Jonas Lihnell</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 03:57:44 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c287086bb3f79904c23ca8</link>
				<description>While I agree that the value of bitcoin is in direct relation to the goods and services it can buy, I utterly disagree with your notion that bitcoin would be increasingly used by criminals. Furthermore bitcoin can be reliably banked and it is unlikely that any particular sovereign has the capability to confiscate properly stored bitcoins. The only reason that makes sense that would make people believe otherwise is that it is still being targeted by FUD in media, much like most new technologies are. Give it a few more years and you will see that it will still be here and while it probably has not changed the reserve currency of the world by then, it will definately have grown to accomodate even the larger multinational businessmodels.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c278dfecad04807bc23cb0</guid>
				<title>Jonas Lihnell</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 02:57:19 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c278dfecad04807bc23cb0</link>
				<description>If you claim that gold has intrinsic value and that the value is its physical properties, then I will claim that bitcoin has intrinsic value and that the value is that the currency bitcoin has a property that allows it to be used with the bitcoin payment system.

No other material has the same physical properties that gold do; No other currency has the same digital properties that bitcoin does. (Being able to exist on the blockchain of the bitcoin payment system)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c2777feab8ea982dc23ca4</guid>
				<title>Jonas Lihnell</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 02:51:27 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c2777feab8ea982dc23ca4</link>
				<description>The algorithms are calculating a proof of work to help build concensus between participants in the network regarding the validity of transactions. Each node verifies that the funds to be sent comes from a valid source and that the source has the permissions to send the fund and that the funds exists and are spendable.

The algorithms are calculating, in effect, verifications/validations of transactions.
The algortightms are doing this as a service to all other nodes in the network to help reach concensus about the validity of the transaction.

If you need a more detailed answer I recommend reading the original whitepaper, it explains things decenty and in great detail despite only being a couple of pages long.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c2754b69beddda76c23cb3</guid>
				<title>Jonas Lihnell</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 02:42:03 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c2754b69beddda76c23cb3</link>
				<description>The underlying value of the bitcoin currency is the inherently valuable utility of the bitcoin payment system. The ability to transfer wealth internationally at extremely low cost and at high speeds is the trait that would compare to golds ability to mold into pretty things.

It's really as simple as that. Gold's inherent value as &quot;can be made into pretty things&quot; is subjective. Bitcoins value as a tool to transfer wealth s subjective. The dollars value as a tool to avoid physical violence by paying taxes to a government who demands such from you or will imprison you if you refuse is also subjective.

Golds value will fail when society no longer needs to have pretty things.
The dollars value will fail when the government no longer demand taxes or have access to monopolized violence.
Bitcoins value will fail the day people have no use to transfer wealth.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c258c66bb3f7e829c23cb0</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 00:40:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c258c66bb3f7e829c23cb0</link>
				<description>By law, you can only pay your US taxes with USD. That means that even if US dollars fell into chaos and became almost as bad as Bitcoins are today, and lost its status as a world reserve currency, USD would still have value because all US citizens and companies would need them to pay their taxes. Sure they could do day-to-day business in Euro, Roubles, pieces of eight, or Dogecoin, but they would still need USD when taxes are due. There is literally nothing other than USD that would do.
Bitcoin doesn't have any such hard floor value. Not even a soft floor.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c2530a69bedd1b36c23ca8</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 00:15:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c2530a69bedd1b36c23ca8</link>
				<description>No, floor value of fiat is all the debts, taxes and contracts which one needs fiat to pay off.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c1f2656bb3f71c65c23cad</guid>
				<title>trademark-2014</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 17:23:33 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c1f2656bb3f71c65c23cad</link>
				<description>Заработайте Bitcoins!
Присоединяйтесь к лучшим Bitcoin PTC и начать зарабатывать Bitcoins для нажатия объявлений.&lt;a href=&quot;http://btcclicks.com/?r=be23d833&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://btcclicks.com/?r=be23d833&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c1f1526bb3f71465c23cb0</guid>
				<title>trademark-2014</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 17:18:58 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c1f1526bb3f71465c23cb0</link>
				<description>&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/pages/Bitcoin/448469965254805?ref=hlhttp://www.earncrypto.com/index.php?r=7940&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;https://www.facebook.com/pages/Bitcoin/448469965254805?ref=hlhttp://www.earncrypto.com/index.php?r=7940&lt;/a&gt;

EarnCrypto.com | Earn free cryptocurrency and virtual currency!
www.earncrypto.com
EarnCrypto.com is a completely free &amp; easy way to earn free bitcoin, litecoin, imvu credits, gaia cash, cryptocurrencies, and virtual currenices.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c1a914ecad04147a1cf3ea</guid>
				<title>Kyler Anderson</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 12:10:44 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c1a914ecad04147a1cf3ea</link>
				<description>Im sorry, but if you seriously just wrote an article based on the say so of Paul Krugman, the same idiot who said the internet would have as much affect on business as the fax machine, then I can take you seriously. Bitcoin is the perfect money, and you are going to have to get used to it, or get run over by it, its up to you. It doesn't need your approval to succeed.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c18db56da811a4601cf3e5</guid>
				<title>Rick Van Coevering</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 10:13:57 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c18db56da811a4601cf3e5</link>
				<description>The problem with Bitcoin, as with any other currency, is its acceptance and transferability. Bitcoins, like Reichsmarks have exactly the value of the goods and/or services that others are willing to trade for in exchange. When the Reichsmark became inflated you could not trade truckloads for a loaf of bread. Bitcoins may have a designed protection against inflation, but they give no guaranty for acceptance. It makes no difference if you have one or a thousand bitcoins if the seller wants dollars or euros. 
The risk of the bitcoin as currency is that it is becoming more and more the currency of criminals. As money laundering through bitcoin proliferates it looks to become increasing illicit in actual commerce. Someone may take your bitcoin, but only at a discount so that it can be fenced it and the seller can get real currency. And any bitcoin that you own may (will) be confiscated and/or criminalized by your particular sovereign. 
Compounding the problem with its lack of liquidity is bitcoins recent run on fraudulent exchanges wherein thousands of bitcoins have been stolen. If bitcoin cannot be reliably banked its value evaporates. 
The bitcoin of today is the tulip of the 17th century, except it is neither so pretty nor so fragrant.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c1437c69beddbc486167bd</guid>
				<title>sisco king</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 04:57:16 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c1437c69beddbc486167bd</link>
				<description>Bitcoin and its other 67 alternative cryptocurrencys do have a market gab of $13 billion US$. This says it all. There will be 1000 more cryptocurrencys coming next year people trust them more than the double standard politics and economics of the USA. This is the floor of the cryptocurrency.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12f6069bedd8c2202ec57</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 03:31:28 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12f6069bedd8c2202ec57</link>
				<description>You realize that there are dozens of international markets trading USD and other currencies for BTC as we speak? Simple demand is what gives it value.

The value of a car is not the price tag the dealer puts on the window. It is the price that someone is willing to pay. You are right that the floor may be 0, but there are a few hundred thousand individuals and a few billion dollars who disagree with you about that.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12df26da8118b4dda2057</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 03:25:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12df26da8118b4dda2057</link>
				<description>The same way you value the worthless paper in your pocket. It is based on the perceived value of a basket of goods that it can be exchanged for today.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12c966da8110c4dda2053</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 03:19:34 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12c966da8110c4dda2053</link>
				<description>You're being pedantic. What is the value of a pair of shoes or a loaf of bread? They have a specific purpose and we can quantify their value as cost in hundreds of different currencies.

The value of a currency is its ability to be exchanged for goods and services. Period.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12b8beab8ea027702ec59</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 03:15:07 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12b8beab8ea027702ec59</link>
				<description>No it is not. Here is a government site refuting you &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bls.gov/data/inflation_calculator.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.bls.gov/data/inflation_calculator.htm&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c129c869beddfd1702ec55</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 03:07:36 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c129c869beddfd1702ec55</link>
				<description>Floor value for all fiat is 0. USD included.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c129a1eab8eaa77602ec55</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 03:06:57 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c129a1eab8eaa77602ec55</link>
				<description>Krugman was in that wrong minority FYI. Now he proclaims that trinkets and taxes are the fallback values for an infinitely inflatable currency.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12642eab8ea6b6802ec67</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 02:52:34 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12642eab8ea6b6802ec67</link>
				<description>Ad hominems are not the hallmark of the superior argument.

Seriously you think jewelry or being able to pay the state are &quot;values&quot;?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c125ba69bedd6c0502ec6f</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 02:50:18 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c125ba69bedd6c0502ec6f</link>
				<description>Cost of entry? It's a currency. Find a way to earn Bitcoin or buy it if you like. It is not a stock. The smallest divisible unit is still cheaper than a penny.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12313ecad04e57a02ec55</guid>
				<title>I have US dollars - inflated by more than 2%</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 02:38:59 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12313ecad04e57a02ec55</link>
				<description>We Don't Quite Know What We are Talking About When We Talk About Volatility.

You are emotional to the point where the intellectual value of your argument suffers.

For a supposed Vix trader that's quite a bummer.

Take it easy, It's just money - and not even yours. Why would you risk a stroke?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12023eab8ea706102ec5b</guid>
				<title>13</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 02:26:27 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c12023eab8ea706102ec5b</link>
				<description>I would give you a pass, if after making 10-20 comments about bitcoin, you would finally learn the correct spelling of the darn thing that freaks you out. Bitcoin. One word. Pretty simple concept. :)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c11e93eab8ea2c5802ec61</guid>
				<title>you can just start your own</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 02:19:47 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c11e93eab8ea2c5802ec61</link>
				<description>Krugman explains: &quot;Underpinning the value of the dollar is a combination of 

(a) the fact that you can use them to pay your taxes to the U.S. government, and 
(b) that the Federal Reserve is a potential dollar sink and has promised to buy them back and extinguish them if their real value starts to sink at (much) more than 2%/year (yes, I know).&quot;

How would your criteria of floor value, described above apply to the dollar?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c11da76bb3f75b5302ec55</guid>
				<title>you can just start your own</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 02:15:51 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c11da76bb3f75b5302ec55</link>
				<description>99% of the companies and their products in the entire economy, can be described as &quot;there is nothing they currently do, that only they can do&quot;. 

Are you claiming that their intrinsic value is zero and it will always be zero? 

Don't be ridiculous.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c11439ecad04695a02ec59</guid>
				<title>hairspray</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 01:35:37 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c11439ecad04695a02ec59</link>
				<description>&quot;And that utility could just as easily be FREE. What a hilariously stupid reason to buy something.&quot;

One of the most abundant things in the universe is energy, even more abundant than oxygen. That is, it should be free, but why isn't it? Why pay for something that is around you everywhere? Something that is essentially worthless since it is so abundant. Yet, you silly person still pay to a utility to deliver something that is essentially free. Why is that? Maybe because the utility has a utility. You are paying for the infrastructure.

No worries, according to your logic someday energy's value will drop to zero, which will be great for everyone, but try convincing the energy companies of that. I'm not holding my breath.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c107df6da8113e60da2061</guid>
				<title>TTC Media</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 00:42:55 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c107df6da8113e60da2061</link>
				<description>The same question can be asked about the US dollar or any other form of paper currency. Why use it? Where is it's value? What backs it. The US dollar is just as much a digital currency as a paper currency. Further, lead is worth more than gold. If a robber sticks a knife in your face, what would you rather send back to him, a gold watch and then maybe a gold ring and he will want to know if you have more? Or would you rather send a lead bullet to him where he will not be coming back at you? Lead is worth more than gold.

 You can encrypt ownership of both tangibles as well as intangibles with Bitcoin, You can not do that with the dollar, gold or the Euro. That makes Bitcoin by far more valuable than any other form or currency alone. Hope that does not screw up your thinking to much.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c105ffeab8eafd2a02ec59</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 00:34:55 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c105ffeab8eafd2a02ec59</link>
				<description>The problem is that securing it takes more resources than breaking it, and creates unnecessary waste.

The public key cryptography that ensures that the right owner spends their &quot;Bitcoin&quot; is much easier to use than to break, and is the same as is used by internet commerce and banks elsewhere. You won't be breaking that unless you find that &quot;P=NP&quot;, have quantum computers, or finds some error in the implementation.

But the mining arms race that is supposed to stop double spending and decides which is the true ledger, is actually using more resources on securing it than it would take to break it. It's less like a locked door and more like an non-lockable castle gate and it takes more soldiers to hold shut than it takes to push it open. As Smaulgld says, the mining calculations are just pointless busywork designed to show that you have more computing power than the other guy.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0fa3a6da8114d3ada2059</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0fa3a6da8114d3ada2059</link>
				<description>I'll be a tiny bit more charitable: If anyone starts offering a product or service that is cheaper to buy with Bitcoin than with anything else, then it would have value as something other than just a speculation vehicle. It might not be a definite floor, but it would at least provide some real value.
If Bitcoin ever were to become a cheaper and better money transmission system, it might also gain some value based on that, which would be a true floor value - but the current version is too slow, expensive, risky and doesn't scale.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0fa1aecad04462602ec5f</guid>
				<title>Don Harder</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:44:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0fa1aecad04462602ec5f</link>
				<description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/digital-currencies-worth-more-than-1-2013-12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.businessinsider.com/digital-currencies-worth-more-than-1-2013-12&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f6fa69beddb51f02ec5b</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:30:50 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f6fa69beddb51f02ec5b</link>
				<description>Yes yes we know, Bit coin is the libertarians wet dream. But wanting the world to be different doesn't give something INTRINSIC value, it just gives it a price. Why can't you see the difference? How old are you? If not 13 yet, I'll give you a pass. If you are, seriously? Value and price are synonymous to you?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f61b69bedd882202ec5c</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:27:07 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f61b69bedd882202ec5c</link>
				<description>Re-read what Gunnar has said, you clearly missed it but it's a very important point. There is NOTHING Bit coin currently does that only Bit coin can do. That's the answer. That's why it's floor price is zero. Until the day comes when Bit coin can offer something that no substitute or clone can, it's floor value will always be zero.

And people buying it doesn't give it intrinsic value. You should probably learn the definition of the words you use. 0.02$</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f4b36bb3f7450602ec56</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:21:07 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f4b36bb3f7450602ec56</link>
				<description>Do you really not understand that we can use the exact same technology Bit coin is using without actually using Bit coins. Do you really not see this? Holy shit, really?

And no, sometimes questions have answers. What's the floor price of Bit coin? ZERO. That's the one and only correct answer. It can go to zero. Run along now, recess is over...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f4166da8110b30da2053</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:18:30 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f4166da8110b30da2053</link>
				<description>&quot;Here is the answer you keep missing: its value is in its utility. (this includes plenty... solving double spend, global transfers of value ... etc.) &quot;

And that utility could just as easily be FREE. What a hilariously stupid reason to buy something. For it's utility. Dodge coin has utility too, does it have intrinsic value? What about the next thousand Bit coin clones that offer the same utility, are those valuable too? 

Idiots will be separated from their money no matter how hard the rest of us try to help them avoid it. Well, one more sucker for me to rob of his savings... All in a days work :)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f2d76da8117123da2085</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:13:11 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f2d76da8117123da2085</link>
				<description>I'm responding to the person above me's completely ludicrous comment that the USD is losing value, and I'll respond to it every time I see it. That's a lot by the way, because there's an entire army of you idiots who regurgitate the same crap.

The value of your dollars may be declining, but for anyone with even a marginally functional brain that is not the case. Sorry, you got shafted at birth with defective gray matter.

Ok, continue talking about the bright future of Bit coin. LOL, I give it a year tops. This pump and dump is as obvious as can be...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f2b7ecad04131b02ec5b</guid>
				<title>you can just start your own</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:12:39 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f2b7ecad04131b02ec5b</link>
				<description>Sure you can fork it, pre-mine... whatever... 

But how do you make it into Bitcoin? As in a cryptocurrency in which people are willing to put their money?

Good luck with that part. It will clearly set apart your crypto from Bitcoin.

Now go and place a value on that difference.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f21a6da8116e23da205c</guid>
				<title>nuru musa</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:10:02 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f21a6da8116e23da205c</link>
				<description>BTC has no clones as there is not a single currency that exactly possesses the characteristics of BTC .no coin that has a 21 million limit of production and no coin that has the same scarcity as BTC.Remember that BTC is an alternative currency,therefore people will be more inclined to believe in it when the store of value of fiat currency fails.remember also that both BTC and fiat currency has no intrinsic value and even if fiat money is backed up by the men with the gun then BTC is also backed up by its own checks and balance system which is a form of guaranty.when fiat money fails wouldn't you buy BTC ?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f1c6eab8ead47d02ec5c</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:08:38 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f1c6eab8ead47d02ec5c</link>
				<description>Continue what? Announcing to the world that you don't have a clue about economics or the world you live in? Sure, go ahead.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f0c2ecad04501c02ec57</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:04:18 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f0c2ecad04501c02ec57</link>
				<description>There's no need to buy one whole Bitcoin, since they're divisible down to small units. Of course, there's no need to buy a fraction of a Bitcoin either. And there is no such thing as &quot;a Bitcoin&quot;, they're not individual tokens that you can follow from person to person - just account balances of a sort.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f081eab8eac70102ec55</guid>
				<title>RecallCarlLevin</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 23:03:13 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0f081eab8eac70102ec55</link>
				<description>Underpinning the value of Bitcoin is the fact that people will always desire freedom an want to remain unmolested by the corruption that excessive bank credit/debt has wrought upon the world.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0eb086da811ce12da205c</guid>
				<title>Don Harder</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 22:39:52 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0eb086da811ce12da205c</link>
				<description>Perhaps. Unless the cost of entry makes the alternatives more attractive. At $500+ this is already happening.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0e2a669beddc46c02ec61</guid>
				<title>whydisbit?</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 22:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0e2a669beddc46c02ec61</link>
				<description>Just too funny, 

Underpinning the value of the dollar is a combination of (a) the fact that you can use them to pay your taxes to the U.S. government,
?!? really ... who cares .. maybe I won't have taxes ! And at what value .. that is just nonsense reasoning

 and (b) that the Federal Reserve is a potential dollar sink and has promised to buy them back

Again .. pretty funny ... buy them back? and give you what? It is no longer secured with silver and gold. So they buy it back with a different fiat currency?!?

Both of the above reasons are nonsensical. With bit coin and any other &quot;currency&quot; including gold. It matters if people will take it as currency. That is it. Will Bitcoin stand time? who knows, but for now it is working for me. 

By the way , no currency is really an investment ... it is a store of value. It depends how long you want to store that value as to the risk of a particular currency is.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0e06d69beddf27102ec55</guid>
				<title>Bitcoin_believers</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 21:54:37 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0e06d69beddf27102ec55</link>
				<description>The dollar has relative (market) value to other currencies and it has a nominal value, but what is this quantifiable value you speak of?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0e048ecad04b27c02ec55</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 21:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0e048ecad04b27c02ec55</link>
				<description>which is worth more being able to make trinkets or pay taxes or being able to store money safely from any threats, transfer any amount without approval of the state, buy or sell to and from anyone anywhere in the world, not have your savings value eroded at the convenience of the state. shall i continue? 

Krugman's arguments are the poor ones.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0dd13eab8eaac5002ec63</guid>
				<title>phro</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 21:40:19 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0dd13eab8eaac5002ec63</link>
				<description>Pretty things and taxes vs protection from seizure, worldwide real time transfer, uninflatable, etc. Take your pick.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0dc41ecad04f07502ec55</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 21:36:49 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0dc41ecad04f07502ec55</link>
				<description>I don't need any amount of any cryptocurrency, but if I did I could easily fork Litecoin. You know the source code is available for free, right? I could configure it to do a 100% pre-mine, with only one coin ever created, but infinitely divisible. It'll be a bit like those huge stone &quot;coins&quot; that sit outside somebody's house, except I own the only one, and I could pretend that I own all the money in the whole world. Unless somebody else were willing to provide goods and services for pieces of this Gunnarcoin, though, it would be pretty worthless even if I spent 50 billion dollars on a mining rig and electricity to &quot;secure&quot; it. I wouldn't be able to stop my neighbor from just creating his own fork instead of buying into my fork.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0d3f46da8117853da2051</guid>
				<title>you can just start your own</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 21:01:24 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0d3f46da8117853da2051</link>
				<description>Go ahead, do it. Come back in a year tell us how easy it was and what's the value of it.
You might be surprised.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0bd916da811970eda205b</guid>
				<title>hairspray</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 19:25:53 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0bd916da811970eda205b</link>
				<description>&quot;Do you people not realize that none of you are answering the question? What is the value of Bitcoin? Not why is it convenient, not why is it a technological breakthrough, not why is it a wet dream for libertarians, the question is how do you quantify it's VALUE.&quot;

You can't even see that you have answered the &quot;question&quot; within your own paragraph. Its as though you have some sort of odd mental block.

Here is the answer you keep missing: its value is in its utility. (this includes plenty... solving double spend, global transfers of value ... etc.)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b8886da8110507da2053</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 19:04:24 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b8886da8110507da2053</link>
				<description>Gold has unique properties - platinum and silver have different chemical and physical characteristics and if you absolutely need gold you have to buy it or manufacture it through a nuclear process.

A cryptocurrency, however, is almost free to aquire - you can just start your own or adopt one that's given away for free. Until there's a product or service you can only buy with Bitcoin, nobody ever needs a Bitcoin.

Bitcoin's floor value is probably asymptotic to 0, since there is an infinite number of possible cryptocurrencies, and plenty of other payment methods which already work better. I only say &quot;probably&quot; as a hedge against a negative value of Bitcoin, as in situations where people would pay to get rid of them.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b54c6da811ee78da2055</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 18:50:36 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b54c6da811ee78da2055</link>
				<description>Facebook stock is a stake in the company. The floor value is all the stuff the company owns, in cash and other property, minus its debts. Whenever a stock becomes valued lower than the floor value, it might get bought out by somebody who wants to sell the desks, office chairs and other assets.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b34c69beddef0e02ec55</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 18:42:04 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b34c69beddef0e02ec55</link>
				<description>You've fallen for the &quot;sunk cost fallacy&quot;, Junayd. If you have to spend resources digging for oil or gold, you need to recoup that cost when you sell what you dug up, so it's a floor price for you to break even no your mining operation. But if you spend the same amount of resources digging up radioactive waste, that doesn't make your radioactive waste worth its worth in gold if nobody needs it. You might even have to pay somebody to take it off your hands.

If all that electricity wasted for &quot;mining&quot; could be released in the future, that would make Bitcoins worth something, and if you mined with an ASIC and unmined it with a CPU you'd have discovered a free energy machine.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b299ecad04112502ec55</guid>
				<title>Bernie B</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 18:39:05 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b299ecad04112502ec55</link>
				<description>Can we please recognize that it's &quot;Bitcoin&quot; not &quot;BitCoin&quot;, come on now...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b031eab8ea887302ec5c</guid>
				<title>Gunnar René Øie</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 18:28:49 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0b031eab8ea887302ec5c</link>
				<description>The Internet Protocol was not the first network protocol. Ever used X400? What about Fidonet? Most people have never heard about them, but they used to be all the rage. On the other hand, our current email system has evolved from before the Internet was a thing.

You are right that most clones don't offer anything better than Bitcoin, but Bitcoin doesn't offer anything other than brandname recognition either. For those who didn't get in on the ground floor, there's no more incentive to get into Bitcoin than Dogecoins, and due to its peer-to-peer nature the infrastructure is easily cloned and spawned ad nauseum as long as tertiary service providers and governments allow it to happen. More mining power doesn't secure the network, since the amount of resources you need to attack the network is equal or less than the resources needed to protect it. 

Claiming that Bitcoin is the payment system that will endure is a bit like claiming that a pay-per-minute BBS system running on a modem in Satoshi's bedroom from 1AM to 8AM will become what everyone uses for email in the future and that it will destroy Darpanet and ACH.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c09be2ecad04217302ec63</guid>
				<title>Pseudonymous</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 17:02:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c09be2ecad04217302ec63</link>
				<description>Joe, maybe you should create a currency! You should call it the Weaselthaler!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0906becad04936302ec57</guid>
				<title>scott7ree</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 16:13:15 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0906becad04936302ec57</link>
				<description>@carlos sounds like you have some unresolved problems with the USA and currency in general. 'when all currencies go to zero?' I can't even tell if you support Bitcoin or not.

I am a firm believer Bitcoin has value based on two things: It is easily transmittable and is decentralized/international.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c08c5e6da811650cda2056</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:55:58 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c08c5e6da811650cda2056</link>
				<description>All money is based on a shared consensus.

With Bitcoin the current price is based on a shared consensus that was defined by price discovery by the various exchanges that trade bitcoin.

It is just confounding that people argue against the value of bitcoin by conjuring up extreme conditions concerning value.

Gold is valuable when all currencies blow up and go to zero.

The USD is valuable when the U.S.A. needs to exert it military power to send countries into total subjugation.

Completely ridiculous arguments!!</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c089b36da811f97dda2067</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:44:35 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c089b36da811f97dda2067</link>
				<description>I agree.

I can't see how difficult this is to grasp.

Bitcoin has utility (i.e. a secure way to transfer money) and it is not free to acquire (you have to expend energy and computational resources). So in the abstract sense, there clearly is a floor that has been established.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c088c8ecad04605402ec59</guid>
				<title>0rang3Cru5h</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:40:40 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c088c8ecad04605402ec59</link>
				<description>&gt;&gt;(a) the fact that you can use them to pay your taxes to the U.S. government. NOTE: Despite what Wall Street et all may think, a measurable portion of the world does not pay taxes to the US Government, That said, this is a critical issue regarding an alternative transaction medium. 
&gt;&gt;... and (b) that the Federal Reserve is a potential dollar sink and has promised to buy them back
Not that it is important, but... what exactly would the Federal Reserve &quot;Spend&quot; to buy back dollars? What would the Fed give me for my dollars? I guess they could use MBS or UST, which they currently hold a lot of, but wouldn't that just be buying dollars with dollars.
Rather than trying to explain what a Bitcoin is worth, please explain what a Dollar is worth, other than $1 of US Tax liability.
About $1500 dollars can be exchanged for 1 ounce of Gold while about 2 Bitcoin are needed for an ounce of Gold. 
If and or as long as exchanges exist for Bitcoin, which china has demonstrated, can be outlawed by a government, then a market value for it exists. Defining a theoretical &quot;value&quot; seems like an academic exercise so lets take it the other way, what is the value of a dollar, other than $1 in US Govt Tax liability?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c08850ecad046f5402ec59</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:38:40 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c08850ecad046f5402ec59</link>
				<description>These folks were not in the minority.

In the early days of the internet, nobody could figure out how to monetize the freemium models.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c083f16da811b871da2051</guid>
				<title>scott7ree</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:20:01 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c083f16da811b871da2051</link>
				<description>The floor is the community. Similar to placing a value in a public company or even a country. Bitcoin is based on people using it. If everyone stopped using Facebook, the stock would go to zero. If everyone left the United States, the currency would go to zero. If everyone stops using Bitcoin, the value will go to zero.
However, the Bitcoin community is proving to be very resilient and has been rewarded greatly with a meteoric increase in value.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c08226ecad04a24402ec63</guid>
				<title>Government spending on financial services</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:12:22 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c08226ecad04a24402ec63</link>
				<description>You are saying that the horse wagon will stay, it will just use combustion engine :)

To quote you: &quot;Hell F'ing no, of course that won't work&quot;.

By the way your &quot;floor value = zero&quot; argument is that &quot;because I say so&quot;... Not sure you noticed that.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c080f96da811446ada2053</guid>
				<title>move along</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:07:21 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c080f96da811446ada2053</link>
				<description>We have moved along. You are the one who got stuck in an old frame of reference.
You need to catch up.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c07f2369bedd681302ec58</guid>
				<title>I have US dollars - inflated by more than 2%</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:59:31 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c07f2369bedd681302ec58</link>
				<description>I love listening to people, who are shifting the topic fundamentally, in order to support their arguments.
No payment for useless service for you.

The floor value argument as cited in this particular discussion does not mention any need of interest bearing bank account. Stay on the topic, don't act infantile.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0754f6bb3f7291402ec59</guid>
				<title>Joseph Crain</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:17:35 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0754f6bb3f7291402ec59</link>
				<description>The value of bitcoin comes from its ability to do work. Fundamentally it removes dependence on trust. This allows it to act as a bank, a courier, a broker, an escrow service, an arbitrator, a lottery, a ballot system, or any other trust dependent service that generally requires a vast amount of resources to uphold an acceptable level of security.

Most people look at bitcoin and see a market chart expressed in terms of USD (or another fiat currency). Somewhat unfortunate for bitcoin is that the term &quot;bitcoin&quot; represents both the BTC/USD chart (the currency) and the system of distributed trust that gives it value (the technology).

Speculation has certainly been a part of the chart's story. But skeptics who don't see past the chart are likening their understanding to a &quot;the world is flat&quot; viewpoint.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c073acecad04ff3002ec55</guid>
				<title>David Lumen</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:10:36 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c073acecad04ff3002ec55</link>
				<description>BTC has several functions that derive it's value. Just as a currency it can be spent with merchants or used to invest. The denominations of BTC are inherent and therefore less costly to maintain than other currencies in terms of fraud and denominational divisions. This is also slightly applicable with precious metals in that some gold sellers have been hollowing out bars and replacing it with similarly weighted material. I know that this is an extreme example, but once again it's almost impossible to invest with micro-transactions the way you could with BTC. The exchanges for trading never close (besides maintenance), so the value is constantly changing. You can claim that the crashes imply that BTC will fail, but how do you reply to the opposite? How will BTC devalue given it's current media attention, limited supply, and the inability to counterfeit BTC? Sure you can buy from a sketchy merchant or use bad security practices, but the reality is that if you follow good practices BTC in a cold-wallet with a Faraday cage even an EMP wouldn't be able to destroy your copy of the block chain or coins.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c07395eab8ea5f7702ec5d</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:10:13 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c07395eab8ea5f7702ec5d</link>
				<description>&quot;3. Slowly loosing value. (but will start to very quickly loose value if the shit hits the fan)&quot;

You were on a roll there until you started blabbing non sense... Don't be a child. US Dollars have not lost any value. Only if you were a complete friggin moron and unplugged from the system, put your dollars in a shoe box or under your mattress would they have lost value. If you just use the brain you were born with (a big assumption I know) and put your dollars in the same exact interest bearing accounts that exist because of said upward sloping inflation lines, you'd be just fine.

Is that really too hard for you to understand? Inflation is positive, and so is interest rates? Really, this confuses you? Holy crap how do you people tie your shoes in the morning?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c072176bb3f72e0d02ec5c</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:03:51 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c072176bb3f72e0d02ec5c</link>
				<description>Now you're getting somewhere. The value of Bitcoin isn't in it's intrinsic value because of course it has none. The value of Bitcoin is in the technology. Meaning, companies and payment systems should be structured around this new technology.

As far as whether we should make an actual currency out of said technology. Hell F'ing no, of course that won't work....

But the technology is definitely here to stay...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c071a26bb3f7990802ec59</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 14:01:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c071a26bb3f7990802ec59</link>
				<description>Another one joining the club of: I'm not going to answer the simple question posed and instead I'm going to ask myself a different question and answer it.

Do you people not realize that none of you are answering the question? What is the value of Bitcoin? Not why is it convenient, not why is it a technological breakthrough, not why is it a wet dream for libertarians, the question is how do you quantify it's VALUE.

Why not just tell the truth. You can't, it's floor price is zero. Move along people....</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c070ff6da811b23cda2058</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:59:11 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c070ff6da811b23cda2058</link>
				<description>You can't, but you can grow a friggin brain and put your dollars in an interest bearing account and none of your dollars will ever lose value again.

I love listening to the mindless masses that complain the value of the dollar is being diminished. NO IT'S NOT ! If you put a dollar in the bank in 1920, it's worth the same amount today as it was then you child.

Here's a tip, don't put it in a shoe box. Problem solved. Would you like my mailing address for payment of my services? :)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c070a86da811823ada2051</guid>
				<title>Thon Brocket</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:57:44 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c070a86da811823ada2051</link>
				<description>Value derives from utility.

Bitcoin has real usefulness as an efficient money-shifter - see my post up yonder - and demand follows. The value, as for anything in this wide world, is determined by what people are prepared to give for it. 

It's that simple. Just the old, old mechanism of the open market, working as it always has, and always will.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06f386da8116536da2052</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:51:36 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06f386da8116536da2052</link>
				<description>&quot;As it get's harder to mine each individual coin so the &quot;floor value&quot; of the coins increases exponentially.&quot;

Try not to strain your brain too much my friend, the answer is ZERO. Bit coin has a floor price of ZERO. If you need an explanation of why this is, then I pray for your future children. That's damn near child abuse...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06eb969bedd5e6a02ec61</guid>
				<title>David Lumen</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:49:29 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06eb969bedd5e6a02ec61</link>
				<description>The US and EU have no intention of banning it. Wall Street intends to invest in the coming month from my understanding of some rulings. The reality is that the volatility is the risk of any early-investment. You'd do well to remember that this currency is just over 4 years old and has already hit gold parity once. It's speculative inertia in a sense. There have been clear attempts to flash crash certain exchanges, and still the value sits relatively stable. Without a reason to stop investing people will obviously assume that the stability will lead to further booms, leading to interest and thus value.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06eabeab8eae86b02ec5b</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:49:15 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06eabeab8eae86b02ec5b</link>
				<description>&quot;However, so is the ability to determine the intrinsic value of Gold&quot;

Yes, exactly, now you're using your head. The people who try to VALUE gold are also idiots just like those that try to value Bitcoin. They have no quantifiable value.

It's just the greater fool theory people. The only value these two things have is that you are betting someone in the future will also want it. They could EASILY stop wanting it.

The USD on the other hand is backed by the biggest military in the world and the largest banking system in the world that by law is forced to buy sell trade in the currency and the US government that says by law you have to pay taxes in said currency. 

You have a child mind if you can't understand why the US dollar is a backed currency, and gold and Bit coin are not. A child mind that has no concept of economics...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06db0ecad04802102ec57</guid>
				<title>Vix-Trader</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:45:04 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06db0ecad04802102ec57</link>
				<description>Again, you are NOT answering the question. You are talking about usefulness, but the question posed to you is one of VALUE. 

Just like Krugman said, these are two different questions. Try answering the right one, I bet you can't :)</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06c156bb3f7737c02ec5d</guid>
				<title>David Lumen</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:38:13 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06c156bb3f7737c02ec5d</link>
				<description>The limit on BTC is a major selling point with investors, so unless an alt-coin can propose to have a major network propagating the end to their coin mintage before the BTC network there's not really a point in competing. The code for BTC is open source, so anyone that has an idea to add something to another cryptocurrency could just as easily apply that update to BTC protocol. I guess my point would be that the average consumer will go to the biggest name, as long as the service and appreciation remain competitive.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06a0f69beddb56202ec5b</guid>
				<title>SETI</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:29:35 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c06a0f69beddb56202ec5b</link>
				<description>Will Digital Currency Replace the US Dollar? Wall Street Strategy to Make Bitcoin the Global Currency?

The Strategy to Make Bitcoin the Global Currency

A Utopia of Equality or Jumping from the Frying Pan to the Fire?

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.globalresearch.ca/will-digital-currency-replace-the-us-dollar-wall-street-strategy-to-make-bitcoin-the-global-currency/5361021&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.globalresearch.ca/will-digital-currency-replace-the-us-dollar-wall-street-strategy-to-make-bitcoin-the-global-currency/5361021&lt;/a&gt;

Also, what exactly are these algorithms calculating, and FOR WHOM?

SETI</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0678eecad04631402ec59</guid>
				<title>Winged</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:18:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0678eecad04631402ec59</link>
				<description>The bottom line is, you have a (growing) segment of the population that understands: dollars, just like bitcoins, are numbers on computers. They have the following advantages over bitcoin:
1. Widely accepted as a store of value and means of payment.
2. Issued by an entity that is (at least trying) to keep their value only slowly depreciating.
3. Comes in paper form for easy transactions without an internet connection. 

And the following disadvantages:
1. Annoying to transfer over the internet.
2. Hard to transfer across borders.
3. Slowly loosing value. (but will start to very quickly loose value if the shit hits the fan)
4. Being printed out of thin air to buy government debt which is very likely going to be defaulted on.

For some people that looks like a pretty good trade. 

I've watched the exchange of alternative crypto-currency for several months now, and one thing I've noticed is: short of technical difficulties its very hard for their value to drop to zero. Is there enough money on the exchange to buy every bitcoin for 700$? Not even close, but there's also not enough bitcoins on the exchange to sell to everyone for 700$ either. 

The people buying bitcoin now are preparing for a possible economic paradigm shift sometime in the future. If it starts, it'll already be too late to gain any buying power through bitcoin, people will be flocking to it because they don't want to loose the buying power they already have. 

Really, when you get right down to it, there's no hard floor anywhere above 0 for bitcoin or the US dollar. But for bitcoin there is buy support for it all the way down simply because it has so much upside potential. And most of that buy support never gets tested because people realize how valuable bitcoins might be... later. 

I know it must look scary from the outside because in an emergency (like we saw two weeks ago with the china regulation) there are lots of people running for a very small exit door. Any serious bitcoin holders don't get too worried about the short term drops though, most of us hold because we believe you will all be running for a very small entrance door if the financial trouble hits (think 2008). We could be wrong, you could be wrong, but (especially if you have a lot of wealth) you may want to consider placing bets on both sides of the table for this one.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0645aeab8ea735802ec5d</guid>
				<title>cypherdoc</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 13:05:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0645aeab8ea735802ec5d</link>
				<description>the &quot;mechanism&quot; by which the Fed &quot;buys back&quot; USD's is via &quot;selling&quot; US Treasuries back into the market. this removes excess USD from the system thus theoretically supporting the USD value by increasing its &quot;scarcity&quot;. the problem with this theory is that UST prices would plummet, interest rates would skyrocket, interest payments on the federal debt would skyrocket, and the economy and US gov't funding mechanism would implode. any sophisticated investor does not believe the Fed will ever do this. their solution to every problem is &quot;print&quot;. and that is what they would be forced to do even more of to control those skyrocketing interest rates via buying back more UST's which would be an abrupt reversal in strategy which would debase the USD even more. there is no floor on the USD where the Fed is concerned.

look at where we are right now: the Fed and US gov't are trumpeting a fantastic recovery since 2008, yet the Fed refuses to significantly back off on QE. $75B/mo QE is still an enormous amount and is unprecedented. Bernanke is scared to death to do more and is conveniently on his way out the door. Yellen will be left to clean up his mess.

there is no floor on gov't support via taxation either as this presumes the US gov't is invincible and that US taxpayers have infinitely deep pockets. every empire in history has fallen over time usually b/c of monetary debasement. are we so special?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05fa26bb3f7a36a02ec5d</guid>
				<title>cypherdoc</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 12:45:06 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05fa26bb3f7a36a02ec5d</link>
				<description>no, mining is a security mechanism against attack from a gov't or hostile entity.

it also is a necessary activity to create a ledger for all transactions that have occurred on the network.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05f1e6da811d205da2057</guid>
				<title>cypherdoc</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 12:42:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05f1e6da811d205da2057</link>
				<description>that could very well be now with the trillions of irredeemable debt the US has built up.

not only that, the Fed is technically insolvent.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05e9becad04df0402ec55</guid>
				<title>Nigel Hess</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 12:40:43 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05e9becad04df0402ec55</link>
				<description>Well, you're correct that there are no limits on clones, and anyone is welcome to make their own copycat payment network. Bitcoin is really just a protocol, or standard, that people are voluntarily choosing to adopt. Bitcoin, though, has a number of advantages over any clone that you could create. These advantages include: First mover/Network effect, acceptance as payment, infrastructure (Bitcoin businesses, start ups, etc.), mining power (security against double spends), media attention, etc...

Thinking of another protocol, internet protocol, might be helpful. Anyone is welcome to create their own clone of internet protocol, but why hasn't this happened? Why aren't boat loads of people switching over to a new &quot;internet protocol&quot; every week? Partially for the above advantages, which apply equally to IP, and partially because clones provide no added value, or compelling reason to transition.

The *real* threat would be a new protocol, analogous to Bitcoin, that isn't a clone but rather provides real value above and beyond Bitcoin. Then people would have a compelling reason to switch over. Then again, the Bitcoin protocol could always just be modified at that point to incorporate whatever innovation this new &quot;coin&quot; brings with it. This seems most likely, considering the vested interest already in Bitcoin.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05c9eeab8ea774a02ec61</guid>
				<title>cypherdoc</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 12:32:14 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05c9eeab8ea774a02ec61</link>
				<description>the answer is very simple: Bitcoin is provably FAIR.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05c1969beddc64002ec64</guid>
				<title>Nigel Hess</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 12:30:01 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05c1969beddc64002ec64</link>
				<description>This goes back to the question of &quot;intrinsic value&quot; or utility. Gold has some obvious utility, outside of being a store of value, in both industry and as jewelry. Bitcoin has utility as a decentralized payment network. After all, Bitcoin is a new technology that enables arbitrary value to be sent anywhere in the world instantaneously, at near zero cost (zero friction), and with no point of failure or trusted third party. The utility here should be obvious. The fact that &quot;bitcoins&quot; can't be held in the palm of your hand, like physical gold, is irrelevant. 

Once you acknowledge that the Bitcoin protocol, as a payment network, has utility, and that the sole unit of account on this network is in the form of &quot;bitcoins&quot;, it shouldn't be surprising that they should command a legitimate market price, independent of pure speculation. Anything that is both useful and scarce will have a price.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05710ecad04f47302ec5b</guid>
				<title>Thon Brocket</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 12:08:32 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c05710ecad04f47302ec5b</link>
				<description>This. As a transmission medium, it's digital copper, digital hydraulic oil. The more power you need to transmit, the more work you need your machine to do, the more coal you need to shift down the conveyor; then the more rubber belting, or hydraulic oil, or kWh of current you need, to do the job.

Looked at it that way, it's standard economic theory. It's probably even amenable to numerical analysis using analogues of elementary engineering design formulae. How much current will this circuit draw at an input voltage of 440V? What diameter of hydraulic hose, and hence what volume of oil, do I need for this hydraulic power press application? How many BTC do I need to maintain a gross throughput of $1million dollars a month in my remittance business to the Philippines? Or to India, where the velocity is less because of tougher regulation?

That value-of-utility is quite easily quantified, using this sort of approach, and after that it's everyday stuff for any competent finance director.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0522169beddd02e02ec64</guid>
				<title>Government spending on financial services</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:47:29 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0522169beddd02e02ec64</link>
				<description>Can anyone compile the figure, that how much all levels of governments, municipalities in the USA pay for financial services in a year?

Let us see how much of tax payers money would be saved if all those transactions would be conducted in Bitcoin.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c051336bb3f7b74b02ec5f</guid>
				<title>Jacob Shumaker</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:43:31 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c051336bb3f7b74b02ec5f</link>
				<description>Bitcoin has intrinsic value because it is useful as a decentralized protocol for electronic payments (just like HTTP and TCP for the Internet). It also has other uses that I won't get into. It gains value (usefulness) through network effects and the infrastructure built on top of it with startups such as Bitpay (recently invested in by Asia's richest man Li Ka-shing), Coinbase (with $25 million in VC funding), Circle (with $9 million series A funding), Coinsetter, Robocoin, BTX Trader and many others.

For example Bitcoin ATMs can allow you to sent money to family/friends from overseas at a much lower cost than Western Union. Several services allow you to lock-in the exchange rate on both sides at the time of transfer removing the risk from volatility.

Due to fixed supply the price of Bitcoins will follow the market capitalization of the Bitcoin network. With time (several years) the market will mature and the prices will stabilize.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c050586bb3f7054e02ec56</guid>
				<title>I have US dollars - inflated by more than 2%</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:39:52 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c050586bb3f7054e02ec56</link>
				<description>Mr. Krugman, please let me know where can I send my US dollars that lost more than 2% value, so that the Federal Reserve can buy it back from me?

Please send me the URL of the web site which gives all the details - and the contact information where people like me can request US dollar buy back.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04fb66da8117e5dda2051</guid>
				<title>Giorgio</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:37:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04fb66da8117e5dda2051</link>
				<description>If you want to start digging deep into what the true value of the US $ is, then good luck with that...the reasons you mention, ability to pay US taxes, &quot;backed&quot; by the FED (don't make me laugh) are a joke globally, and is precisely why other countries are exiting $ positions wherever possible. The real reason for $ supremacy over the past 40 years has been the petrodollar, and that is going away. Things like Bitcoin are arising as global alternatives precisely because the $ is very quickly becoming valueless and people don't trust the US Govt, Congress, or the FED to do the right thing. and no, saying that the US $ is backed by guns isn't a valid argument either.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04fb6ecad04286902ec59</guid>
				<title>&lt;nobody&gt;</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:37:10 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04fb6ecad04286902ec59</link>
				<description>Using what assets? Try FRN's. Always remember there is no third party auditing this crew, and a large sigma change in price must accompany a large sigma change in the market. Could just be the exponential phase of adoption, or ...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04ee26bb3f7894502ec59</guid>
				<title>ahmed.sharieff.79</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:33:38 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04ee26bb3f7894502ec59</link>
				<description>Also, what's holding up the value of Facebook stock? What's the floor on that? If it's zero, why is it valuable to anyone?</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04e5beab8ea392b02ec63</guid>
				<title>BTC</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:31:23 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04e5beab8ea392b02ec63</link>
				<description>What you are missing here, is that the confidence in Bitcoin already exists. 

It is not based on traditional economic zones - since people use Bitcoin across the boundaries of any existing economic zone - it is global, and it has been working globally from the very beginning. Right now there are more BTC users than the entire population of many smaller countries.

The confidence is not tied to government blessings, since government did not create or operate Bitcoin.

There is not much what governments can do against Bitcoin, other than put roadblocks to transfer Bitcoin to fiat back and forth easily. But any government ban would be as useless as trying to ban barter or &quot;war on drugs&quot;.

The bottom line is, that if people really want to use BTC - they will.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04e576bb3f7844502ec5f</guid>
				<title>ahmed.sharieff.79</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:31:19 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04e576bb3f7844502ec5f</link>
				<description>The Fed &quot;promising to buy&quot; dollars means nothing. What would they buy them with? Gold? Food rations? I'm confused on what this even means. So, with that gone, the dollar has no floor either. Being able to pay your taxes isn't enough of a reason to hold onto dollars all year - you can just buy dollars right before paying your taxes, and pay them, and be dollarless again.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04bcbeab8ea602602ec58</guid>
				<title>bdbr</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:20:27 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04bcbeab8ea602602ec58</link>
				<description>Not a worthy analogy because it assumes that some people being wrong about one thing increases the likelihood of other people being wrong about something else.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04b7c6bb3f76a4502ec57</guid>
				<title>Don Harder</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:19:08 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04b7c6bb3f76a4502ec57</link>
				<description>But what happens to the value when faced with competition? There may be limits on BTC, but there is no limit on clones. At the end of the day, all it has is brand recognition and since there isn't even a broad infrastructure of vendors willing to accept it as payment, there is no guarantee as of yet it's going to win the brand game. People making bets at the current levels of valuation just don't understand how incredible the risk they are exposed to yet.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04a0feab8eab02102ec5f</guid>
				<title>Don Harder</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 11:13:03 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c04a0feab8eab02102ec5f</link>
				<description>Speculative value isn't intrinsic and is limited by the greater fool theory. 

I too wonder how the Fed proposes to put a floor on inflation with a buy-back program (more exp. needed Joe) but the dollar is backed by a country that has the largest military in the world allowing it to control its interests, oil and other commodities are priced in dollars, etc...</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c044dd69bedd350a02ec58</guid>
				<title>pontius</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 10:50:53 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c044dd69bedd350a02ec58</link>
				<description>The Fed will buy back your dollars with what, more dollars?
Seriously, what is the Fed going to buy your dollars with, if not gold or silver?
Full faith and credit?
WTF is that?
I'm just not under the spell of this Jedi mind trick, and never have been, but I am in awe of the fact that hundreds of millions are.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c043e5ecad048d4c02ec61</guid>
				<title>Krugman's evilisly bad tech predictions</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 10:46:45 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c043e5ecad048d4c02ec61</link>
				<description>Krugman, who predicted in 1998 that by 2005 the impact of the Internet on economy will be no greater than the fax machines :) - is now struggling to understand an other tech intrusion into economics: Bitcoin - and digital currencies.

In his stupidly titled blog entry in the New York Times he brings in to the discussion as a help for him, a fellow economist, Brad DeLong, who asks all the questions that Joe is asking here now.

The floor value of Bitcoin.

Krugman explains: &quot;Underpinning the value of the dollar is a combination of 
(a) the fact that you can use them to pay your taxes to the U.S. government, and 
(b) that the Federal Reserve is a potential dollar sink and has promised to buy them back and extinguish them if their real value starts to sink at (much) more than 2%/year (yes, I know).&quot;

Basically for Krugman the floor value of dollar is 
a) the government ability to collect taxes without receiving plenty of chickens, goats
b) the Federal Reserve promised to buy them back...

I am not sure how collecting tax gives value to a currency - it does not make it gold for sure.

The Federal Reserve buy back argument is interesting, considering that The Fed is privately owned entity - not a US government institution, as the name cunningly suggests.

I would be curious, how would The Fed buy back trillions of dollars if everybody wanted to get rid of it, because the value dropped more than 2%? And what would The Fed pay for the dollar? Gold? Does The Fed own enough gold to cover all the dollar it prints?

The floor value of Bitcoin is not centered around government tax collection and a private entity, which probably has no ability to do what it is promising.

The floor value of Bitcoin is that people around the world, have decided to accept Bitcoin to play the role of making payments for products and services among the members of the grass root, volunteer community - without the need of the assistance of any traditional third party (government, existing financial system, financial infrastructure).

The community is open for anyone, people or businesses can join and participate, regardless of their location, nationality.

Hell, even the government can join in and accept Bitcoin for collecting taxes - and do all government businesses in Bitcoin. 

I bet it would be much cheaper for taxpayers than what the government pays for financial services now. Not to mention that it would be completely transparent for tax payers where the government is spending their money.

I think these are much more solid floor value propositions than the US dollar ever offered.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c03b386bb3f78e2602ec5c</guid>
				<title>bitcoinstu</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 10:09:44 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c03b386bb3f78e2602ec5c</link>
				<description>Bitcoin = holistic payments solution in which the “shares” are the system. Its value is intrinsically tied to the very high level of convenience it can offer as a payment system, convenience at a level that should be the norm in today's connected world.

As I see it Bitcoin as it currently stands is a unique payments solution in which Bitcoins function both as shares of the system and as an efficient and cheap method of payment.

With service providers such as Bitpay merchants and customers can essentially choose to transact fiat currency, using Bitcoins as an intermediary to avoid credit card fees and take advantage of super-fast payments.

But users can also choose to retain some Bitcoins as if they were owning shares of the Bitcoin network. These shares may also be traded between users. It is as if Bitcoin had its IPO from the very outset, which is what makes it so exciting for people wanting to get into the “company” early.

The fact is Bitcoin is an entirely new concept being tested in real time. I use the words “company” and “share” just to give an idea of the way the phenomenon is working. I think it is a remarkable 21st-century achievement which has given and continues to give those who do their own research the opportunity to join in at what is still an early stage in its development.

Read more: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.businessinsider.com/everyone-who-believes-in-bitcoin-should-try-to-answer-this-question-2013-12#ixzz2osQRihYZ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.businessinsider.com/everyone-who-believes-in-bitcoin-should-try-to-answer-this-question-2013-12#ixzz2osQRihYZ&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c03a916da811461fda2053</guid>
				<title>bitcoinstu</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 10:06:57 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c03a916da811461fda2053</link>
				<description>Bitcoin = holistic payments solution in which the “shares” are the system. Its value is intrinsically tied to the very high level of convenience it can offer as a payment system, convenience at a level that should be the norm in today's connected world.

As I see it Bitcoin as it currently stands is a unique payments solution in which Bitcoins function both as shares of the system and as an efficient and cheap method of payment.

With service providers such as Bitpay merchants and customers can essentially choose to transact fiat currency, using Bitcoins as an intermediary to avoid credit card fees and take advantage of super-fast payments.

But users can also choose to retain some Bitcoins as if they were owning shares of the Bitcoin network. These shares may also be traded between users. It is as if Bitcoin had its IPO from the very outset, which is what makes it so exciting for people wanting to get into the “company” early.

The fact is Bitcoin is an entirely new concept being tested in real time. I use the words “company” and “share” just to give an idea of the way the phenomenon is working. I think it is a remarkable 21st-century achievement which has given and continues to give those who do their own research the opportunity to join in at what is still an early stage in its development.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c034686da8118a0eda2055</guid>
				<title>Vitalik Buterin</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 09:40:40 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c034686da8118a0eda2055</link>
				<description>It seems to be a common psychological trait to want to have some kind of &quot;floor&quot; or certainty behind everything; indeed, I think that that is a major reason why many people support centralized and authoritarian institutions: they are the only kind of institutions that can provide that illusory perception of certainty, even if they actually just serve to shuffle risk over to catastrophic black swan events in the long term. In reality, however, that kind of thinking is fatally flawed; in the real world, there is no absolute certainty behind anything (even mathematics, since you can't trust your own mind to be 100% infallible). Gold seems to have a price floor because it is pretty, but the reality is that lots of things are pretty, including many ornaments you can buy in Chinatown for $1. Gold only has the elevated value because of (1) speculative / store-of-value investment, and (2) because it is a Veblen good - its specific kind of beauty is valued only because it is rare. If people stopped buying gold for investment reasons, gold would fall to $100, and everybody would start walking around with gold necklaces - making gold lose even more value since it's no longer that special and perhaps fall to $10. The US dollar has no price floor either; sure, the US government accepts them for taxes, but it does not accept them for taxes at any specific ratio. If the market value of a US dollar falls by a factor of 1000, the value of each dollar toward paying your income tax liability will also drop by 1000x - in fact, even more so, because in such a scenario everyone with even a losing business in real-value terms would have to pay tax on capital &quot;gains&quot; on the increased number of dollars that they have. There's also nothing technically guaranteeing that the US government will keep accepting US dollars. The Zimbabwean government doesn't accept its own currency. It's all a probabilities game.

See also: &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoinmagazine.com/8640/an-exploration-of-intrinsic-value-what-it-is-why-bitcoin-doesnt-have-it-and-why-bitcoin-does-have-it/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://bitcoinmagazine.com/8640/an-exploration-of-intrinsic-value-what-it-is-why-bitcoin-doesnt-have-it-and-why-bitcoin-does-have-it/&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02fc2ecad044c2902ec65</guid>
				<title>Dean Wormer</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 09:20:50 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02fc2ecad044c2902ec65</link>
				<description>Bitcoin is scrip from a bunch of research labs that didn't want to pay for cloud computing CPU time. fundamentally worthless.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02d6e6da8113d76da2067</guid>
				<title>Smaulgld</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 09:10:54 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02d6e6da8113d76da2067</link>
				<description>Artificial Mining Scarcity 

The computer mining of Bitcoins, the trading component of the Bitcoin system, is an artificial construct. Mining for real commodities like silver or drilling for oil has real costs and real returns. Silver is needed to power the electronics (without silver Bitcoin doesn’t work!) and solar industries and oil is needed, among many things, to heat millions of homes, for gasoline to power millions of cars and to create countless plastic products. Thus, the costs of mining for silver and oil are justified in that they lead to the extraction of silver and oil and the prices of these commodities can be valued based on their need and demand. In contrast, the mining costs of Bitcoins can only be justified if demand can be created for the Bitcoins themselves. 

The underlying value of the Bitcoin itself is based on a Bitcoin computer mining game that wastes electricity to solve math problems that don’t need to be solved, and therefore is not a meaningful measure of value. Bitcoin mining is in effect, the solving of riddles for riddles’ sake. How can a value be placed on Bitcoins if they have no intrinsic value or unique properties? If Bitcoin’s value is in its use as a crypto currency, why wouldn’t any crypto currency do?
&lt;a href=&quot;http://smaulgld.com/bitcoin-a-mining-disaster-waiting-to-happen/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://smaulgld.com/bitcoin-a-mining-disaster-waiting-to-happen/&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02d436da8115579da2057</guid>
				<title>Junayd</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 09:10:11 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02d436da8115579da2057</link>
				<description>Wouldn't the floor on the value of total bitcoins be the value of the money/effort/productivity that it takes to mine the coins in the first place (equipment/electricity etc.) As it get's harder to mine each individual coin so the &quot;floor value&quot; of the coins increases exponentially.

I would also suggest that the &quot;floor&quot; to the value of the dollar is the value of the paper it's printed on. I'm unsure how the fact you can pay your taxes in them is relevant at all?! When we're looking at the scenario of a floor value we pretty much have to assume that the US government is no longer a going concern.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02ba56bb3f71b0302ec68</guid>
				<title>jamesxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 09:03:17 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02ba56bb3f71b0302ec68</link>
				<description>Actually, those folks were in the minority.

Also, it's not even a worthy analogy.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02b50ecad04a62002ec61</guid>
				<title>jamesxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 09:01:52 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02b50ecad04a62002ec61</link>
				<description>No.

BTC is *intrinsically* volatile with respect to all other currencies.

There will *never* be stability - by definition.

Unless entire economic zones adopt BTC as a real currency (say the entire Carribean starts to use BTC for everything) - it will always be a very risky crap shoot.

'Still has risk' ?

BTC is *pure risk*.

The value of BTC could be 0 tomorrow and the likelihood of that is not that small.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02abd6bb3f74b0302ec65</guid>
				<title>jamesxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:59:25 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02abd6bb3f74b0302ec65</link>
				<description>Your arguments make no sense.

I hate Krugman but he is right.

There is no reason for anyone to own Bitcoin - without that confidence, it could crash any instance.

Bitcoin is a meme that will be around for a long time, but that's about it.

It cannot be taken seriously because it is too volatile.

Once the US and EU ban it, it's game over.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0284ceab8ea765c02ec5d</guid>
				<title>buckethead</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0284ceab8ea765c02ec5d</link>
				<description>IIRC, certain PHD economists prognosticated a bleak future for Internet commerce in those earlier days. Now certain PHD economists are making similar predictions about Bitcoin</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02330ecad04020d02ec65</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:27:12 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c02330ecad04020d02ec65</link>
				<description>&quot;Bitcoin is only in its infancy&quot; which explains the volatility and the bubble like charts.

Has anyone created a chart for Facebook or Twitter before the IPO? If these companies could have been traded pre-IPO, then you would see similar wild swings and a similar bubble. However, unlike Bitcoin, early investor access to these companies were only for the privileged few.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0226969beddf33d02ec58</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:23:53 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c0226969beddf33d02ec58</link>
				<description>I recall the early days of the internet.

When lots of folks were saying, you can't make money if you give everything away for free.

Folks were also saying is, how do you monetize a digital brochure?

However, those who can see past their own physical biases will realize that there is more going on here 'digital coins',</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c022576da811285cda205b</guid>
				<title>Btc</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:23:35 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c022576da811285cda205b</link>
				<description>Bitcoin is only in its infancy and the ability to determine a price or value is difficult. However, so is the ability to determine the intrinsic value of Gold, which has been around much longer. The value of Gold has declined almost 30% in 2013 and this is despite several leading gold experts claiming an intrinsic value nearly 9x its current level. As for price stability, this is likely to increase over time as transaction levels grow and distortions from trading runs and regulatory shocks become less regular. Bitcoin still has risk. Best to approach it prudently, with an eye towards risk management, and not overallocation of personal wealth. 

We comment on related issues on our blog at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitmorecoin.com/blog.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; &gt;http://www.bitmorecoin.com/blog.html&lt;/a&gt;</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c021a1eab8ea024c02ec5e</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:20:33 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c021a1eab8ea024c02ec5e</link>
				<description>The speculative value of bitcoin itself is extremely valuable.

Think about Macao and Las Vegas, cities that both thrive on nothing but gambling. Are these cities not creating revenue?

Now think of all the world's stock markets? Do these exchange not profit just on people speculating?

Now think of a global currency like Bitcoin and its variants. I can loan, short, buy futures, buy GHs rate, buy alt-coins, etc... a multitude of ways to speculate on alternative sides. When someone for example buys a Tesla using Bitcoins, he actually sells Bitcoins. When miners mine Bitcoins and sell to pay for their hardware and energy costs, they actually sell Bitcoins. Bitcoins are sold almost every day, yet the price keeps going up? That is because speculation has value and speculation with high returns have even more value in this fiscal environment with paltry interest rates.

The current world situation in fact is position for Bitcoin to really explode. The lack of trust in the USD. The financial controls in China. The European crisis and the confiscation of money in Cyprus. The billions of unbanked people of the world. The paltry returns on both loans. 

Now your telling me that some economics ivory tower dude who can't grasp the abstraction is asking for a floor? What is the floor for the gambling cities of Macao and Las Vegas? Does gambling create anything useful???</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c01f47eab8ea1a4c02ec55</guid>
				<title>CarlosCarlos</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:10:31 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c01f47eab8ea1a4c02ec55</link>
				<description>Easy answer.

The utility of Bitcoin is proportional to the amount of money that you can transfer across borders. The bigger bitcoin liquidity grows, the larger the amount you can transfer without affecting the price. 

Note: Other alternative coins have lower liquidity, so their liquidity (and their price) is not as high as bitcoin.</description>                            
			</item>
       			<item>
				<guid>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c01dc1eab8eade4402ec61</guid>
				<title>buckethead</title>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:04:01 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.businessinsider.com/c/52c01dc1eab8eade4402ec61</link>
				<description>The FRB will buy back FRNs which lose value at a rate greater than 2% annually? At what price (exchange rate denominated in euros, for instance?), and using what assets? This I need to know.

I openly admit that Joe is more knowledgeable regarding finance than me. I see the world through simple eyes. This is a simple claim Joe makes. I just want to understand. (What if it's true?) (Who is the arbiter?)</description>                            
			</item>
         </channel>
</rss>

